<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2024-01-28T20:02:05Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 28 Jan 2024 20:02:05</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-01-28T20:02:05Z</published><updated>2024-01-28T20:02:05Z</updated><id>e0b5b871-2b7a-45cd-9c2e-b8f946b38436</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://imgproxy.nanxiongnandi.com/P_O89MPBYlhmFIfXN1-KWHdQIOZ40lkQcMHMZlMdWf8/w:1280/aHR0cHM6Ly9pbWcu/bmFueGlvbmduYW5k/aS5jb20vMjAyNDAx/L0J1a2hhbnNhblNl/b3VsLmpwZw.jpg" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/e0b5b871-2b7a-45cd-9c2e-b8f946b38436.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world, Russia is reportedly changing tactics in its attempt to capture the city of Avdiivka in Ukraine. According to the Institute for the Study of War (ISW), Russia plans to fight through the city 'block-by-block.' However, the Kremlin denies reports that Russian President Vladimir Putin reached out to the US for talks on ending the war in Ukraine. Meanwhile, an article discusses what to do when your counteroffer is better than your new job offer, highlighting the dilemma faced by individuals in such situations. In a personal experience, someone shares their decision to quit Amazon Prime, finding it easier than expected and prompting them to reevaluate various aspects of their life. Stanley, a popular brand, admits that its TikTok-famous mugs are made with lead after all, raising concerns about the safety of the products. Google is debuting a new Chrome feature where artificial intelligence (AI) can write posts for users, showcasing the advancements in AI technology. Lise Meitner, a brilliant scientist who helped discover nuclear fission, never won a Nobel Prize despite being nominated 49 times, shedding light on the biases and oversights in the award system. Gig driving, which was seen as a glimmer of hope for many people with disabilities, is proving to be a dead end for some individuals, highlighting the challenges faced by this group in finding sustainable employment opportunities. In the sports world, there is an enormous financial divide among the four NFL quarterbacks still hoping to win the Super Bowl, emphasizing the disparities in earnings within the industry. On a different note, the non-profit organization behind Wikipedia and a crypto exchange are recognized as top companies for work-from-anywhere jobs, with some positions offering salaries over $100,000. Lastly, an article features a millennial DINK (Dual Income, No Kids) who appreciates the flexibility of a childfree lifestyle during a medical crisis, showcasing the advantages of such a lifestyle choice. Additionally, the Violectric V266 Headphone Amp is recommended for music enthusiasts, promising an enhanced listening experience.
    </summary></entry></feed>