<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2024-01-29T08:03:46Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Mon, 29 Jan 2024 08:03:46</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-01-29T08:03:46Z</published><updated>2024-01-29T08:03:46Z</updated><id>163428b1-cd8d-47d8-a428-fb68757fe774</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://imgproxy.nanxiongnandi.com/P_O89MPBYlhmFIfXN1-KWHdQIOZ40lkQcMHMZlMdWf8/w:1280/aHR0cHM6Ly9pbWcu/bmFueGlvbmduYW5k/aS5jb20vMjAyNDAx/L0J1a2hhbnNhblNl/b3VsLmpwZw.jpg" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/163428b1-cd8d-47d8-a428-fb68757fe774.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of technology, there have been some exciting developments recently. One such development is the use of the "time_ago_in_words" feature in Rails, which allows users to journey into the past by displaying the time elapsed since a certain event. This feature adds a touch of magic to Rails applications, making them more interactive and engaging for users.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another interesting project that has caught attention is the creation of a personalized quiz game using Flutter, AWS Amplify Gen2, and Amazon Bedrock. This game allows users to test their knowledge in a fun and interactive way, with personalized questions and challenges. The combination of Flutter's user-friendly interface, AWS Amplify Gen2's powerful backend capabilities, and Amazon Bedrock's robust infrastructure makes for a seamless and enjoyable gaming experience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the realm of coding, there has been a new development in the Ransack library. The latest update introduces the "Autorização" feature, which allows users to permit or deny certain search and sorting operations. This feature adds an extra layer of control and security to the Ransack library, ensuring that users have the ability to customize their search and sorting options according to their preferences.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, there is an exciting open-source project called OpenCiv1, which aims to rewrite the source code of the classic game Civilization 1. This project allows developers and enthusiasts to contribute to the recreation of this iconic game, making it accessible to a wider audience and ensuring its preservation for future generations. The OpenCiv1 project is a testament to the power of open-source collaboration and the passion for preserving gaming history.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;These recent developments in technology and coding showcase the constant innovation and creativity happening in the world. From adding magical features to web applications, creating personalized quiz games, enhancing library functionalities, to rewriting classic game source codes, the possibilities are endless. As technology continues to evolve, we can expect even more exciting advancements in the future.
    </summary></entry></feed>