<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2024-01-28T15:48:09Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 28 Jan 2024 15:48:09</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-01-28T15:48:09Z</published><updated>2024-01-28T15:48:09Z</updated><id>d96f643b-85b5-4828-8632-031c9b5f3cb6</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://imgproxy.nanxiongnandi.com/P_O89MPBYlhmFIfXN1-KWHdQIOZ40lkQcMHMZlMdWf8/w:1280/aHR0cHM6Ly9pbWcu/bmFueGlvbmduYW5k/aS5jb20vMjAyNDAx/L0J1a2hhbnNhblNl/b3VsLmpwZw.jpg" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xiayanzheng/xiayanzheng.github.io/main/voice/d96f643b-85b5-4828-8632-031c9b5f3cb6.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent news, a special monitor has suggested that former US President Donald Trump may have falsified disclosures regarding a $48 million loan, potentially indicating tax evasion. This report has raised concerns about the financial practices of the former president. In another development, a video has emerged highlighting a personal transformation regarding climate change. The individual, who previously did not worry about the issue, now expresses concern and acknowledges the importance of addressing climate change. This shift in perspective reflects the growing awareness and urgency surrounding environmental issues. Additionally, a new AI library called LangGraph has been introduced, designed for building stateful, multi-actor applications using LLMs (Language Models) on top of LangChain. This advancement in artificial intelligence technology opens up possibilities for creating complex applications with multiple actors and state management. On a different note, an exploration into the decline of hammerhead sharks has been conducted through the perspective of local divers. This study sheds light on the challenges faced by these majestic creatures and emphasizes the need for conservation efforts to protect their populations. Lastly, there is a reflection on the history of Unix desktops and the lessons that can be learned from them. This retrospective analysis offers insights into the evolution of desktop computing and the potential for innovation in the future.
    </summary></entry></feed>