<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2024-01-28T15:44:56Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 28 Jan 2024 15:44:56</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-01-28T15:44:56Z</published><updated>2024-01-28T15:44:56Z</updated><id>aed4c684-47da-4e67-b918-93337da98da5</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://imgproxy.nanxiongnandi.com/P_O89MPBYlhmFIfXN1-KWHdQIOZ40lkQcMHMZlMdWf8/w:1280/aHR0cHM6Ly9pbWcu/bmFueGlvbmduYW5k/aS5jb20vMjAyNDAx/L0J1a2hhbnNhblNl/b3VsLmpwZw.jpg" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xiayanzheng/xiayanzheng.github.io/main/voice/aed4c684-47da-4e67-b918-93337da98da5.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent news, a special monitor has suggested that former President Donald Trump falsified disclosures regarding a $48 million loan, potentially indicating tax evasion. This report raises concerns about the integrity of Trump's financial disclosures. Additionally, there is a video highlighting a personal transformation regarding climate change, where the individual expresses a shift from not worrying about it to now being concerned. On the technological front, LangGraph, an AI library, has been introduced for building stateful, multi-actor applications using LLMs on top of LangChain. This development showcases advancements in artificial intelligence and its potential applications. In the realm of environmental conservation, an exploration into the decline of hammerhead sharks is being conducted through the perspective of local divers. This research aims to shed light on the factors contributing to the decline of this species. Furthermore, there is a reflection on the history of Unix desktops and the lessons that can be learned from them. Lastly, Adept AI has unveiled Fuyu-Heavy, a new multimodal model specifically designed for digital agents. This model demonstrates advancements in the field of digital agents and their capabilities.
    </summary></entry></feed>