<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>LF-Air</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml</id><updated>2024-01-28T15:54:06Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Sun, 28 Jan 2024 15:54:06</title><link href="https://xiayanzheng.github.io/rss.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-01-28T15:54:06Z</published><updated>2024-01-28T15:54:06Z</updated><id>4a2e99c1-363b-40e4-9a9f-066105ec4218</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://imgproxy.nanxiongnandi.com/P_O89MPBYlhmFIfXN1-KWHdQIOZ40lkQcMHMZlMdWf8/w:1280/aHR0cHM6Ly9pbWcu/bmFueGlvbmduYW5k/aS5jb20vMjAyNDAx/L0J1a2hhbnNhblNl/b3VsLmpwZw.jpg" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/4a2e99c1-363b-40e4-9a9f-066105ec4218.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent news, a special monitor has suggested that former President Donald Trump falsified disclosures regarding a $48 million loan, potentially indicating tax evasion. This report raises concerns about the integrity of Trump's financial disclosures and the possibility of illegal activities. In another story, a video highlights a personal transformation regarding climate change. The individual expresses a shift from not worrying about climate change to now being concerned about its impact. This video reflects the growing awareness and concern surrounding the issue of climate change. Additionally, there is news about LangGraph, an AI library designed for building stateful, multi-actor applications using LLMs on top of LangChain. This development in artificial intelligence showcases the continuous advancements in technology and its potential applications. Furthermore, an article delves into the decline of hammerhead sharks, exploring the issue through the perspective of local divers. This piece sheds light on the environmental challenges faced by these marine creatures and the importance of conservation efforts. Lastly, there is a reflection on Unix desktops and the lessons we can learn from them. This article reminisces about the past and emphasizes the value of understanding history to inform future decisions. Overall, these news stories provide insights into various aspects of the world, from political controversies to environmental concerns and technological advancements.
    </summary></entry></feed>