<rss version="2.0" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd"><channel><title>Trend Tech</title><link>https://novasparkxx.github.io/trend_tech.xml</link><description>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</description><language>en-us</language><itunes:author>Tony</itunes:author><itunes:summary>In the world of technology, there have been several notable developments recently. Eggscape Entertainment, a company specializing in social gaming on mixed reality headsets, has successfully raised $4.25 million in funding. This investment will allow them to further develop their gaming platform and provide users with immersive gaming experiences.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meanwhile, Australian IT professionals are being urged to prepare for the imminent EU AI Act, which will introduce regulations on artificial intelligence for the first time. This act will have significant implications for the use and development of AI in Australia, and IT professionals need to be proactive in understanding and complying with the new regulations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a groundbreaking move, AI2, an artificial intelligence research institute, has released the first-ever truly open-source LLM (Language Learning Model). This development is expected to drive a critical shift in AI development, as it allows researchers and developers to collaborate and build upon each other's work more effectively.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the gaming front, Temple Gates Games has launched Dominion, a popular board game, in a digital format for mobile and PC. This move allows board game enthusiasts to enjoy their favorite game on digital platforms, providing convenience and accessibility.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the realm of app analytics, a new tool called Custom Interactions for AppExchange App Analytics has been introduced. This tool aims to provide better user insights by allowing developers to customize and analyze user interactions with their apps. This will enable developers to make data-driven decisions and improve the user experience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the field of mixed reality headsets, Stanford researchers are calling for further study on video passthrough technology. This technology allows users to see the real world while wearing a headset, enhancing the immersive experience. The researchers believe that more research is needed to fully understand the potential benefits and challenges of this technology.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Coris, a company specializing in SMB risk management, has raised $3.7 million in funding. They are aiming to drive an AI-driven paradigm shift in SMB risk management, leveraging artificial intelligence to provide more accurate and efficient risk assessment and mitigation strategies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, Dynatrace Perform 2024, a conference focused on observability, has ushered in a new era of observability in cloud development environments. This conference has showcased the latest tools and techniques for monitoring and analyzing cloud-based applications, enabling developers to gain valuable insights and optimize their applications for better performance.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, these recent developments highlight the continuous advancements in technology and the growing importance of AI, gaming, app analytics, mixed reality, risk management, and observability in various industries. These tools, products, and projects are shaping the future and opening up new possibilities for innovation and growth.</itunes:summary><itunes:image href="https://imgproxy.nanxiongnandi.com/P_O89MPBYlhmFIfXN1-KWHdQIOZ40lkQcMHMZlMdWf8/w:1280/aHR0cHM6Ly9pbWcu/bmFueGlvbmduYW5k/aS5jb20vMjAyNDAx/L0J1a2hhbnNhblNl/b3VsLmpwZw.jpg" /><item><title>Trend Tech report on</title><description>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/a9632a9f-fe6b-4369-a2c4-0f7951cc3d86.mp3</guid><enclosure url="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/a9632a9f-fe6b-4369-a2c4-0f7951cc3d86.mp3" /><enclosure type="audio/mpeg" /><enclosure length="os.stat_result(st_mode=33188, st_ino=283121, st_dev=2065, st_nlink=1, st_uid=1001, st_gid=127, st_size=3797760, st_atime=1706806268, st_mtime=1706806268, st_ctime=1706806268)" /></item></channel></rss>