<rss xmlns:ns0="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0"><channel><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link>https://novasparkxx.github.io/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</link><description>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</description><language>en-us</language><ns0:author>Tony</ns0:author><ns0:summary>In the world of cloud computing, there are several exciting developments taking place this February. One of the highlights is the Private Preview of Azure Site Recovery support for Azure Trusted Launch VMs with Windows OS. This new feature allows users to securely recover their virtual machines in the event of a disaster or system failure.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another interesting development is the ability to consume Cloud Storage objects on Google Kubernetes Engine (GKE) using the Kubernetes API. This feature, known as Part I of the series, provides users with a seamless way to access and utilize cloud storage resources within their Kubernetes clusters.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meanwhile, AWS Glue introduces a new chat experience using natural language processing. This feature, called Amazon Q Dataset Integration, allows users to interact with AWS Glue using conversational language, making data integration tasks more intuitive and user-friendly.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In other news, Deutsche B&#246;rse Group is reaping significant benefits by moving to S/4 HANA on Google Cloud. This migration has brought improved performance and efficiency to the financial services company, demonstrating the advantages of leveraging cloud infrastructure for business operations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additionally, Azure Virtual Network Manager security admin rule has become generally available in 30 regions. This feature enables users to manage and enforce security policies within their virtual networks, enhancing the overall security of their cloud environments.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, a new report delves into the crucial question of whether to pay ransomware demands or not. This report explores the various factors and considerations that organizations face when dealing with ransomware attacks, shedding light on the complex decision-making process.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, the highlighted developments include Azure Site Recovery support for Azure Trusted Launch VMs, the Kubernetes API integration for consuming Cloud Storage objects on GKE, the natural language chat experience in AWS Glue, the migration of Deutsche B&#246;rse Group to S/4 HANA on Google Cloud, the availability of Azure Virtual Network Manager security admin rule, and the insightful report on ransomware payment decisions. These advancements showcase the continuous innovation and evolution of cloud technologies, providing professionals with numerous opportunities to enhance their cloud careers.</ns0:summary><ns0:image href="https://imgproxy.nanxiongnandi.com/P_O89MPBYlhmFIfXN1-KWHdQIOZ40lkQcMHMZlMdWf8/w:1280/aHR0cHM6Ly9pbWcu/bmFueGlvbmduYW5k/aS5jb20vMjAyNDAx/L0J1a2hhbnNhblNl/b3VsLmpwZw.jpg" /><item><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight report on</title><description>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 17:59:32 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/35fd7b53-5a6c-40f1-b5fe-62c51cc0c97b.mp3</guid><enclosure url="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/35fd7b53-5a6c-40f1-b5fe-62c51cc0c97b.mp3" /><enclosure type="audio/mpeg" /><enclosure length="os.stat_result(st_mode=33188, st_ino=801990, st_dev=2049, st_nlink=1, st_uid=1001, st_gid=127, st_size=3012960, st_atime=1706810372, st_mtime=1706810372, st_ctime=1706810372)" /></item><item><title>Cloud Chronicles: Exploring Azure Site Recovery, AWS Glue, Cloud Career Tips, Ransomware Dilemma, Kubernetes API, S/4 HANA Migration, and Azure Virtual Network Manager</title><description>In the world of technology, several developments have taken place recently. Azure Site Recovery now offers support for Azure Trusted Launch VMs with Windows OS, providing a private preview for users. This feature enhances the security and reliability of virtual machines on the Azure platform. Additionally, AWS Glue introduces a new chat experience called Amazon Q Dataset Integration, which allows users to integrate Amazon Q datasets within AWS Glue using natural language. This feature is currently in the preview version. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For those looking to advance their cloud careers, a report highlights 29 no-cost ways to leap ahead in February. This resource provides valuable insights and tips for individuals seeking to enhance their skills and knowledge in the cloud computing field. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another significant topic covered in recent news is the debate surrounding ransomware payments. A new report delves into the crucial question of whether organizations should pay ransom demands or not. This exploration aims to provide insights and guidance for those facing such situations, as ransomware attacks continue to pose a threat to businesses worldwide. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Furthermore, a guide on consuming Cloud Storage objects on Google Kubernetes Engine (GKE) using the Kubernetes API has been published. This guide assists users in effectively utilizing Cloud Storage objects within the GKE environment, enhancing their cloud storage capabilities. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, Deutsche B&#246;rse Group highlights the benefits of moving to S/4 HANA on Google Cloud. This transition brings significant advantages to the financial institution, leveraging the power and features of Google Cloud's infrastructure. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, Azure introduces the Azure Virtual Network Manager security admin rule, which is now generally available in 30 regions. This tool enhances the security management capabilities of Azure Virtual Networks, providing administrators with greater control and flexibility in securing their network infrastructure.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 18:26:41 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/e315fe56-5fff-4849-ba3d-7b2861dc3d16.mp3</guid><enclosure url="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/e315fe56-5fff-4849-ba3d-7b2861dc3d16.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="os.stat_result(st_mode=33188, st_ino=288522, st_dev=2049, st_nlink=1, st_uid=1001, st_gid=127, st_size=2585280, st_atime=1706812001, st_mtime=1706812001, st_ctime=1706812001)" /></item><item><title>1. "Azure Virtual Network Manager Security Admin Rule Now Available in 30 Regions"&lt;br&gt;2. "AWS Glue Introduces New Chat Experience with Amazon Q Dataset Integration"&lt;br&gt;3. "Retirement of Log Alert Rules with Cross-Workspace Queries on May 31, 2024"&lt;br&gt;4. "29 No-Cost Ways to Boost Your Cloud Career in February"&lt;br&gt;5. "Deutsche B&#246;rse Group Benefits from Moving to S/4 HANA on Google Cloud"&lt;br&gt;6. "To Pay or Not to Pay: Exploring the Crucial Ransomware Question"&lt;br&gt;7. "Consume Cloud Storage Objects on GKE with Kubernetes API - Part I"&lt;br&gt;8. "Private Preview: Azure Site Recovery Support for Azure Trusted Launch VMs (Windows OS)"</title><description>In the world of technology, several significant developments have taken place. Azure Virtual Network Manager security admin rule has now become generally available in 30 regions, providing enhanced security measures for virtual networks. AWS Glue has introduced a new chat experience called Amazon Q Dataset Integration, allowing users to interact with the platform using natural language. However, this feature is currently in the preview version. On the other hand, log alert rules that utilize cross-workspace queries with resource names or qualified name identifiers will be retired by May 31, 2024. This change indicates a shift in the approach to log alerting. Additionally, a report has been published exploring the dilemma of whether to pay ransomware demands or not, shedding light on the crucial decision-making process. In the cloud career domain, professionals can find 29 no-cost ways to advance their skills and knowledge this February, providing valuable opportunities for growth. Furthermore, Deutsche B&#246;rse Group has experienced significant benefits by migrating to S/4 HANA on Google Cloud, showcasing the advantages of this transition. Lastly, Azure Site Recovery now offers support for Azure Trusted Launch VMs (Windows OS) in a private preview, enabling users to ensure the security and integrity of their virtual machines. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, there are a few noteworthy mentions. Azure Virtual Network Manager's security admin rule becoming generally available in 30 regions signifies the continuous improvement and expansion of Azure's security capabilities. AWS Glue's new chat experience, Amazon Q Dataset Integration, demonstrates the platform's commitment to enhancing user interaction and accessibility. The report exploring the decision of whether to pay ransomware demands or not provides valuable insights into the evolving landscape of cybersecurity. Additionally, the availability of 29 no-cost ways to advance cloud career skills this February offers professionals numerous opportunities for personal and professional growth. Lastly, the private preview of Azure Site Recovery's support for Azure Trusted Launch VMs (Windows OS) showcases Microsoft's dedication to providing robust security features for virtual machines. These developments highlight the ongoing innovation and progress in the technology industry.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 18:55:43 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/2c6f374a-23f3-4a03-9d06-213c2e3f6b13.mp3</guid><enclosure url="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/2c6f374a-23f3-4a03-9d06-213c2e3f6b13.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="os.stat_result(st_mode=33188, st_ino=802891, st_dev=2065, st_nlink=1, st_uid=1001, st_gid=127, st_size=3017280, st_atime=1706813743, st_mtime=1706813743, st_ctime=1706813743)" /></item><item><title>Ransomware Dilemma: To Pay or Not to Pay? Azure Site Recovery's Private Preview for Trusted Launch VMs. Exploring Cloud Storage on GKE with Kubernetes API. Retirement of Cross-Workspace Log Alert Rules. Azure Virtual Network Manager Security Admin Rule Now Available in 30 Regions. Deutsche B&#246;rse Group's Benefits of Moving to S/4 HANA on Google Cloud. AWS Glue's New Chat Experience with Amazon Q Dataset Integration. Leap Ahead in Your Cloud Career with 29 No-Cost Tips.</title><description>In the world of cybersecurity, a new report has been released that delves into the crucial question of whether or not to pay ransomware demands. Ransomware attacks have become increasingly prevalent, and organizations are often faced with the difficult decision of whether to give in to the hackers' demands or not. The report explores the various factors that come into play when making this decision, including the potential financial and reputational consequences. It provides valuable insights and guidance for organizations grappling with this issue.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools and products, Azure has introduced a private preview of Azure Site Recovery support for Azure Trusted Launch VMs with Windows OS. This feature enhances the security of virtual machines by ensuring that only trusted and verified firmware and operating system components are used during the boot process. It provides an additional layer of protection against firmware attacks and helps organizations maintain the integrity of their virtual environments.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another development in the tech world is the ability to consume Cloud Storage objects on Google Kubernetes Engine (GKE) using the Kubernetes API. This feature, which is part of a series, allows users to easily access and manage their Cloud Storage objects within the GKE environment. It simplifies the process of working with cloud storage and enables seamless integration between GKE and Cloud Storage.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In other news, support for log alert rules that use cross-workspace queries with resource names or qualified name identifiers will be retired on May 31, 2024. This change will impact organizations that rely on these types of queries for log monitoring and analysis. It is important for affected organizations to make the necessary adjustments and find alternative solutions before the retirement date.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additionally, Azure Virtual Network Manager security admin rule has become generally available in 30 regions. This feature allows organizations to manage and enforce security policies for their virtual networks more effectively. It provides granular control over network access and helps organizations ensure the security and compliance of their virtual environments.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, Deutsche B&#246;rse Group has announced significant benefits from moving to S/4 HANA on Google Cloud. The migration to this advanced business suite has brought improved performance, scalability, and efficiency for the financial services company. It highlights the advantages of leveraging cloud technology for business operations and underscores the growing trend of organizations embracing cloud solutions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the realm of data integration, AWS Glue has introduced a new chat experience using natural language. This feature, called Amazon Q Dataset Integration, allows users to interact with AWS Glue using conversational language. It simplifies the process of data integration and enhances the user experience by providing a more intuitive and user-friendly interface.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, for those looking to advance their cloud careers, there are 29 no-cost ways to do so this February. These resources, which may include webinars, online courses, or certifications, offer individuals the opportunity to enhance their skills and knowledge in the cloud computing field without any financial burden. It is a valuable opportunity for professionals to stay up-to-date with the latest trends and developments in the industry.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 00:06:52 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/7a9ce96b-4d0d-4fa2-b2af-be5b7dfd10af.mp3</guid><enclosure url="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/7a9ce96b-4d0d-4fa2-b2af-be5b7dfd10af.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="os.stat_result(st_mode=33188, st_ino=264607, st_dev=2065, st_nlink=1, st_uid=1001, st_gid=127, st_size=4383360, st_atime=1706832412, st_mtime=1706832412, st_ctime=1706832412)" /></item></channel></rss>