<rss xmlns:ns0="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0"><channel><title>Voyager</title><link>https://novasparkxx.github.io/vite.xml</link><description>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</description><language>en-us</language><ns0:author>Tony</ns0:author><ns0:summary>In recent news, Polygon Labs, a company in the technology industry, has made the difficult decision to lay off 60 employees, which accounts for approximately 19% of its workforce. The CEO of Polygon Labs expressed his regret over this decision but stated that it was necessary for the company's future. In another tech-related news, Apple Vision Pro, a product known for its advanced visual capabilities, has been discovered to have a hidden feature - a thick Lightning cable. This unexpected addition has sparked curiosity among Apple enthusiasts. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moving on to the world of artificial intelligence, VERSES, a prominent player in the field, has brought the concept of natural computing to the forefront of discussions at the prestigious Davos 2024 event. This development highlights the growing importance of incorporating human-like intelligence into AI systems. Additionally, Hikvision, a leading company in the security industry, has launched its second-generation access control system, aiming to enhance the overall access management experience. This new product is expected to provide improved security and convenience for users.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shifting gears, there is positive news for renters in London as rents have finally started to decline after two years of continuous increase. This development brings relief to many individuals struggling with high housing costs in the city. However, concerns arise as corporations are openly attempting to undermine core public institutions. This worrisome trend raises questions about the future of these institutions and their ability to serve the public effectively.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the realm of diversity and inclusion, black workers still perceive code-switching as necessary for their career success. This practice, where individuals alter their behavior or speech to conform to different cultural or professional environments, highlights the challenges faced by black professionals in the workplace. It emphasizes the need for organizations to create inclusive environments where individuals can bring their authentic selves.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the world of space exploration, NASA's Mars Helicopter, which encountered a fatal malfunction, is set to undergo a 'wiggle' test to assess its functionality. This test is a crucial step in determining the helicopter's ability to continue its mission on the red planet. Lastly, President Biden has made it clear that he will veto any attempts to dismantle the SEC breach reporting rule. This rule ensures transparency and accountability in reporting cybersecurity breaches, and Biden's stance aims to prioritize the protection of sensitive information.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, one notable development is the launch of Hikvision's second-generation access control system. This system promises an enhanced access management experience, providing users with improved security and convenience. Additionally, VERSES' focus on natural computing at Davos 2024 showcases the company's commitment to advancing the field of artificial intelligence. These developments highlight the ongoing innovation and progress in the technology industry.</ns0:summary><ns0:image href="https://novasparkxx.github.io/cover/voyager.png" /><item><title>Vite report on</title><description>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 17:57:06 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/e8366927-1c6e-4711-b7cc-67681c35b5d6.mp3</guid><enclosure url="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/e8366927-1c6e-4711-b7cc-67681c35b5d6.mp3" /><enclosure type="audio/mpeg" /><enclosure length="os.stat_result(st_mode=33188, st_ino=796477, st_dev=2049, st_nlink=1, st_uid=1001, st_gid=127, st_size=3944160, st_atime=1706810226, st_mtime=1706810226, st_ctime=1706810226)" /></item><item><title>"The AI Revolution: Unveiling the Latest Innovations and Insights"</title><description>In the world of technology, AveriSource has recently launched a new AI-powered platform and user experience for application modernization. This innovative platform aims to streamline the process of modernizing applications by utilizing artificial intelligence. Additionally, FanDuel TV has brought premier programming to Las Vegas for Super Bowl LVIII, providing an exciting entertainment experience for sports enthusiasts. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the realm of data storage, an article highlights 8 key requirements for AI data storage that are essential for organizations to consider. These requirements play a crucial role in ensuring efficient and effective storage of data for AI applications. Furthermore, RAG Efficiency, Self-Learning Secrets, and the Business of AI are among the must-read articles for the month of January, shedding light on the advancements and challenges in the field of artificial intelligence.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In global financial news, China has taken a significant step to fend off financial stress by merging hundreds of small banks. This strategic move aims to strengthen the country's financial sector and ensure stability in the face of potential challenges. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the world of open-source AI, AI2 has introduced a new open-source LLM (Language Model) that has the potential to redefine the concept of 'open AI.' This development opens up new possibilities for collaboration and innovation in the field of artificial intelligence. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Arc, on the other hand, is working on building an AI agent that can browse the internet on behalf of users. This AI agent aims to simplify the browsing experience by autonomously searching for relevant information and providing users with the desired results. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the realm of tech gadgets, Tim Cook, the CEO of Apple, has been photographed wearing Apple's new face computer. This device represents Apple's foray into wearable technology and showcases their commitment to innovation in the tech industry. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, an interesting article explores the concept of not quitting a job but rather stopping showing up until being fired. This unconventional approach raises questions about workplace dynamics and the potential consequences of such actions. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, the Allen Institute for AI has released OLMo, an open-source project that includes 7B and 1B models. These models have the potential to significantly enhance natural language processing and understanding, opening up new avenues for AI research and development.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 18:24:28 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/547c64ca-702e-43f7-950d-7fe48dfb09e5.mp3</guid><enclosure url="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/547c64ca-702e-43f7-950d-7fe48dfb09e5.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="os.stat_result(st_mode=33188, st_ino=288516, st_dev=2049, st_nlink=1, st_uid=1001, st_gid=127, st_size=3170400, st_atime=1706811868, st_mtime=1706811868, st_ctime=1706811868)" /></item><item><title>Tech Talk: Meta&#8217;s Quest vs. Vision Pro, Microsoft Planner and Project, Hikvision's Access Control, VERSES at Davos 2024, Taylor Swift's Economic Impact, Google Bard's Upgrades, Secureworks Threat Score, Palworld's Game Pass Success, eBay's Legal Troubles, and the Top AS2 Software Solutions in 2024.</title><description>In recent news, Meta's Quest headsets have introduced new features to compete with Vision Pro. These headsets now offer spatial video and pinch controls, enhancing the user experience and providing a more immersive virtual reality environment. Meanwhile, Microsoft Planner and Project are set to unveil exciting updates and improvements in the near future, promising enhanced project management capabilities. Hikvision has launched its second-generation access control system, aiming to provide an enhanced access management experience. This new system will offer improved security and efficiency in managing access to various facilities. VERSES, a leading AI company, has brought natural computing to the forefront of AI discussions at the prestigious Davos 2024 World Stage. This development highlights the growing importance of natural computing in advancing artificial intelligence technologies. Surprisingly, a study has revealed that Taylor Swift's concerts have a significant positive impact on local economies, almost rivaling the economic boost generated by hosting a Super Bowl. This highlights the immense influence of the entertainment industry on local communities. Google Bard has introduced image generation capabilities and a more advanced Gemini Pro, aiming to compete with ChatGPT. These enhancements will provide users with more powerful and versatile AI chatbot experiences. Secureworks has introduced Threat Score, a groundbreaking cybersecurity AI that ushers in a new age of advanced threat detection and prevention. This innovative technology will greatly enhance cybersecurity measures and protect against evolving cyber threats. Palworld, a popular gaming platform, has achieved its biggest third-party Game Pass launch ever, with player numbers nearing 20 million. This success highlights the growing popularity of gaming and the significant impact it has on the entertainment industry. In legal news, eBay has been ordered to pay $59 million after the Department of Justice linked its sales of pill presses to fentanyl drug rings. This serves as a reminder of the importance of regulating online platforms to prevent illegal activities. Lastly, a comprehensive review has identified the top six AS2 software solutions in 2024, offering insights into the best options for businesses seeking reliable and efficient AS2 capabilities. These software solutions have been carefully selected from over 400 reviews, providing valuable guidance for organizations in need of AS2 integration.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 18:54:02 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/f23c9a48-5b70-4cce-8b1b-3dbe2711cfdf.mp3</guid><enclosure url="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/f23c9a48-5b70-4cce-8b1b-3dbe2711cfdf.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="os.stat_result(st_mode=33188, st_ino=802855, st_dev=2065, st_nlink=1, st_uid=1001, st_gid=127, st_size=3216000, st_atime=1706813642, st_mtime=1706813642, st_ctime=1706813642)" /></item><item><title>"Grounding AI Systems: Leveraging Contexts for Enhanced Performance"&lt;br&gt;"Dove Sparks Movement: Acclaim in dozan&#252; innovations&#8217; 2024 SOAM Report"&lt;br&gt;"Google's Gemini Pro: Surpassing GPT-4 on Bard's Global Rollout"&lt;br&gt;"Synth Riders: Rebuilt as Apple Vision Pro's Launch Title"&lt;br&gt;"Bell Canada and SentinelOne: Advanced Endpoint Protection Partnership"&lt;br&gt;"Meta's Reality Labs: Best Quarter Despite $4 Billion Loss"&lt;br&gt;"CDNetworks Upgrades WAAP Solution: AI-Powered Cloud Security 2.0 Platform"&lt;br&gt;"GenAI: Transforming Fraud Detection and Customer Service in Insurance"&lt;br&gt;"Secureworks Threat Score: Revolutionizing Cybersecurity AI"&lt;br&gt;"Cathy Hackl Launches Spatial Dynamics: Spatial Computing &amp; AI Solutions"</title><description>In recent news, there have been several significant developments in the world. One notable event is the grounding of AI systems through the utilization of a combination of derived and user-provided contexts. This approach aims to enhance the understanding and decision-making capabilities of AI systems by incorporating various sources of information.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another noteworthy news is the movement sparked by Dove against harmful beauty standards. Their efforts have earned them acclaim in dozan&#252; innovations' 2024 SOAM Report. Dove's initiative aims to challenge societal norms and promote inclusivity and self-acceptance in the beauty industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google's Gemini Pro Global Rollout on Bard is set to surpass GPT-4 soon. This development in AI technology showcases Google's continuous efforts to advance natural language processing and improve user experiences.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the world of entertainment, the hit rhythm game Synth Riders has been rebuilt as a launch title for Apple Vision Pro. This collaboration between the game developers and Apple aims to provide an immersive and visually stunning gaming experience for users.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bell Canada and SentinelOne have joined forces to provide advanced endpoint protection. This partnership aims to enhance cybersecurity measures and safeguard against evolving threats in the digital landscape.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meta's Reality Labs has had its best quarter, although it still incurred a loss of $4 billion. Despite the financial setback, Meta's continued progress in the field of augmented reality and virtual reality signifies the growing potential of these technologies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;CDNetworks has upgraded its WAAP Solution with the latest AI-powered Cloud Security 2.0 Platform. This enhancement aims to strengthen cloud security measures and protect against emerging cyber threats.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to research, GenAI has the potential to transform fraud detection and customer service in the insurance industry. By leveraging AI technology, insurance companies can enhance their ability to identify fraudulent activities and provide efficient customer service.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Secureworks Threat Score has ushered in a new age of cybersecurity AI. This innovative tool utilizes advanced algorithms to assess and prioritize potential threats, enabling organizations to proactively protect their digital assets.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In other news, Cathy Hackl is set to launch Spatial Dynamics, a new Spatial Computing &amp; AI Solutions Company. This venture aims to explore the possibilities of spatial computing and AI in various industries, offering innovative solutions to complex problems.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;These recent developments highlight the continuous advancements in AI technology, cybersecurity, entertainment, and spatial computing. As the world progresses, these tools, products, and projects contribute to shaping a more technologically advanced and interconnected society.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 00:04:28 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/eea38678-619c-417a-91a4-9b77d74fcec2.mp3</guid><enclosure url="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/eea38678-619c-417a-91a4-9b77d74fcec2.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="os.stat_result(st_mode=33188, st_ino=264601, st_dev=2065, st_nlink=1, st_uid=1001, st_gid=127, st_size=3639360, st_atime=1706832268, st_mtime=1706832268, st_ctime=1706832268)" /></item><item><title>"Russian Artillery Shells from North Korea: Ukraine's Struggle for Supplies"&lt;br&gt;"Consider Function URLs Instead of Amazon API Gateway in 2024"&lt;br&gt;"Uno Platform 5.1 Release: Live Wizard, UI Controls, and Performance Boost"&lt;br&gt;"Mezmo Bolsters Sales Leadership with Chef and Apptio Hires"&lt;br&gt;"Grab ZBrush Alphas &amp; Brushes with 50% Discount"&lt;br&gt;"Water Usage by Quebec's Mining and Metal Industry Revealed"&lt;br&gt;"SAP Employees Feel 'Betrayed' by Radical Return-to-Office U-turn"&lt;br&gt;"H2O.ai Reduces Inferencing Cost with Snowflake Integration"&lt;br&gt;"The Dawn of AI Revolutionizing Voice Interaction"&lt;br&gt;"FAST Apps Outperform Viewer Attention Benchmarks for Linear TV and CTV"</title><description>In recent news, it has been reported that Russia is acquiring a million artillery shells from North Korea, according to Zelenskyy, the President of Ukraine. This development comes at a time when Ukraine is struggling to secure supplies from its own allies. The situation highlights the challenges Ukraine is facing in obtaining necessary resources for its defense. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the tech world, there have been several noteworthy developments. Amazon API Gateway is being questioned as a viable option for use in 2024, with a suggestion to consider Function URLs instead. This raises discussions about the future of API management and the potential alternatives that may emerge. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Uno Platform has released version 5.1, introducing a Live Wizard, new UI controls, and performance improvements. This update enhances the capabilities and user experience of the platform, providing developers with more tools to create cross-platform applications efficiently. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mezmo, a company specializing in sales, has strengthened its sales leadership by hiring new professionals from Chef and Apptio. This move aims to enhance the company's sales strategies and expand its market reach. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the creative industry, ZBrush is offering a 50% discount on a bundle of alphas and brushes, providing artists with a cost-effective opportunity to enhance their digital sculpting and painting workflows. This promotion enables artists to access a wide range of tools and resources to elevate their artistic creations. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On a different note, data has revealed that Quebec's mining and metal industry consumes billions of liters of water annually. This highlights the significant impact of these industries on water resources and raises concerns about sustainability and environmental conservation. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the corporate world, thousands of employees at SAP, a tech giant, have signed a petition expressing their feeling of being "betrayed" by the company's sudden reversal of its return-to-office plans. This demonstrates the challenges and tensions that arise when companies navigate the complexities of remote work and office policies. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;H2O.ai has made an announcement regarding a breakthrough in reducing the cost of inferencing through its integration with Snowflake. This development has the potential to revolutionize the field of artificial intelligence by making inferencing more cost-effective and accessible, opening up new possibilities for AI applications. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, data has shown that FAST apps outperform viewer attention benchmarks for linear TV and overall connected TV (CTV). This highlights the growing influence and effectiveness of FAST apps in capturing and retaining viewer attention, indicating a shift in consumer preferences towards digital streaming platforms. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In summary, the world has witnessed various developments ranging from geopolitical tensions to technological advancements. These news pieces shed light on the challenges faced by nations, the evolution of technology, and the impact of industries on the environment. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, the highlights include the Uno Platform 5.1 release, the discounted ZBrush alphas and brushes bundle, and the breakthrough in reducing the cost of inferencing with Snowflake integration by H2O.ai. These developments offer enhanced capabilities for developers, cost-effective resources for artists, and advancements in artificial intelligence.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 12:02:49 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/fc5405e1-a8a9-48c8-8fe6-3bb6996e9af0.mp3</guid><enclosure url="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/fc5405e1-a8a9-48c8-8fe6-3bb6996e9af0.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="os.stat_result(st_mode=33188, st_ino=802043, st_dev=2049, st_nlink=1, st_uid=1001, st_gid=127, st_size=4368480, st_atime=1706875369, st_mtime=1706875369, st_ctime=1706875369)" /></item><item><title>"The Data Dive: Exploring High-Resolution RGB Data in Time Series Analysis"</title><description>In the world today, there have been several interesting developments. Firstly, a study titled "An Evaluation of Calibrated and Uncalibrated High-Resolution RGB Data in Time Series Analysis for Coal Spoil Characterisation: A Comparative Study" has been conducted, focusing on the use of RGB data in analyzing coal spoil. This research aims to improve the understanding of coal spoil characteristics.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a lighter news, a phenomenon called "beakiating" has caught the attention of bird enthusiasts. Parrots have been observed swinging from perch to perch using their beaks, showcasing their unique and fascinating behavior.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;However, the economic situation in China seems to be a cause for concern. Experts predict that the chances of an economic rebound this year are slim, casting doubt on the country's ability to recover from its current financial challenges.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another study has delved into the world of spatiotemporal statistics, specifically focusing on regularized estimation methods and cross-validation. This research aims to enhance the accuracy and reliability of statistical analysis in this field.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moving on to a personal anecdote, the competitive environment at Yale University has hindered extracurricular participation for some students, including the author. This issue is not exclusive to Yale but highlights a broader problem within the education system.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the political realm, a GOP senator has expressed concern over the extent to which some Republicans defer to former President Trump. The senator finds it unfortunate that certain members of the party prioritize loyalty to an individual rather than the principles of the party.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On a more sustainable note, a refinery in Singapore is paving the way for greener aviation by using used cooking oil to power planes. This innovative approach to fuel production is a step towards reducing carbon emissions in the aviation industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, a review of the popular video game "Persona 3" has been conducted, with the conclusion that there is no perfect version of the game. However, the review suggests that the "Reload" edition comes close to achieving the desired gaming experience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, one notable development is the use of time series-based ensemble model output statistics for temperature forecasts postprocessing. This approach aims to improve the accuracy of temperature predictions by utilizing ensemble models and statistical techniques.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, these recent events and developments highlight the diverse range of topics and advancements taking place in the world today.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:23:41 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/b3818bb9-4e4e-4037-8339-a3c042196c7f.mp3</guid><enclosure url="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/b3818bb9-4e4e-4037-8339-a3c042196c7f.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="os.stat_result(st_mode=33188, st_ino=801874, st_dev=2049, st_nlink=1, st_uid=1001, st_gid=127, st_size=3316320, st_atime=1706891021, st_mtime=1706891021, st_ctime=1706891021)" /></item><item><title>1. "AI Adventures: Unleashing the Power of Speech Recognition on a Raspberry Pi"&lt;br&gt;2. "Lens Data Analytics Revolutionized: Exploring Tempus One AI Assistant"&lt;br&gt;3. "Building the Future: Join Ciro's Journey to Create an SMB Search Engine"&lt;br&gt;4. "Internship Seeker Extraordinaire: Let's Connect and Make Magic Happen!"&lt;br&gt;5. "Gen Z Workforce Empowerment: Chipotle's Innovative Benefits Program"&lt;br&gt;6. "Breaking Barriers: Overcoming a 1920s Law to Propel Wind Energy in the US"&lt;br&gt;7. "GenAI: The Disruptive Force Shaking Up the Entertainment Industry"&lt;br&gt;8. "Transforming Healthcare: Atropos Health's Google Cloud-Powered Clinical Evidence"&lt;br&gt;9. "Stay Updated with Hashnode Blog GitHub Action: Discover the Latest Blogs"&lt;br&gt;10. "In Defense of Meta and Zuck: Unraveling the Truth Behind Social Media"</title><description>In the world, there have been several interesting developments. One notable project is the use of speech recognition, push-to-talk (PTT), and a large action model on a Raspberry Pi. This weekend AI project showcases the potential of these technologies and their application in various fields.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tempus, a company focused on lens data analytics, has launched an AI assistant called 'Tempus One.' This assistant aims to enhance research in the field of lens data analytics, providing valuable insights and improving efficiency in this area.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ciro, a startup from Y Combinator's S22 batch, is currently hiring a Founding Engineer. The engineer will be responsible for building an SMB search engine, which could have significant implications for small and medium-sized businesses.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In other news, Chipotle, the popular fast-food chain, has introduced new benefits to attract and support its growing Gen Z workforce. These benefits aim to provide additional support and incentives for employees, reflecting the company's commitment to its workforce.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;However, the US wind energy sector faces challenges due to an obscure 1920s law. Despite having big plans for wind energy, this law is hindering progress and creating obstacles for the industry's growth.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A study suggests that GenAI, an emerging technology, could disrupt over 200,000 jobs in the entertainment industry by 2026. This highlights the potential impact of artificial intelligence on various sectors and the need for adaptation and preparation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Atropos Health, a healthcare-focused company, is leveraging Google Cloud to generate actionable clinical evidence for healthcare institutions. This collaboration aims to provide valuable insights and improve decision-making processes in the healthcare sector.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools and projects, the Hashnode Blog GitHub Action is worth mentioning. This tool allows users to fetch and display the latest blogs in a visually appealing format, making it easier for readers to access and explore new content.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, there is a statement asserting that Meta and its CEO, Mark Zuckerberg, did nothing wrong, along with the claim that social media as a whole is not at fault. This perspective reflects a different viewpoint on the role and responsibility of social media platforms in various societal issues.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, these developments showcase the ongoing advancements in technology, the challenges faced by different industries, and the potential impact of AI and other emerging technologies on various sectors.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 17:55:01 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/9c0b21c6-21f9-4eb7-a6bc-dc847ac243cc.mp3</guid><enclosure url="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/9c0b21c6-21f9-4eb7-a6bc-dc847ac243cc.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="3247200" /></item></channel></rss>