<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-08-02T16:05:34Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>The Cloud Chronicles: Unlocking Access Control and Launching Cloud Careers with AWS Lake Formation and EMR Serverless</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-08-02T16:05:34Z</published><updated>2024-08-02T16:05:34Z</updated><id>b705b690-eb44-428a-aa35-0464526bcf5a</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/b705b690-eb44-428a-aa35-0464526bcf5a.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of technology, there have been several exciting developments recently. AWS has announced the introduction of fine-grained access control through AWS Lake Formation with EMR Serverless. This new feature allows users to have more control over their data and access permissions. Additionally, AWS has launched the AWS Cloud Support Associate Certificate, providing individuals with an opportunity to kickstart their cloud career.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In other news, Amazon has introduced the Llama 3.1, Mistral Large 2, AWS Step Functions, and updated AWS certifications. These updates aim to enhance the overall user experience and provide more efficient solutions for businesses. Furthermore, there is a guide available on how to significantly reduce SAP storage costs by utilizing Amazon SDK for SAP ABAP and seamless integration with Amazon S3.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the streaming front, Amazon AppStream 2.0 has introduced Red Hat Enterprise Linux Application and Desktop streaming. This allows users to stream and access Red Hat applications and desktops from anywhere, providing greater flexibility and convenience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the realm of artificial intelligence, a landmark partnership has been launched to support AI startups in collaboration with Y Combinator. This partnership aims to provide resources and support to startups in the AI field, fostering innovation and growth.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Azure Container Storage is also making strides in the future of container native storage. With the introduction of container native storage, users can expect improved performance and efficiency in managing their containers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, Amazon Connect has introduced a new feature that enables agents to view pre-approved windows when scheduling time off. This enhancement streamlines the scheduling process and ensures that agents have a clear view of their approved time off.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, AWS Training and Certification has announced new courses and certification updates for July 2024. These updates aim to provide individuals with the latest knowledge and skills in the ever-evolving field of cloud computing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, these developments showcase the continuous innovation and advancements in the technology industry, providing users with more control, efficiency, and convenience in their daily operations.
    </summary></entry></feed>