<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-07-30T16:05:47Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>The AI Empowerment Podcast: Unleashing Customization and Scalability with Phi-3 Fine-Tuning and New Generative AI Models</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-07-30T16:05:47Z</published><updated>2024-07-30T16:05:47Z</updated><id>2360e78f-9592-4e64-ba8b-4bad07b1af94</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/2360e78f-9592-4e64-ba8b-4bad07b1af94.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of technology, there have been several updates and announcements that are shaping the future. Azure AI has introduced Phi-3 fine-tuning and new generative AI models, empowering organizations to customize and scale their AI applications. This development will enable businesses to harness the power of AI and tailor it to their specific needs. Additionally, Amazon has expanded its EC2 D3en instances to the Asia Pacific (Jakarta) region, providing businesses in that area with enhanced computing capabilities. This move will undoubtedly contribute to the growth and development of the region's technological landscape. Furthermore, AWS Training is being leveraged to enable workforces to achieve digital transformation. This training program will equip employees with the necessary skills and knowledge to adapt to the ever-evolving digital world. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, Meta has announced the release of Llama 3.1 405B, 70B, and 8B models in Amazon Bedrock. These models are expected to revolutionize the field of AI and contribute to advancements in various industries. Additionally, AWS DataSync has expanded its support for agentless cross-region data transfers to include opt-in regions. This expansion will facilitate seamless and efficient data transfers between different regions, enhancing data management and accessibility for businesses. These new tools, products, and projects demonstrate the continuous innovation and progress being made in the technology sector, promising a future filled with exciting possibilities.
    </summary></entry></feed>