<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Tech</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml</id><updated>2024-04-27T16:06:22Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>"Database Migration Demystified: Exploring Flyway and Spring Boot in a Populated Environment"</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-04-27T16:06:22Z</published><updated>2024-04-27T16:06:22Z</updated><id>6be749fd-7ee1-47f8-bdde-f493211f1849</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_tech.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/6be749fd-7ee1-47f8-bdde-f493211f1849.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world news, there have been several developments across different areas. Firstly, there is an article discussing the use of Flyway and Spring Boot in a scenario involving a non-empty database. This highlights the importance of these tools in managing and migrating databases effectively.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another news piece focuses on Microsoft's approach to hackathons, emphasizing the use of design-led thinking to unleash creative potential. This highlights the significance of incorporating design principles into the development process to create innovative solutions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additionally, there is an informative article explaining the difference between the &lt;b&gt; and &lt;strong&gt; tags in HTML, providing examples to illustrate their usage. This helps web developers understand the nuances and appropriate application of these tags in their coding.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moving on to the gaming industry, a popular third-person action MOBA game called "神之浩劫 2" is set to begin its Alpha testing on May 2nd. This news excites gamers as they will have the opportunity to explore and experience the game's 14 different characters.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, there is a guide on how to deploy a NextJs project to AWS EC2 using GitHub CI/CD Pipeline. This tutorial provides developers with step-by-step instructions on leveraging these tools to streamline the deployment process and ensure efficient continuous integration and delivery.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, there is no specific information provided in the given news articles.
    </summary></entry></feed>