<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Tech</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml</id><updated>2024-06-06T16:07:31Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Pressing Play: Mastering WordPress Deployment on AWS EC2's Private Subnet</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-06-06T16:07:31Z</published><updated>2024-06-06T16:07:31Z</updated><id>b40a7ff7-508b-4a2c-b0f2-2230fe153fdf</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_tech.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/b40a7ff7-508b-4a2c-b0f2-2230fe153fdf.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent news, there have been several interesting developments around the world. One notable event is the deployment of WordPress on a private subnet in AWS EC2 using a Linux server. This advancement in technology allows for enhanced security and control over WordPress websites, ensuring a safer online experience for users.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additionally, there has been a fascinating project that combines Rust and C++ Barcode SDK to build a command-line barcode reader. This innovative tool enables efficient barcode scanning and decoding using the power of these programming languages. It has the potential to revolutionize various industries that rely on barcode technology.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the realm of virtual reality, Ikea has made an intriguing announcement. The furniture giant is offering real money to individuals who work in its virtual Roblox store. This unique employment opportunity showcases the growing integration of virtual platforms and traditional businesses, providing a glimpse into the future of retail.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, Boeing's Starliner spacecraft has finally taken flight, marking a significant milestone. However, mission control has reported helium leaks during the mission. While this is a setback, it highlights the challenges and complexities of space exploration. It also emphasizes the importance of continuous improvement and problem-solving in the aerospace industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, there have been several noteworthy developments. One such example is the deployment of WordPress on a private subnet in AWS EC2, which enhances website security. Additionally, the creation of a command-line barcode reader using Rust and C++ Barcode SDK showcases the potential for efficient barcode scanning. Ikea's virtual Roblox store offers a unique employment opportunity, blending virtual reality and traditional retail. Lastly, the launch of Boeing's Starliner spacecraft, despite helium leaks, demonstrates ongoing advancements in space exploration.
    </summary></entry></feed>