<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Science and Research</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_science_and_research.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_science_and_research.xml</id><updated>2024-07-11T16:05:36Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Material Matters: Exploring the Impact of Temperature on LPBF Processing</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_science_and_research.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-07-11T16:05:36Z</published><updated>2024-07-11T16:05:36Z</updated><id>7f3176cf-9a01-4dfe-9713-77edb5497877</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_science_and_research.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/7f3176cf-9a01-4dfe-9713-77edb5497877.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world today, several interesting developments have taken place. In the field of materials science, a study published in Materials journal explores the effect of temperature on passive film characteristics of LPBF (Laser Powder-Bed Fusion) processing on UNS-S31603. This research sheds light on the behavior of materials under specific conditions, which can have implications for various industries. Meanwhile, in the realm of genetics, Genes journal presents a comprehensive review of HER2 in cancer biology and therapeutics, providing valuable insights into this important gene and its potential applications in cancer treatment. Additionally, Horticulturae journal showcases an efficient in vitro shoot organogenesis technique for Gaillardia pulchella Foug, accompanied by comparative GC-MS metabolite profiling. This research contributes to the understanding of plant growth and development, offering potential benefits for horticulture. In the field of mathematics, Fractal Fract journal introduces fuzzy differential subordination for classes of admissible functions defined by a class of operators, presenting new mathematical concepts and applications. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moving on to other news, a new book has been released that delves into the question of why teenagers take such risks. This publication offers insights and explanations for the behavior of adolescents, providing valuable information for parents, educators, and researchers. In the realm of aquaculture, Fishes journal presents a data review on the variation in sensitivity to aquaculture chemotherapeutants in crustacean life stages. This research contributes to the understanding of the effects of chemotherapeutic agents on crustaceans, which can have implications for sustainable aquaculture practices. In the field of biomedical informatics, BioMedInformatics journal introduces Chauhan Weighted Trajectory Analysis, a novel approach that reduces sample size requirements and expedites time-to-efficacy signals in advanced cancer clinical trials. This innovative method has the potential to accelerate the development of effective cancer treatments. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Furthermore, Foods journal explores the effects of high-pressure processing pre-treatment on apple fruit for juice production. This research investigates the impact of different processing techniques on the quality and characteristics of apple juice, offering insights for the food industry. In the realm of philosophy and religion, Religions journal presents an analysis of Maimon's enlightened skepticism and its implications for the problem of natural sciences. This philosophical exploration provides a thought-provoking perspective on the relationship between religion and science. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the technology sector, Samsung users are expressing their frustration over the "ridiculous" prices of new flip phones, with the Z Fold6 starting at $1900. This news highlights the ongoing debate surrounding the affordability and accessibility of cutting-edge technology.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, there are no specific mentions in the provided news. However, the various research studies and the book mentioned earlier can be considered as new contributions to their respective fields, offering valuable insights and potential advancements.
    </summary></entry></feed>