<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-08-04T16:06:14Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Streamlining Your Workflows: Exploring Amazon AppStream 2.0 and Red Hat Enterprise Linux</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-08-04T16:06:14Z</published><updated>2024-08-04T16:06:14Z</updated><id>fcdd36e5-5531-43da-a940-0bb57fd0c187</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/fcdd36e5-5531-43da-a940-0bb57fd0c187.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent news, Amazon has introduced a new feature called AppStream 2.0 that allows for the streaming of Red Hat Enterprise Linux Applications and Desktops. This partnership aims to provide a seamless experience for users and enhance the capabilities of AI startups. Additionally, there is a guide available on how to significantly reduce SAP storage costs by using ABAP to call Amazon S3, which integrates seamlessly with SAP ABAP and S3. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the world of technology, AWS Training and Certification has announced new courses and updates for July 2024. This demonstrates their commitment to providing up-to-date training and certification opportunities for professionals in the field. Furthermore, Amazon Connect has introduced a feature that allows agents to view pre-approved windows when scheduling time off, enhancing the scheduling process and improving efficiency.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For those looking to start a career in cloud computing, the AWS Cloud Support Associate Certificate is now available, providing individuals with the necessary skills and knowledge to launch their cloud career. In addition, AWS Lake Formation now offers fine-grained access control through EMR Serverless, allowing for more precise control over data access and security.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, Azure Container Storage is embracing the future of container native storage, offering a solution for efficient and scalable storage for containerized applications. This advancement in container storage technology showcases the continuous innovation in the cloud computing industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Tools, Products, or Projects:&lt;br&gt;- AppStream 2.0 by Amazon: Allows for the streaming of Red Hat Enterprise Linux Applications and Desktops.&lt;br&gt;- AWS Training and Certification Updates: New courses and certification updates available in July 2024.&lt;br&gt;- AWS Cloud Support Associate Certificate: Launch your cloud career with this certification.&lt;br&gt;- Fine-Grained Access Control via AWS Lake Formation with EMR Serverless: Provides more precise control over data access and security.&lt;br&gt;- Azure Container Storage: Embracing the future of container native storage for efficient and scalable storage for containerized applications.
    </summary></entry></feed>