<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-05-15T16:06:05Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>"Securing the Digital Gateway: Safeguarding Sensitive Data with Azure Front Door Web Application Firewall"</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-05-15T16:06:05Z</published><updated>2024-05-15T16:06:05Z</updated><id>bb16cb72-cf1d-449b-b2aa-ffc210e480c4</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/bb16cb72-cf1d-449b-b2aa-ffc210e480c4.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent news, Microsoft has announced the public preview of sensitive data protection for Azure Front Door Web Application Firewall. This new feature aims to enhance the security of web applications by providing protection for sensitive data. With this update, users can now have an added layer of defense against potential data breaches and unauthorized access. Additionally, Amazon RDS for SQL Server has introduced support for SQL Server 2019's SSAS multidimensional mode. This enhancement allows users to leverage the latest features and capabilities of SQL Server 2019 for their data analysis needs. Moving on to Amazon Web Services (AWS), several new functionalities have been introduced. Amazon Bedrock, AWS AmplifyGen 2, and Amazon RDS have all received updates, offering users improved services and features. Lastly, AWS users can now create a custom AWS Certification exam practice tool with Amazon Q Apps. This tool enables individuals to prepare for their AWS Certification exams by providing a personalized and interactive learning experience. With these new tools, products, and projects, the technology landscape continues to evolve, offering enhanced security, improved data analysis capabilities, and innovative learning resources for users.
    </summary></entry></feed>