<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Tech</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml</id><updated>2024-08-23T16:07:32Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Forbidden Knowledge Unleashed: Mastering eBPF/XDP on WSL2</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-08-23T16:07:32Z</published><updated>2024-08-23T16:07:32Z</updated><id>d04f790f-1760-40cc-b933-ee7d0280fbc7</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_tech.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/d04f790f-1760-40cc-b933-ee7d0280fbc7.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of technology, there have been several interesting developments. One significant news is the enabling of eBPF/XDP for Kernel Tinkering on WSL2. This advancement allows users to experiment and make changes to the kernel, providing more flexibility and customization options. Additionally, there is a guide on how to utilize the HTML ruby element for enhanced text annotations in HTML. This feature enables users to add annotations and explanations to specific words or phrases within their web content, enhancing the overall user experience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another noteworthy development is the unveiling of SafeLine WAF's High Traffic Handling Secrets. SafeLine, a web application firewall, leverages Nginx to efficiently handle high volumes of web traffic while ensuring security. This insight into their techniques and strategies provides valuable knowledge for developers and organizations looking to enhance their web application security.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Furthermore, there is an exploration of server-side rendering and database operations in Nuxt.js with Prisma ORM. This article delves into the benefits and implementation of server-side rendering, a technique that improves website performance and user experience. The integration of Prisma ORM, a database toolkit, further enhances the efficiency and functionality of Nuxt.js.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, there is a guide on how to separate files owned by a specific user in Linux. This tutorial provides step-by-step instructions on organizing and managing files based on ownership, allowing for better file management and access control.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, there is no specific information provided in the given news. However, it is worth mentioning that the advancements mentioned above, such as eBPF/XDP for Kernel Tinkering, HTML ruby element, SafeLine WAF, and Nuxt.js with Prisma ORM, can be considered as new tools or projects that contribute to the ever-evolving landscape of technology. These innovations offer developers and users new capabilities and possibilities in their respective fields.
    </summary></entry></feed>