<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Business and Market</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_business_and_market.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_business_and_market.xml</id><updated>2024-06-08T16:07:40Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>The Kiwi Chronicles: Unveiling New Zealand's T20 World Cup Misadventure and Unwanted Record</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_business_and_market.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-06-08T16:07:40Z</published><updated>2024-06-08T16:07:40Z</updated><id>af39784c-72df-4806-9dee-e55a77649548</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_business_and_market.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/af39784c-72df-4806-9dee-e55a77649548.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world news, New Zealand faced a disappointing performance in the T20 World Cup against Afghanistan, leading to them bagging an unwanted record. Meanwhile, an executive from Nippon Steel observed a positive reaction from U.S. Steel workers and others. The NMPA has signed an agreement with Srinivas Healthcare Port Hospital to develop healthcare infrastructure in Mangaluru. Berkshire Hathaway has made a filing showing their purchase of an additional 2.57 million shares in Occidental Petroleum. Gland Pharma has appointed Srinivas Sadu as the Executive Chairman &amp; CEO, while Sri Lanka has been praised by the IMF for making strong progress on debt restructuring. Volvo India has signed a Memorandum of Understanding with Indian universities to offer mentorship programs and internships. The upcoming week will see significant events such as Modi's swearing-in, the India vs Pakistan match, Mutual Funds Data, and the FOMC Meet Outcome. Additionally, drivers have been warned about a 'family and friends' rule that could invalidate their insurance and cost them £1,000. Finally, the moment that the Tories have long dreaded is finally upon them.
    </summary></entry></feed>