<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Tech</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml</id><updated>2024-06-18T16:08:46Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Code Chronicles: Unraveling OOP with JavaScript and Real-Life Examples</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-06-18T16:08:46Z</published><updated>2024-06-18T16:08:46Z</updated><id>1ed056a3-c6c9-4dfd-95f8-083e79373756</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_tech.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/1ed056a3-c6c9-4dfd-95f8-083e79373756.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of programming, there is a focus on mastering Object-Oriented Programming (OOP) concepts such as encapsulation, abstraction, inheritance, and polymorphism. A recent article explains these concepts using JavaScript examples, helping developers understand and implement them effectively.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meanwhile, there is a shift in marketing and communications strategies among startups in the US and Europe. With the ever-evolving digital landscape, startups are adapting their approaches to reach and engage with their target audience. This includes utilizing social media platforms, content marketing, and personalized messaging to create meaningful connections with customers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the tech industry, a new product has been released called the OnexPlayer 游侠 X1 mini. This three-in-one computer boasts an 8.8-inch 144Hz screen and is powered by the Ryzen 7 8840U processor. With a starting price of 5699 元, this device offers a compact and powerful computing solution for users.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additionally, vivo has launched the Pad 3 Pro tablet, equipped with the MediaTek Dimensity 9300 chipset and a massive 11500mAh battery. The tablet comes in a 256GB version and is available for purchase at 2699 元. To further entice customers, vivo is offering a substantial subsidy of billions of yuan, making the Pad 3 Pro an attractive option for those in need of a high-performance tablet.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Tools, Products, or Projects:&lt;br&gt;- OnexPlayer 游侠 X1 mini: A compact three-in-one computer featuring an 8.8-inch 144Hz screen and powered by the Ryzen 7 8840U processor.&lt;br&gt;- vivo Pad 3 Pro: A tablet equipped with the MediaTek Dimensity 9300 chipset and a 11500mAh battery. It comes in a 256GB version and is available at a subsidized price of 2699 元.
    </summary></entry></feed>