<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-06-02T16:07:28Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Virtual Network Verifier Unleashed: Exploring Azure's Latest Tool</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-06-02T16:07:28Z</published><updated>2024-06-02T16:07:28Z</updated><id>c316c264-3e33-4edc-9537-fcd5fa164d6e</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/c316c264-3e33-4edc-9537-fcd5fa164d6e.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of technology, there have been several significant developments. Azure Virtual Network Manager's virtual network verifier has entered the public preview stage, allowing users to test and verify their virtual networks. Additionally, Azure NetApp Files now supports an Active Directory connection per NetApp account, providing enhanced security and access control. Another exciting update is the public preview of Kubernetes Metadata and Logs Filtering in Azure Monitor - Container Insights, enabling users to easily filter and analyze metadata and logs in their Kubernetes environments.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of cloud services, there is a new tool called Pub/Sub import topics that allows users to stream data from AWS Kinesis to Google Cloud effortlessly. This tool simplifies the process of transferring data between these two platforms, making it more convenient for users.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moving on to cybersecurity, a recent article titled "Cloud CISO Perspectives: What the past year tells us about our cybersecurity future" sheds light on the lessons learned from the past year and provides insights into the future of cybersecurity. It is an informative read for anyone interested in staying updated on the latest trends and challenges in this field.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, there are a couple of announcements regarding the retirement and transition of certain services. Azure Time Series Insights will be retired on July 7, 2024, and users are encouraged to transition to Azure Data Explorer. Additionally, it has been noted that TLS 1.3 is incompatible with AWS SDK versions 1.9.5 to 1.10.31 for Java. This information is crucial for developers and users working with these technologies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, these developments showcase the continuous advancements in technology, providing users with new tools, improved security measures, and valuable insights into the future of cybersecurity.
    </summary></entry></feed>