<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.fun/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.fun/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-10-20T16:09:41Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Data Dynamics: Unleashing AWS Innovations for Smarter Sharing and Insights</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.fun/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-10-20T16:09:41Z</published><updated>2024-10-20T16:09:41Z</updated><id>f1da0014-0bac-439b-ad60-1a563c082743</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.fun/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/f1da0014-0bac-439b-ad60-1a563c082743.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent developments within the tech world, Amazon Web Services (AWS) has made significant strides in enhancing its data management and analytics capabilities. The introduction of APIs for data grants in AWS Data Exchange marks a pivotal moment for programmatic data sharing, allowing users to streamline their data access processes. Additionally, the long-awaited zero ETL integration between Amazon Aurora PostgreSQL, Amazon DynamoDB, and Amazon Redshift has officially launched, simplifying data workflows and reducing the complexity of data movement. QuickSight has also improved its functionality by supporting subfolders in restricted folders, facilitating governed data sharing among users. The AWS Lambda console has been upgraded to include real-time log analytics through Amazon CloudWatch Logs Live Tail, providing developers with immediate insights into their applications. Furthermore, Amazon Bedrock now allows for the evaluation of custom model imports, enhancing its machine learning capabilities. The AWS Marketplace has expanded its offerings to include four new currencies and non-US bank accounts for disbursement, broadening its accessibility. The Lambda console now features a built-in Amazon CloudWatch Metrics Insights dashboard, offering key function insights to users. Additionally, Amazon DataZone has launched support for AWS IAM Identity Center account instances, while Amazon RDS Multi-AZ deployment with two readable standbys has introduced support for AWS IAM database authentication, enhancing security and reliability.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;### New Tools, Products, or Projects:&lt;br&gt;1. **AWS Data Exchange APIs for Data Grants**: Enables programmatic data sharing for easier access and management.&lt;br&gt;2. **Zero ETL Integration**: Official launch of integration between Amazon Aurora PostgreSQL, Amazon DynamoDB, and Amazon Redshift.&lt;br&gt;3. **QuickSight Subfolder Support**: New functionality for governed data sharing through subfolders in restricted folders.&lt;br&gt;4. **AWS Lambda Real-Time Log Analytics**: Enhanced console support for real-time log analytics via Amazon CloudWatch Logs Live Tail.&lt;br&gt;5. **Amazon Bedrock Model Evaluation**: Now supports evaluating custom model imports for improved machine learning assessments.&lt;br&gt;6. **AWS Marketplace Currency Expansion**: Support for four new currencies and non-US bank accounts for disbursement.&lt;br&gt;7. **AWS Lambda Metrics Insights Dashboard**: Built-in dashboard for key function insights in the Lambda console.&lt;br&gt;8. **Amazon DataZone IAM Identity Center Support**: New support for AWS IAM Identity Center account instances.&lt;br&gt;9. **Amazon RDS Multi-AZ Deployment**: Now supports AWS IAM database authentication with two readable standbys for enhanced security.
    </summary></entry></feed>