<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Science and Research</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_science_and_research.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_science_and_research.xml</id><updated>2024-02-10T20:04:05Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Podcast Title: "Cutting-Edge Medicine: Unraveling the Science of Precise Tumor Resection and Hip Reconstruction"</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_science_and_research.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-02-10T20:04:05Z</published><updated>2024-02-10T20:04:05Z</updated><id>2823c27c-17b6-4c04-ae7b-c0b951170937</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_science_and_research.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/2823c27c-17b6-4c04-ae7b-c0b951170937.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world, various research studies and developments have taken place across different fields. In the medical field, a study titled "Precise single column resection and reconstruction with femoral head plus total hip replacement for primary malignant peri-acetabulum tumors" explores a surgical technique for treating tumors in the hip area. Another study in the field of ecology, titled "Spatiotemporal Pattern, Evolutionary Trend, and Driving Forces Analysis of Ecological Quality in the Irtysh River Basin (2000–2020)," examines the changes in ecological quality in a specific river basin over a 20-year period.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moving on to psychology, a study investigates the association between childhood trauma and emotion recognition. It suggests that this association is reduced or eliminated when considering factors such as alexithymia and psychopathy traits. In the field of animal research, a study titled "Metabolic and Endocrine Insights in Donkeys" provides insights into the metabolic and endocrine aspects of donkeys.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the realm of biomedicine, an editorial highlights the pathophysiology of chronic kidney disease and its complications. Similarly, another editorial in the journal Medicina focuses on the lymphatic system, discussing the discovery of the system and new perspectives in microsurgical reconstruction and patient rehabilitation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the food science domain, a study explores the preparation of sweet potato porous starch using marine dextranase and investigates its adsorption characteristics. Additionally, a study in rural China examines the impacts of habit formation on food consumption and nutrient intake.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, a study in the field of behavioral sciences investigates the relationship between a competitive school climate and school bullying among secondary vocational school students in China. It proposes a moderated mediation model to understand this relationship.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As for new tools, products, or projects, the provided news does not mention any specific developments in this area.
    </summary></entry></feed>