<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-08-20T16:07:30Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>The Cloud Chronicles: Unleashing the Power of Assured Workloads, Custom Compute, and AI Capabilities</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-08-20T16:07:30Z</published><updated>2024-08-20T16:07:30Z</updated><id>9f89c45b-3944-4fb1-bd9b-238bfe377299</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/9f89c45b-3944-4fb1-bd9b-238bfe377299.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world today, there have been several developments in the technology and cloud computing sectors. Google Cloud has introduced updates and new control packages in Assured Workloads, allowing users to have more control over their infrastructure resources. Additionally, they have launched the GKE custom compute class API, giving users the flexibility to customize their infrastructure resources according to their needs. Looker, a data analytics platform, has opened its semantic layer through a new SQL Interface and connectors for Tableau and other tools, enabling users to access and analyze data more efficiently. Google Cloud has also curated a list of top AI courses for individuals to learn and enhance their skills during the summer. In Saudi Arabia, Google Cloud has expanded its services, providing enhanced data sovereignty and AI capabilities to users in the region. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moving on to Amazon Web Services, they have introduced prioritized and capacity-optimized-prioritized allocation strategies for EC2 instances in their Amazon EMR support. This allows users to allocate resources more effectively and optimize their usage. Additionally, Amazon EC2 On-Demand Capacity Reservations now have new capabilities, including the ability to split, move, and modify additional attributes, providing users with more flexibility in managing their capacity reservations. Lastly, Azure OpenAI Service has launched new deployment and cost management solutions, enabling users to deploy their AI models more efficiently and manage costs effectively.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, Google Cloud has introduced the Assured Workloads feature, which allows users to have more control over their infrastructure resources. They have also launched the GKE custom compute class API, providing users with the ability to customize their infrastructure resources. Looker has opened its semantic layer through a new SQL Interface and connectors for Tableau and other tools, enhancing data accessibility and analysis. Amazon Web Services has introduced prioritized and capacity-optimized-prioritized allocation strategies for EC2 instances in their Amazon EMR support. They have also enhanced the capabilities of Amazon EC2 On-Demand Capacity Reservations, allowing users to split, move, and modify additional attributes. Azure OpenAI Service has introduced new deployment and cost management solutions, enabling users to deploy AI models more efficiently and manage costs effectively.
    </summary></entry></feed>