<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://novasparkxx.github.io/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://novasparkxx.github.io/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-02-02T01:59:32Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight report on Fri, 02 Feb 2024 01:59:32</title><link href="https://novasparkxx.github.io/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-02-02T01:59:32Z</published><updated>2024-02-02T01:59:32Z</updated><id>35fd7b53-5a6c-40f1-b5fe-62c51cc0c97b</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://imgproxy.nanxiongnandi.com/P_O89MPBYlhmFIfXN1-KWHdQIOZ40lkQcMHMZlMdWf8/w:1280/aHR0cHM6Ly9pbWcu/bmFueGlvbmduYW5k/aS5jb20vMjAyNDAx/L0J1a2hhbnNhblNl/b3VsLmpwZw.jpg" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/35fd7b53-5a6c-40f1-b5fe-62c51cc0c97b.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of cloud computing, there are several exciting developments taking place this February. One of the highlights is the Private Preview of Azure Site Recovery support for Azure Trusted Launch VMs with Windows OS. This new feature allows users to securely recover their virtual machines in the event of a disaster or system failure.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another interesting development is the ability to consume Cloud Storage objects on Google Kubernetes Engine (GKE) using the Kubernetes API. This feature, known as Part I of the series, provides users with a seamless way to access and utilize cloud storage resources within their Kubernetes clusters.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meanwhile, AWS Glue introduces a new chat experience using natural language processing. This feature, called Amazon Q Dataset Integration, allows users to interact with AWS Glue using conversational language, making data integration tasks more intuitive and user-friendly.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In other news, Deutsche Börse Group is reaping significant benefits by moving to S/4 HANA on Google Cloud. This migration has brought improved performance and efficiency to the financial services company, demonstrating the advantages of leveraging cloud infrastructure for business operations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additionally, Azure Virtual Network Manager security admin rule has become generally available in 30 regions. This feature enables users to manage and enforce security policies within their virtual networks, enhancing the overall security of their cloud environments.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, a new report delves into the crucial question of whether to pay ransomware demands or not. This report explores the various factors and considerations that organizations face when dealing with ransomware attacks, shedding light on the complex decision-making process.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, the highlighted developments include Azure Site Recovery support for Azure Trusted Launch VMs, the Kubernetes API integration for consuming Cloud Storage objects on GKE, the natural language chat experience in AWS Glue, the migration of Deutsche Börse Group to S/4 HANA on Google Cloud, the availability of Azure Virtual Network Manager security admin rule, and the insightful report on ransomware payment decisions. These advancements showcase the continuous innovation and evolution of cloud technologies, providing professionals with numerous opportunities to enhance their cloud careers.
    </summary></entry></feed>