<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-02-18T20:04:03Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>"The AWS Weekly Roundup: Lunar New Year Celebrations, IaC Generators, NFL's Digital Athletes, and AWS Cloud Club - February 12, 2024"&lt;br&gt;"Cold Tier Support and Object Replication: Azure Blob Storage's Latest Update"&lt;br&gt;"Amazon CloudWatch Synthetics Unveils New Runtimes for NodeJS/Puppeteer and Python/Selenium"&lt;br&gt;"The AI Alliance: Building Relationships and Shaping AI Policy"&lt;br&gt;"Experience the Love of Next '24: Explore the Full Session Catalog Now"</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-02-18T20:04:03Z</published><updated>2024-02-18T20:04:03Z</updated><id>8a01e20c-3db9-4cff-80f4-a28832f30f77</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/8a01e20c-3db9-4cff-80f4-a28832f30f77.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world this week, several noteworthy events took place. Firstly, the Lunar New Year was celebrated, bringing joy and festivities to many cultures around the globe. Additionally, a new Infrastructure as Code (IaC) generator was introduced, providing developers with a powerful tool to streamline their workflow and automate infrastructure management. In the sports realm, the NFL made headlines with the rise of digital athletes, showcasing the increasing integration of technology in sports. Lastly, the AWS Cloud Club was launched, offering a platform for cloud enthusiasts to connect, learn, and collaborate on various projects and initiatives.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, Azure Blob Storage Cold Tier support has now become generally available. This feature enables users to leverage Change Feed and Object Replication capabilities, enhancing their data storage and management capabilities. Furthermore, Amazon CloudWatch Synthetics has released new versions of its NodeJS/Puppeteer Runtime (6.2 and 5.2) and Python/Selenium Runtime (2.1). These updates provide developers with improved performance and functionality for monitoring and testing their applications. Lastly, the Next '24 conference has unveiled its full session catalog, offering a diverse range of sessions and workshops for attendees to explore and learn from.
    </summary></entry></feed>