<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-10-08T16:09:50Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Cloud Chronicles: Navigating the Latest AWS Innovations and Insights</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-10-08T16:09:50Z</published><updated>2024-10-08T16:09:50Z</updated><id>1093868d-5aea-4855-9aa0-583348f84e0f</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/1093868d-5aea-4855-9aa0-583348f84e0f.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent developments across the tech landscape, several significant updates have emerged from Amazon and Microsoft, enhancing user experiences and operational efficiencies. Amazon has introduced automatic time zone redirection in AppStream 2.0, improving usability for global users. Additionally, Amazon WorkSpaces now allows file transfers between WorkSpaces sessions and local devices, streamlining workflows. Amazon Connect has made strides in workload management by enabling forecasts with minimal contact data, while also introducing new read-only permissions for its Contact Lens reports and dashboards. Furthermore, Amazon Connect has enhanced its scheduling capabilities, allowing for multi-day copy and paste of agent schedules. In the realm of cloud services, AWS Partner Central now facilitates the association of private offers to launched opportunities, and Amazon Route 53 Resolver endpoints have added support for DNS-over-HTTPS (DoH) with Server Name Indication (SNI) validation. Meanwhile, Microsoft has launched Drasi, an open-source project aimed at simplifying change detection and response in complex systems. Additionally, users can now sign Microsoft Windows artifacts with keys protected by Cloud HSM, enhancing security protocols.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;### New Tools, Products, and Projects:&lt;br&gt;1. **Amazon AppStream 2.0**: Automatic time zone redirection feature for improved user experience.&lt;br&gt;2. **Amazon WorkSpaces**: New functionality for file transfer between WorkSpaces sessions and local devices.&lt;br&gt;3. **Amazon Connect**: &lt;br&gt;   - Forecast generation for workloads with minimal contact data.&lt;br&gt;   - New read-only permissions for Contact Lens reports and dashboards.&lt;br&gt;   - Multi-day copy and paste functionality for agent schedules.&lt;br&gt;4. **AWS Partner Central**: Support for associating AWS Marketplace private offers with launched opportunities.&lt;br&gt;5. **Amazon Route 53 Resolver**: Support for DNS-over-HTTPS (DoH) with Server Name Indication (SNI) validation.&lt;br&gt;6. **Drasi**: Microsoft’s new open-source project for simplifying change detection and reaction in complex systems.&lt;br&gt;7. **Cloud HSM**: Enhanced security for signing Microsoft Windows artifacts with protected keys.
    </summary></entry></feed>