<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Science and Research</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_science_and_research.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_science_and_research.xml</id><updated>2024-06-24T16:07:10Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>The Soccer Scoreboard: Unveiling the Ultimate Performance Index</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_science_and_research.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-06-24T16:07:10Z</published><updated>2024-06-24T16:07:10Z</updated><id>4642ef2a-4fa2-4d50-97e3-3372d7429967</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_science_and_research.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of professional soccer, a new composite index has been developed to summarize physical performance. This index aims to provide a comprehensive evaluation of players' physical abilities and can be used to assess their overall performance on the field. Additionally, a theoretical model has been proposed to analyze the dynamics of digital media use in religious communities. This model explores how digital media is utilized within religious contexts and its impact on community dynamics.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the field of coatings and protection, a novel flame-retardant paint has been prepared and characterized. This paint incorporates substituted cyclodiphosph(V)azane sulfonomide and their metal complexes as new additives for exterior wood coating protection. This development could lead to improved fire safety measures for wooden structures.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A prospective repeated-measures study has focused on predicting fluid responsiveness in spontaneously breathing patients with hemodynamic stability. This study aims to identify reliable methods for determining fluid responsiveness in these patients, which can aid in their treatment and management.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the field of dentistry, a new approach to restoration planning has been introduced. Digital implant-supported restoration planning is now being placed in autologous graft using titanium implants produced by additive manufacturing. This innovative technique could enhance the precision and effectiveness of dental restorations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The molecular cloning and expression analysis of the geranyllinalool synthase gene (SgGES) from Salvia guaranitica plants has been conducted in the field of horticulture. This research provides insights into the genetic mechanisms involved in the synthesis of geranyllinalool, a compound with potential applications in the fragrance and flavor industries.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the realm of sustainability, a study has focused on modeling CO2 emission forecasting in the energy consumption of the industrial building sector in Thailand. The researchers have enhanced the LISREL-LGM model to incorporate sustainability policies. This modeling approach can aid in predicting and managing CO2 emissions, contributing to sustainable energy practices.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The properties of monolayer and multilayer MoS2-Metal van der Waals interfaces have been investigated in the field of nanomaterials. This research explores the contact properties of these interfaces, which can have implications for the development of advanced electronic devices and materials.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the field of genetics, the complete mitochondrial genome of the Blue Whistling Thrush (Myophonus caeruleus) has been sequenced and analyzed. This genetic analysis provides valuable insights into the evolutionary history and phylogenetic relationships of this bird species.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, in the realm of food safety, the genome- and toxicology-based safety assessment of probiotic Akkermansia muciniphila ONE, isolated from humans, has been conducted. This assessment aims to ensure the safety and efficacy of this probiotic strain for human consumption, contributing to the development of safe and beneficial probiotic products.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Tools, Products, or Projects:&lt;br&gt;- The development of a new composite index for summarizing physical performance in professional soccer.&lt;br&gt;- The preparation and characterization of a novel flame-retardant paint for exterior wood coating protection.&lt;br&gt;- The use of digital media in religious communities and the proposal of a theoretical model to analyze its dynamics.&lt;br&gt;- The prediction of fluid responsiveness in spontaneously breathing patients with hemodynamic stability.&lt;br&gt;- Digital implant-supported restoration planning in dentistry using titanium implants produced by additive manufacturing.&lt;br&gt;- The molecular cloning and expression analysis of the geranyllinalool synthase gene from Salvia guaranitica plants.&lt;br&gt;- The modeling of CO2 emission forecasting in the industrial building sector under sustainability policy in Thailand.&lt;br&gt;- The investigation of the contact properties of monolayer and multilayer MoS2-Metal van der Waals interfaces.&lt;br&gt;- The complete mitochondrial genome sequencing and phylogenetic analysis of the Blue Whistling Thrush.&lt;br&gt;- The genome- and toxicology-based safety assessment of probiotic Akkermansia muciniphila ONE for human consumption.
    </summary></entry></feed>