<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Business and Market</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_business_and_market.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_business_and_market.xml</id><updated>2024-08-06T16:06:48Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>The Trillion-Dollar Club: Unstoppable Stocks and Apple's Potential Impact</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_business_and_market.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-08-06T16:06:48Z</published><updated>2024-08-06T16:06:48Z</updated><id>3deee05d-4e12-448b-bd1e-185342613f80</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_business_and_market.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/3deee05d-4e12-448b-bd1e-185342613f80.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world news, Apple is predicted to potentially contribute to the addition of two stocks to the prestigious $1 trillion club. Meanwhile, Meta, the parent company of Facebook, has issued an apology for removing a post by Malaysia's Prime Minister Anwar Ibrahim, which offered condolences for the assassination of a Hamas leader. The Nikkei 225 index experienced a significant jump of almost 11% following Japan's worst stock plunge since 1987. Evergrande's liquidators are seeking to recover $6 billion from seven defendants, including founder Hui Ka Yan and his ex-wife. The mass imprisonment of rioters in England is raising concerns about the strain it will put on the country's jail system, according to a union warning. In the media industry, CNET has been sold to Ziff Davis, indicating potential future media deals. BNP Paribas is set to acquire AXA's fund business for $5.5 billion, as reported by domain-b.com. The ED (Enforcement Directorate) has filed charges against Lalu Prasad and his son Tejashwi Yadav in relation to the land-for-jobs scandal. Lastly, Quantum Capital Group is planning to acquire IPP Cogentrix from Carlyle for $3 billion, according to the American Public Power Association.
    </summary></entry></feed>