<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Business and Market</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_business_and_market.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_business_and_market.xml</id><updated>2024-08-05T16:06:54Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>The Growth Report: Unveiling the Titans, Delhivery, and More!</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_business_and_market.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-08-05T16:06:54Z</published><updated>2024-08-05T16:06:54Z</updated><id>8998c080-3b29-4e49-8343-12a93999b8cf</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_business_and_market.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/8998c080-3b29-4e49-8343-12a93999b8cf.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world, there have been several notable events and developments. In the business sector, Titan's Q1 results have been reviewed, with analysts highlighting the growth of the international segment and the jewellery sector. Delhivery's Q1 results have also been reviewed, with profit secured but uncertainty rising in B2C volume. The Indian rupee has sunk to the second worst in Asia, despite India topping overseas inflows this quarter. NIIT's Q1 results have shown mixed results, but the commentary on growth remains optimistic. Arkema, a company in the chemical industry, has reported growth in Q2 with sales up 3.8%. Triveni Engineering's Q1 results have been reviewed, with a bright outlook for H2 and a recommendation to maintain a buy. In the sports world, David Beckham-backed Guild Esports is set for a takeover by US-based DCB Sports. Olympic ads have come under fire, raising concerns about how sportspersons can protect their personality rights. Zydus Wellness's Q1 review shows a turnaround in progress, with favorable seasonality lifting the Q1 further. Mold-Tek Packaging's Q1 results review indicates an expected ramp-up of new capacities in H2. These developments reflect the diverse and dynamic nature of the global landscape.
    </summary></entry></feed>