<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-06-09T16:06:56Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>The Cloud Chronicles: Exploring the Latest in AWS, Azure, and Google Cloud (June 3, 2024)</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-06-09T16:06:56Z</published><updated>2024-06-09T16:06:56Z</updated><id>a918cd6c-8b7f-4045-8492-5b03933e2eaf</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/a918cd6c-8b7f-4045-8492-5b03933e2eaf.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world this week, there have been several updates and releases in the technology industry. Amazon Web Services (AWS) introduced the Amazon EC2 U7i instance, which provides enhanced performance and capabilities for users. Additionally, AWS launched the Bedrock Converse API, allowing developers to integrate conversational AI capabilities into their applications. Furthermore, AWS celebrated World IPv6 Day, highlighting the importance of IPv6 in enabling the growth of the internet.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In other news, Microsoft Azure announced the general availability of multi-select delete in Azure Cosmos DB with Data Explorer, providing users with a more efficient way to manage their data. Azure also added support for Azure Monitor log search alert rules in Resource Health, enabling customers to monitor and respond to potential issues more effectively.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google emphasized the benefits that European customers can enjoy with the power of choice through their Sovereign Cloud offering. They highlighted how this solution allows customers to store and process their data within the European Union, ensuring compliance with local regulations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google Cloud and SAP collaborated to forge a path to enduring business innovation in the era of artificial intelligence. They emphasized the importance of leveraging AI technologies to drive innovation and transformation in businesses.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Furthermore, AWS provided a deployment guide for their Web Application Firewall (WAF), offering insights on how to use Centralized Logging with OpenSearch Light Engine to reduce monitoring costs for Amazon WAF logs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the realm of Microsoft Azure, they announced the general availability of long-term backup retention for Azure Database for PostgreSQL Flexible Server, providing users with enhanced data protection and recovery options. Additionally, Azure Cosmos DB introduced continuous backup for accounts using Azure Synapse Link, offering users a seamless backup solution for their data.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, the use of Gateway Load Balancer and Palo Alto Firewall was highlighted as a means to achieve centralized deep inspection of network traffic. This integration allows for enhanced network security and monitoring capabilities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, AWS introduced the Amazon EC2 U7i instance and the Bedrock Converse API. Microsoft Azure added support for Azure Monitor log search alert rules in Resource Health and introduced long-term backup retention for Azure Database for PostgreSQL Flexible Server. Google emphasized the benefits of their Sovereign Cloud offering for European customers and highlighted their collaboration with SAP for business innovation in the AI era.
    </summary></entry></feed>