<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Science and Research</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_science_and_research.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_science_and_research.xml</id><updated>2024-09-07T16:07:14Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Palate Perspectives: Exploring the Science and Sensory Delights of Infant Formula, Sustainable Mobility, Atherosclerosis, Nanomaterials, Polymers, Biodiversity, Genes, Bio-Innovation, Materials, and Water</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_science_and_research.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-09-07T16:07:14Z</published><updated>2024-09-07T16:07:14Z</updated><id>b5fc6f2b-e1fb-4f59-b23f-a8bbf5cf6a5b</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_science_and_research.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of infant nutrition, a study published in Foods, Vol. 13, Pages 2839, explores the variations in sensory attributes of infant formula among different batches and their impact on maternal consumer preferences. The study combines consumer preferences, pivot profile, and quantitative descriptive analysis to gain insights into the preferences of mothers when it comes to choosing infant formula.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sustainability, Vol. 16, Pages 7802, presents a model of sustainable household mobility in multi-modal transportation networks. This research focuses on developing a framework that promotes sustainable transportation options for households, considering factors such as accessibility, affordability, and environmental impact. The aim is to create a more sustainable and efficient transportation system.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Diagnostics, Vol. 14, Pages 1981, offers a narrative review on the role of non-coding RNA in the pathogenesis of atherosclerosis. This research delves into the molecular mechanisms and functions of non-coding RNA in the development and progression of atherosclerosis, providing valuable insights for potential diagnostic and therapeutic approaches.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nanomaterials, Vol. 14, Pages 1457, presents in situ studies on the influence of surface symmetry on the growth of MoSe2 monolayer on sapphire using reflectance anisotropy spectroscopy and differential reflectance spectroscopy. This research explores the impact of surface symmetry on the growth of nanomaterials, contributing to the understanding of their properties and potential applications in various fields.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the field of polymers, Vol. 16, Pages 2533, focuses on the orientation control of perfluorosulfonic acid films through the addition of 1,2,4-triazole during casting. This study investigates the effects of the additive on the orientation and properties of the polymer films, offering insights into the development of advanced polymer materials with controlled characteristics.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Diversity, Vol. 16, Pages 558, analyzes the biodiversity, ecological status, and ecosystem attributes of agricultural ditches based on the analysis of macroinvertebrate communities. This research sheds light on the importance of agricultural ditches in supporting biodiversity and maintaining ecological balance in agricultural landscapes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Genes, Vol. 15, Pages 1174, introduces a new method for conditional gene-based analysis that effectively accounts for the regional polygenic background. This innovative approach allows for a more accurate understanding of the genetic factors influencing various traits and diseases, improving our ability to develop targeted treatments and interventions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another study in the field of polymers, Vol. 16, Pages 2532, explores the bio-innovative modification of poly(ethylene terephthalate) fabric using enzymes and chitosan. This research investigates the potential of enzymatic and chitosan treatments to enhance the properties and performance of poly(ethylene terephthalate) fabric, opening up new possibilities for sustainable and functional textile materials.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Materials, Vol. 17, Pages 4411, investigates the curing and thermal properties of epoxy/amine/phthalonitrile blend. This study explores the behavior of the blend under different curing conditions and analyzes its thermal stability, providing valuable insights for the development of advanced composite materials.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, Water, Vol. 16, Pages 2534, explores the application of immobilized microorganism gel beads in black-odor water with high nitrogen and phosphorus removal performance. This research focuses on developing innovative solutions for the treatment of polluted water, offering a potential method to efficiently remove nitrogen and phosphorus contaminants.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Tools, Products, or Projects:&lt;br&gt;- A framework for sustainable household mobility in multi-modal transportation networks.&lt;br&gt;- Innovative modification of poly(ethylene terephthalate) fabric using enzymes and chitosan.&lt;br&gt;- Immobilized microorganism gel beads for efficient removal of nitrogen and phosphorus contaminants in polluted water.&lt;br&gt;- A new method for conditional gene-based analysis that effectively accounts for the regional polygenic background.
    </summary></entry></feed>