<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Tech</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml</id><updated>2024-09-01T16:07:38Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Azure Adventures: Embark on Your Cloud Journey with Azure Fundamentals</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-09-01T16:07:38Z</published><updated>2024-09-01T16:07:38Z</updated><id>0d529dd7-b341-4251-bb69-81d1db94c72f</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_tech.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/0d529dd7-b341-4251-bb69-81d1db94c72f.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world today, there are several noteworthy developments. Firstly, Microsoft has introduced a new Azure Fundamentals Student Learn Plan, which aims to assist individuals in embarking on their Azure journey. This program provides comprehensive training and resources for students to gain a solid understanding of Azure and its functionalities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additionally, there have been significant advancements in the field of artificial intelligence (AI). Jürgen Schmidhuber, a renowned expert in AI, has released a video discussing neural and non-neural AI, reasoning, transformers, and LSTMs. This insightful video sheds light on the latest developments and trends in AI technology.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Furthermore, Microsoft has introduced the Azure Data Fundamentals Student Learn Plan, which focuses on enhancing data skills. This program equips students with the necessary knowledge and tools to work with data effectively, enabling them to analyze and interpret data sets efficiently.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a recent study, it was revealed that there are data exposure risks associated with language model (LLM) applications like OpenAI's GPTs. The study delves into the potential vulnerabilities and privacy concerns that arise from using these applications, highlighting the need for robust data protection measures.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moreover, Microsoft offers the Azure AI Fundamentals Student Learn Plan, which allows individuals to delve deeper into the world of artificial intelligence. This program provides comprehensive training on AI concepts, algorithms, and applications, empowering students to leverage AI technologies effectively.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools and products, GitHub and GitHub Copilot have introduced a Learn Plan to enhance coding workflows. This plan offers valuable resources and guidance to optimize coding practices, enabling developers to streamline their workflow and improve productivity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, Microsoft has developed the Security, Compliance, and Identity Fundamentals Learn Plan, which aims to strengthen knowledge in these crucial areas. This program equips individuals with the necessary skills to ensure secure and compliant practices in the digital landscape.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, these developments highlight the continuous advancements in technology and the importance of acquiring relevant skills and knowledge in various domains. With the introduction of new learn plans and the emergence of cutting-edge tools and products, individuals can stay updated and enhance their expertise in the ever-evolving world.
    </summary></entry></feed>