<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-09-18T16:08:46Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Cloud Chronicles: Unpacking AWS Innovations and Security Secrets</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-09-18T16:08:46Z</published><updated>2024-09-18T16:08:46Z</updated><id>270884c8-ff15-42cb-8543-cfff4519f592</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/270884c8-ff15-42cb-8543-cfff4519f592.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent developments within the tech world, Amazon Web Services (AWS) has made significant strides in enhancing its cloud computing offerings. Notably, Amazon Elastic Container Service (ECS) has introduced support for AWS Fargate, enabling users to leverage AWS Graviton-based Spot instances for cost-effective computing. Additionally, AWS Amplify has expanded its capabilities to support long-running tasks through asynchronous server-side function calls, improving the efficiency of application development. In a move to enhance collaboration, AWS Chatbot now allows users to interact with Amazon Bedrock agents directly from Microsoft Teams and Slack, streamlining workflows. Furthermore, Amazon S3 Express One Zone has integrated support for AWS Key Management Service (KMS) with customer-managed keys, bolstering data security. The AWS Transfer Family has also increased its throughput and file size limits for SFTP connectors, facilitating smoother file transfers. On a security note, a concerning report emerged regarding the UNC2970 backdoor deployment, which utilizes a Trojanized PDF reader. Lastly, Amazon RDS Custom for SQL Server has expanded its availability to three additional AWS regions, allowing more users to benefit from tailored database solutions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;### New Tools, Products, or Projects:&lt;br&gt;1. **AWS Fargate with Graviton Spot Instances**: Cost-effective computing options for containerized applications.&lt;br&gt;2. **AWS Amplify**: Now supports asynchronous server-side function calls for long-running tasks.&lt;br&gt;3. **AWS Chatbot**: Integration with Amazon Bedrock agents for Microsoft Teams and Slack.&lt;br&gt;4. **Amazon S3 Express One Zone**: Enhanced security with AWS-KMS and customer-managed keys.&lt;br&gt;5. **AWS Transfer Family**: Increased throughput and file size support for SFTP connectors.&lt;br&gt;6. **Amazon RDS Custom for SQL Server**: Expanded availability in three new AWS regions.
    </summary></entry></feed>