<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-03-26T16:12:17Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>"The Cybersecurity Chronicles: Unveiling CISA, Zero Trust, and Google Workspace at Next '24"</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-03-26T16:12:17Z</published><updated>2024-03-26T16:12:17Z</updated><id>cbd863ed-789d-4012-9466-9666987eeb33</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/cbd863ed-789d-4012-9466-9666987eeb33.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of cybersecurity, there have been significant developments aimed at strengthening federal cybersecurity. At the Next '24 conference, exclusive sessions were held to discuss the implementation of the Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) and the Zero Trust framework. These initiatives are designed to enhance the protection of sensitive data and prevent cyber threats. Additionally, Google Workspace, a comprehensive productivity and collaboration tool, was introduced to provide a secure and efficient platform for organizations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In other news, Microsoft has announced the retirement of the Azure Maps Creator Feature State Service Versions by 31st March 2025. This decision will impact users who rely on this feature for mapping and location-based services. It is important for affected users to take necessary action and find alternative solutions before the specified date.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Furthermore, a reminder has been issued to upgrade App Service apps to Node 20 LTS by 30th April 2025. This upgrade is crucial to ensure compatibility and security for applications running on the App Service platform. Users are advised to make the necessary changes within the given timeframe to avoid any disruptions or vulnerabilities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the Azure platform, a new feature called Agentless multi-disk crash consistent backup for virtual machines (VM) has entered the public preview phase. This feature, provided by Azure Backup, allows users to perform backups of VMs without the need for an agent. It ensures crash-consistent backups across multiple disks, providing a reliable and efficient backup solution for VMs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, it has been announced that Basic and Standard A-series VMs on HDInsight will be retired on 31st August 2024. Users currently utilizing these VMs for their HDInsight workloads will need to migrate to alternative VM types before the retirement date. This change aims to optimize the VM offerings and provide users with improved performance and capabilities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Tools, Products, or Projects:&lt;br&gt;- Google Workspace: A comprehensive productivity and collaboration tool designed to provide a secure and efficient platform for organizations.&lt;br&gt;- Agentless multi-disk crash consistent backup by Azure Backup for VM: A new feature in Azure Backup that allows users to perform backups of VMs without the need for an agent, ensuring crash-consistent backups across multiple disks.&lt;br&gt;- Retirement of Azure Maps Creator Feature State Service Versions: Microsoft has announced the retirement of this feature by 31st March 2025, impacting users who rely on it for mapping and location-based services.&lt;br&gt;- Upgrade to Node 20 LTS for App Service apps: Users are required to upgrade their App Service apps to Node 20 LTS by 30th April 2025 to ensure compatibility and security.&lt;br&gt;- Retirement of Basic and Standard A-series VMs on HDInsight: These VMs will be retired on 31st August 2024, prompting users to migrate to alternative VM types for their HDInsight workloads.
    </summary></entry></feed>