<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Tech</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml</id><updated>2024-08-16T16:07:07Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Unlocking the Power of API Management: Building Developer Portals with the WordPress Plugin</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-08-16T16:07:07Z</published><updated>2024-08-16T16:07:07Z</updated><id>fb83d7da-ada2-416f-80ce-fa9f15556dfb</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_tech.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/fb83d7da-ada2-416f-80ce-fa9f15556dfb.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world, there have been several significant developments. Firstly, a new API Management WordPress plugin has been announced, which is now available for public preview. This plugin allows organizations to build customized developer portals, providing them with greater control and flexibility in managing their APIs. With this tool, developers can easily create, publish, and manage APIs, enhancing the overall user experience and streamlining the development process.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additionally, AWS Security Hub has introduced a new control called "IAM Access Analyzer external access analyzer should be enabled" in organizations' environments. This control, labeled as [IAM.28], focuses on ensuring the security of AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) by enabling the external access analyzer. By enabling this feature, organizations can proactively identify and mitigate potential security risks related to external access to their IAM resources. This enhancement further strengthens the security measures in place, safeguarding sensitive data and protecting against unauthorized access.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In conclusion, the introduction of the API Management WordPress plugin offers organizations the ability to create tailored developer portals, while the new control in AWS Security Hub enhances IAM security by enabling the external access analyzer. These advancements contribute to a more efficient and secure technological landscape, empowering organizations to better manage their APIs and protect their valuable resources.
    </summary></entry></feed>