<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Tech</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml</id><updated>2024-08-04T16:06:35Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>The Workflow Wizard: Unleashing the Power of AWS Lambda, SQS, Node.js, and MongoDB for Scalable Automation like HubSpot</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-08-04T16:06:35Z</published><updated>2024-08-04T16:06:35Z</updated><id>525a49bd-47e3-4808-834a-ea5f4889999f</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_tech.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/525a49bd-47e3-4808-834a-ea5f4889999f.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of technology, there have been some exciting developments recently. One notable news is the article on how to build scalable automated workflows similar to HubSpot using AWS Lambda, SQS, Node.js, and MongoDB. This guide provides insights into leveraging these tools to create efficient and automated workflows.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the realm of web development, Angular 18 has caught the attention of developers. Coupled with Cypress, Material, Transloco, Jest, EsLint, Docker, and Prettier, Angular 18 offers a powerful and comprehensive framework for building web applications. This combination of tools and technologies promises enhanced performance and ease of development.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For gaming enthusiasts, the JavaScript MMORPG - Maiu Online - has been making waves. Episode 34 of this game, titled "Experience and levels," delves into the intricacies of character progression and leveling up within the virtual world. Powered by the popular Babylon.js framework, Maiu Online offers an immersive gaming experience for players.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the realm of web design, a tutorial on creating an animated avatar stack widget using Tailwind CSS has gained attention. This tutorial provides step-by-step instructions on how to implement visually appealing and interactive avatar stacks using the popular CSS framework, Tailwind. This widget can add a touch of creativity and interactivity to websites.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, there has been a breakthrough in the field of language AI. A new project allows for the deployment of powerful language AI models in tiny packages, without compromising performance. This innovation enables the compression of large AI models, making them more accessible and efficient for various applications. This development has the potential to revolutionize the field of natural language processing and AI-driven applications.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, these recent advancements in technology showcase the continuous evolution and innovation happening in various domains. From building scalable workflows to creating immersive gaming experiences and deploying efficient AI models, the world of technology is constantly pushing boundaries and offering new possibilities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Tools, Products, or Projects:&lt;br&gt;- AWS Lambda, SQS, Node.js, and MongoDB for building scalable automated workflows&lt;br&gt;- Angular 18 with Cypress, Material, Transloco, Jest, EsLint, Docker, and Prettier for web development&lt;br&gt;- Babylon.js framework for the JavaScript MMORPG - Maiu Online&lt;br&gt;- Tailwind CSS for creating animated avatar stack widgets&lt;br&gt;- Breakthrough project enabling the deployment of powerful language AI models in compressed packages.
    </summary></entry></feed>