<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.fun/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.fun/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-10-22T16:10:21Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Cloud Chronicles: Navigating AWS Innovations and Insights</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.fun/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-10-22T16:10:21Z</published><updated>2024-10-22T16:10:21Z</updated><id>5c91ab12-ef26-4661-9881-4b07362b77d6</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.fun/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/5c91ab12-ef26-4661-9881-4b07362b77d6.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent developments within the tech world, Amazon Web Services (AWS) has made significant strides in enhancing its offerings and expanding its global reach. The AWS Marketplace has now broadened its support to include four new currencies and allows for disbursement to non-US bank accounts, making it easier for international customers to engage with AWS services. Additionally, the Amazon RDS Multi-AZ deployment has been upgraded to support AWS IAM database authentication, enhancing security and access management. In the realm of data visualization, QuickSight has introduced support for subfolders in restricted folders, facilitating governed data sharing. AWS has also emphasized the importance of gamification in cloud learning through the introduction of AWS Jam(s), which are designed to make the cloud journey more engaging. Furthermore, the AWS Lambda console has been enhanced with built-in Amazon CloudWatch Metrics Insights for key function insights and real-time log analytics via Amazon CloudWatch Logs Live Tail. On the AI front, Amazon Bedrock Model Evaluation now allows for the evaluation of custom model imports, while AWS Data Exchange has introduced APIs for data grants, enabling programmatic data sharing. Lastly, Amazon DataZone has launched support for AWS IAM Identity Center account instances, further streamlining user management. In hardware advancements, Intel's AMX CPU accelerator for AI has been tested, revealing promising insights into its capabilities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;### New Tools, Products, and Projects:&lt;br&gt;1. **AWS Marketplace**: Now supports four new currencies and non-US bank accounts for disbursement.&lt;br&gt;2. **Amazon RDS Multi-AZ Deployment**: Enhanced to support AWS IAM database authentication.&lt;br&gt;3. **QuickSight**: Introduced subfolders in restricted folders for improved governed data sharing.&lt;br&gt;4. **AWS Jam(s)**: New gamification initiatives to enhance cloud learning experiences.&lt;br&gt;5. **AWS Lambda Console**: Features built-in Amazon CloudWatch Metrics Insights and real-time log analytics via CloudWatch Logs Live Tail.&lt;br&gt;6. **Amazon Bedrock Model Evaluation**: Now supports the evaluation of custom model imports.&lt;br&gt;7. **AWS Data Exchange**: New APIs for data grants to enable programmatic data sharing.&lt;br&gt;8. **Amazon DataZone**: Launched support for AWS IAM Identity Center account instances.&lt;br&gt;9. **Intel AMX CPU Accelerator**: Tested for AI, providing insights into its performance and capabilities.
    </summary></entry></feed>