<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-06-06T16:07:03Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>The Cloud Chronicles: Unleashing Innovation and Empowered Development in the AI Era</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-06-06T16:07:03Z</published><updated>2024-06-06T16:07:03Z</updated><id>89d8cde2-b709-4c24-9cd5-b7e0e9846473</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/89d8cde2-b709-4c24-9cd5-b7e0e9846473.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of technology, several updates and releases have taken place. Firstly, Azure Cosmos DB for MongoDB now supports Mongo Ver 7.0, providing users with enhanced capabilities and features. Additionally, Azure Database for PostgreSQL has introduced online migration in its migration service, which is currently in the public preview stage. This allows for a seamless and efficient transfer of data. Furthermore, Azure Monitor log search alert rules can now be utilized in Resource Health, providing users with improved monitoring and alerting capabilities. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In another development, Azure Cosmos DB has introduced continuous backup for accounts using Azure Synapse Link, which is currently in the public preview stage. This feature ensures that data is consistently backed up, providing users with peace of mind and data protection. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moving on to AWS, several updates have been made. Amazon EC2 U7i instances have been introduced, offering improved performance and capabilities. Bedrock Converse API has also been released, providing developers with enhanced tools for building conversational interfaces. Additionally, AWS celebrated World IPv6 Day, highlighting the importance of IPv6 in the digital landscape.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the realm of Azure Database for PostgreSQL Flexible Server, long-term backup retention is now available, allowing users to retain backups for extended periods. This ensures data availability and recovery options. Furthermore, Azure Cosmos DB with Data Explorer now supports multi-select delete, providing users with a more efficient and streamlined data management experience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the world of business innovation, Google Cloud and SAP are collaborating to forge a path towards enduring innovation. Leveraging AI technology, they aim to empower businesses and drive growth. Additionally, Google Cloud offers GitLab for streamlined delivery and enhanced security, enabling developers to work more efficiently and securely.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, starting from July 2024, log search alert rules using linked storage in Azure will require the use of a managed identity. This change ensures improved security and access control for log search alert rules.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Tools, Products, or Projects:&lt;br&gt;- Azure Cosmos DB for MongoDB now supports Mongo Ver 7.0, providing enhanced capabilities.&lt;br&gt;- Azure Database for PostgreSQL introduces online migration in its migration service.&lt;br&gt;- Azure Monitor log search alert rules can now be utilized in Resource Health.&lt;br&gt;- Azure Cosmos DB introduces continuous backup for accounts using Azure Synapse Link.&lt;br&gt;- Amazon EC2 U7i instances are now available, offering improved performance.&lt;br&gt;- Bedrock Converse API is released, providing enhanced tools for building conversational interfaces.&lt;br&gt;- Google Cloud and SAP collaborate to drive enduring business innovation.&lt;br&gt;- GitLab on Google Cloud enables streamlined delivery and enhanced security.&lt;br&gt;- Log search alert rules using linked storage in Azure will require a managed identity starting July 2024.
    </summary></entry></feed>