<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Tech</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml</id><updated>2024-04-07T16:05:53Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>"The EV Delivery Dilemma: Xiaomi's Extended Wait Time Unveiled"</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-04-07T16:05:53Z</published><updated>2024-04-07T16:05:53Z</updated><id>cf02c5a7-b0e2-40c4-8e4d-6e896cbd61c5</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_tech.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/cf02c5a7-b0e2-40c4-8e4d-6e896cbd61c5.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world, there has been an extension in the delivery wait time for Xiaomi's electric vehicles (EV) to more than five months. This delay in delivery could be attributed to various factors such as high demand, supply chain disruptions, or production challenges. Xiaomi, known for its smartphones and other consumer electronics, has been expanding its presence in the EV market with the launch of models like the Xiaomi Mi Electric Scooter and the Xiaomi Mi Electric Bike. However, customers who have ordered their EVs from Xiaomi will now have to wait longer than anticipated to receive their vehicles.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the technology realm, React 19 has introduced new features for handling forms. The useOptimistic and useFormStatus hooks, in combination with React Hook Form and Zod, provide a practical example of how to efficiently manage form submissions and their status updates. These additions to React 19 aim to enhance the user experience by streamlining the form handling process and improving performance.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moreover, at the OKX Web3 Night event, Avery Ching, the co-founder and CTO of Aptos, made an appearance to share the latest developments of the Move language on the Aptos platform. Aptos is a company that focuses on Web3 and blockchain technology. The Move language, developed by Facebook's Diem Association, is designed for creating smart contracts and executing transactions on the Diem blockchain. Ching's presence at the event highlights the significance of Move language integration in Aptos and showcases the company's commitment to leveraging blockchain technology for their platform's development.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, there is no specific information provided in the given news.
    </summary></entry></feed>