<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-05-02T16:06:18Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>"Cloud Chronicles: Unveiling the Latest in AWS and Azure Training &amp; Certification"&lt;br&gt;"Tech Talk: Exploring the Cutting-Edge Updates in AWS and Azure Certifications"&lt;br&gt;"The Cloud Academy: Discovering the Newest AWS and Azure Training Innovations"&lt;br&gt;"Certify and Thrive: Unveiling the Latest AWS and Azure Certification Updates"&lt;br&gt;"Cloud Mastery: Navigating the Exciting New Courses and Certifications from AWS and Azure"&lt;br&gt;"The Future of Cloud Learning: Exploring the April 2024 Updates in AWS and Azure Training"&lt;br&gt;"Cloud Revolution: Unveiling the Game-Changing Updates in AWS and Azure Certifications"&lt;br&gt;"Tech Training Unleashed: Exploring the Latest AWS and Azure Certification Updates"&lt;br&gt;"Cloud Insights: Delving into the April 2024 Updates in AWS and Azure Training"&lt;br&gt;"Certification Revolution: Unveiling the Cutting-Edge Updates in AWS and Azure Training"</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-05-02T16:06:18Z</published><updated>2024-05-02T16:06:18Z</updated><id>46e0e6f9-5bca-4e09-8958-17f4916f22e8</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/46e0e6f9-5bca-4e09-8958-17f4916f22e8.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In April 2024, AWS Training and Certification announced new courses and certification updates. These updates aim to provide individuals with the latest skills and knowledge in the ever-evolving field of cloud computing. With these new offerings, professionals can enhance their expertise and stay up-to-date with the latest advancements in AWS technologies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meanwhile, Azure Spring Apps introduced a feature update in the first quarter of 2024. This update allows users to save up to 47% with Azure savings plan. By leveraging this feature, organizations can optimize their costs while utilizing the powerful capabilities of Azure Spring Apps. This update reflects Microsoft's commitment to providing cost-effective solutions to its customers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additionally, Azure HDInsight on AKS (Azure Kubernetes Service) is now available for preview in seven new regions. This public preview allows users to leverage the power of HDInsight, a cloud-based big data analytics service, on AKS. With this integration, organizations can efficiently process and analyze large volumes of data using the scalable and flexible infrastructure provided by AKS. The availability of this preview in new regions further expands the reach and accessibility of this powerful tool.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, there are several noteworthy developments. AWS Training and Certification has introduced new courses and certification updates, ensuring professionals have access to the latest skills and knowledge in cloud computing. Azure Spring Apps has rolled out a feature update that enables users to save significantly on costs with Azure savings plan. Additionally, Azure HDInsight on AKS is now available for preview in seven new regions, allowing organizations to leverage the power of big data analytics on AKS infrastructure. These advancements highlight the continuous efforts of both AWS and Azure to provide cutting-edge solutions and empower businesses in the ever-changing world of technology.
    </summary></entry></feed>