<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-10-02T16:09:09Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Cloud Control Chronicles: Unleashing Oracle Management Agent 13.5 on Amazon RDS</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-10-02T16:09:09Z</published><updated>2024-10-02T16:09:09Z</updated><id>2a0e447d-081d-4564-b3e5-a83b2194e951</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/2a0e447d-081d-4564-b3e5-a83b2194e951.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent developments in the tech world, Amazon has announced that its Relational Database Service (RDS) for Oracle now supports the Oracle Management Agent version 13.5.0.0.v2, which is designed for use with Oracle Enterprise Manager Cloud Control 13cR5. This enhancement allows users to better manage their Oracle databases hosted on Amazon RDS, providing improved monitoring, management, and automation capabilities. The integration of this new version of the Oracle Management Agent is expected to streamline database operations, enhance performance, and facilitate more efficient resource management for businesses utilizing cloud-based database solutions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;### New Tools, Products, or Projects&lt;br&gt;- **Amazon RDS for Oracle**: Now enhanced with support for Oracle Management Agent version 13.5.0.0.v2.&lt;br&gt;- **Oracle Enterprise Manager Cloud Control 13cR5**: The latest version of Oracle's management tool, providing advanced capabilities for monitoring and managing Oracle databases.&lt;br&gt;- **Improved Monitoring and Management Features**: The integration aims to offer users better insights and control over their database environments, enabling more efficient operations and resource utilization.
    </summary></entry></feed>