<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://novasparkxx.github.io/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://novasparkxx.github.io/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-02-03T00:26:10Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>1. "The AWS Glue Chat Experience: Exploring Amazon Q Data Integration"&lt;br&gt;2. "Unlocking Cloud Storage on GKE: A Guide to the Kubernetes API - Part I"&lt;br&gt;3. "Private Preview: Azure Site Recovery for Azure Trusted Launch VMs (Windows OS)"&lt;br&gt;4. "Leap Ahead in Your Cloud Career: 29 No-Cost Tips for February"&lt;br&gt;5. "Retiring Log Alert Rules: Cross-Workspace Queries with Resource Names"&lt;br&gt;6. "Azure Virtual Network Manager: Enhancing Security in 30 Regions"&lt;br&gt;7. "Unlocking Benefits: Moving to S/4 HANA on Google Cloud for Deutsche Börse Group"</title><link href="https://novasparkxx.github.io/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-02-03T00:26:10Z</published><updated>2024-02-03T00:26:10Z</updated><id>222e4214-27c9-4c25-917f-e0bb5a81be63</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://imgproxy.nanxiongnandi.com/P_O89MPBYlhmFIfXN1-KWHdQIOZ40lkQcMHMZlMdWf8/w:1280/aHR0cHM6Ly9pbWcu/bmFueGlvbmduYW5k/aS5jb20vMjAyNDAx/L0J1a2hhbnNhblNl/b3VsLmpwZw.jpg" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/222e4214-27c9-4c25-917f-e0bb5a81be63.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of technology, there have been several notable developments. AWS Glue, a data integration service, has introduced a new chat experience called Amazon Q. This feature allows users to communicate using natural language, enhancing the overall user experience. Additionally, AWS Glue has released a preview version of their data integration tool, which further improves data management capabilities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another significant update comes from Google Kubernetes Engine (GKE), where users can now consume Cloud Storage objects using the Kubernetes API. This development, known as Part I, aims to streamline the process of accessing and utilizing Cloud Storage resources within the GKE environment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moving on to Microsoft Azure, a private preview has been announced for Azure Site Recovery support for Azure Trusted Launch VMs with Windows OS. This feature enhances the security and reliability of virtual machines, providing users with a trusted environment for their workloads.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For those looking to advance their cloud careers, an article highlights 29 no-cost ways to leap ahead in February. This resource offers valuable insights and tips for professionals seeking to enhance their skills and stay up-to-date with the latest trends in cloud computing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of retirement, Microsoft Azure has announced that support for log alert rules using cross-workspace queries with resource names or qualified name identifiers will be discontinued on May 31, 2024. Users are advised to make necessary adjustments to their log alert rules to ensure uninterrupted monitoring and management of their resources.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Furthermore, Azure Virtual Network Manager security admin rule has become generally available in 30 regions. This feature enables users to manage and enforce security policies within their virtual networks, enhancing overall network security and control.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, Deutsche Börse Group has experienced significant benefits by migrating to S/4 HANA on Google Cloud. This move has allowed the financial institution to leverage the advanced capabilities of Google Cloud's infrastructure, resulting in improved performance and efficiency.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, AWS Glue's introduction of Amazon Q and the preview version of their data integration tool showcases their commitment to enhancing data management and user experience. Additionally, GKE's ability to consume Cloud Storage objects using the Kubernetes API provides users with more flexibility and ease of access to their cloud resources. Microsoft Azure's private preview of Azure Site Recovery support for Azure Trusted Launch VMs demonstrates their dedication to providing secure and reliable virtual machine environments. Lastly, the retirement of log alert rules and the availability of Azure Virtual Network Manager security admin rule highlight Microsoft Azure's ongoing efforts to improve resource management and network security.
    </summary></entry></feed>