<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Business and Market</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.fun/podcast/trend_business_and_market.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.fun/podcast/trend_business_and_market.xml</id><updated>2024-11-20T16:08:21Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vote, Work, Thrive: Navigating Mumbai's Freebies, Resignations, and Economic Shifts</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.fun/podcast/trend_business_and_market.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-11-20T16:08:21Z</published><updated>2024-11-20T16:08:21Z</updated><id>5968d93f-586f-43cf-8175-bdd967004710</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.fun/cover/trend_business_and_market.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/5968d93f-586f-43cf-8175-bdd967004710.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent global news, Swiggy Instamart has launched an initiative in Mumbai, urging residents to participate in the upcoming elections by offering freebies, encapsulated in the slogan "Vote Or Suffer 'Tinday'." This move highlights the increasing importance of civic engagement in the face of political apathy. Meanwhile, a phenomenon dubbed "Great Resignation 2.0" is emerging as employees across various sectors report feeling overworked and underpaid, prompting many to seek better job opportunities. In the business realm, inflation has surged to 2.3%, while Dunelm has acquired Home Focus, and the Royal Mail's takeover is expected to receive approval. On the energy front, India's oil demand is projected to rise in November 2024 following a recovery in October, while Russian gas supplies to the EU via Ukraine remain stable despite ongoing disputes with OMV. In corporate news, ADM has faced a decline in Q3 earnings, compounded by delays in reporting due to additional accounting errors. Lastly, Goldman Sachs has warned investors about the potential risks posed by Trump's tariffs, predicting a slowdown in growth for 2025.
    </summary></entry></feed>