<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.fun/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.fun/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-10-19T16:09:48Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Cloud Chronicles: Unpacking AWS Innovations and Insights</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.fun/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-10-19T16:09:48Z</published><updated>2024-10-19T16:09:48Z</updated><id>91bf4c8b-4173-4cd2-a6b1-71fbece3510b</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.fun/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/91bf4c8b-4173-4cd2-a6b1-71fbece3510b.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent developments within the tech world, Amazon Web Services (AWS) has rolled out several significant updates aimed at enhancing user experience and functionality across its platforms. The AWS Lambda console has introduced real-time log analytics through Amazon CloudWatch Logs Live Tail, allowing developers to monitor their applications more effectively. Additionally, the console now features a built-in Amazon CloudWatch Metrics Insights dashboard that surfaces key function insights, streamlining the monitoring process. In terms of database services, Amazon Aurora PostgreSQL and Amazon DynamoDB have officially launched zero ETL integration with Amazon Redshift, simplifying data workflows. Furthermore, Amazon RDS Multi-AZ deployment has expanded its capabilities to support AWS IAM database authentication with two readable standbys, enhancing security and accessibility. AWS DataZone has also launched support for AWS IAM Identity Center account instances, improving identity management. In analytics, QuickSight now allows for subfolders in restricted folders, facilitating governed data sharing. AWS Data Exchange has introduced APIs for data grants, enabling programmatic data sharing, while the AWS Marketplace has expanded its offerings to include four new currencies and support for non-US bank accounts for disbursement. Lastly, Amazon Bedrock Model Evaluation has added support for evaluating custom model import models, providing users with greater flexibility in model assessment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;### New Tools, Products, or Projects:&lt;br&gt;1. **AWS Lambda Console Enhancements**: Real-time log analytics via Amazon CloudWatch Logs Live Tail and built-in Metrics Insights dashboard.&lt;br&gt;2. **Zero ETL Integration**: Official launch of zero ETL integration between Amazon Aurora PostgreSQL, Amazon DynamoDB, and Amazon Redshift.&lt;br&gt;3. **Amazon RDS Multi-AZ Deployment**: Now supports AWS IAM database authentication with two readable standbys.&lt;br&gt;4. **AWS DataZone**: Launch of support for AWS IAM Identity Center account instances.&lt;br&gt;5. **QuickSight Updates**: Introduction of subfolders in restricted folders for governed data sharing.&lt;br&gt;6. **AWS Data Exchange APIs**: New APIs for data grants to enable programmatic data sharing.&lt;br&gt;7. **AWS Marketplace Expansion**: Support for four new currencies and non-US bank accounts for disbursement.&lt;br&gt;8. **Amazon Bedrock Model Evaluation**: New support for evaluating custom model import models.
    </summary></entry></feed>