<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Science and Research</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_science_and_research.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_science_and_research.xml</id><updated>2024-06-28T16:08:03Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Roots &amp; Remedies: Unearthing the Power of Plants</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_science_and_research.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-06-28T16:08:03Z</published><updated>2024-06-28T16:08:03Z</updated><id>d5d64589-bfc5-4d8b-8cc9-63d96a05cfb0</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_science_and_research.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/d5d64589-bfc5-4d8b-8cc9-63d96a05cfb0.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of plants, a study published in Plants, Vol. 13, Pages 1788 explored the effect of harvest time on the growth and bioactive compounds in Salvia miltiorrhiza. The research aimed to understand how the timing of harvest can impact the quality and medicinal properties of this plant.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the healthcare sector, a cross-sectional study published in Healthcare, Vol. 12, Pages 1294 examined the diagnostic accuracy of the Recognizing Acute Delirium as Part of Your Routine (RADAR) Scale for delirium assessment in hospitalized older adults. The study aimed to improve the identification and management of delirium in this vulnerable population.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Antioxidants, Vol. 13, Pages 784 featured a study that explored the bioactive properties and therapeutic benefits of pear pomace. The research aimed to uncover the potential health-promoting compounds present in this byproduct of pear processing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vaccines, Vol. 12, Pages 719 presented an overview of the progress and challenges in the development and deployment of hepatitis E vaccines. The study highlighted the importance of continued efforts in combating this viral infection.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the field of diagnostics, Diagnostics, Vol. 14, Pages 1374 introduced a novel approach to diagnosing progression in glioblastoma, a type of brain tumor. The study utilized artificial intelligence-derived volumetric change over time on magnetic resonance imaging to examine progression-free survival in glioblastoma patients.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Office of Science and Technology Policy (OSTP) made an announcement regarding the publication of an "Updated Report to the U.S. Congress on Financing Mechanisms for Open Access Publishing of Federally Funded Research." This report aimed to address the financial aspects of open access publishing for federally funded research.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nursing Reports, Vol. 14, Pages 1604-1620 featured a qualitative study that explored the experiences of nursing students during their clinical education. The research focused on the challenges faced by these students and the support they received to foster resilience in their nursing practice.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the realm of genomics, a study delved into the genomic and functional divergence of the NAT gene family, which plays a role in microbial secondary metabolism. The research aimed to gain insights into the evolutionary and functional aspects of this gene family.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beverages, Vol. 10, Pages 52 presented a study on the preservation of malolactic starters of Lactiplantibacillus plantarum strains obtained through solid-state fermentation on apple pomace. The research aimed to develop effective preservation methods for these strains, which are important for the production of certain beverages.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, Applied Sciences, Vol. 14, Pages 5638 featured a study that investigated the impact of binder system composition on the rheological and magnetic properties of Nd-Fe-B feedstocks for metal injection molding. The research aimed to optimize the manufacturing process of these materials, which are widely used in various industries.
    </summary></entry></feed>