<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-02-06T20:04:15Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>"The Cloud Chronicles: Unleashing the Power of Mounting Azure Storage Locally in App Service Linux"</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-02-06T20:04:15Z</published><updated>2024-02-06T20:04:15Z</updated><id>65b126ac-2543-4cca-8001-ca75313fb90b</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/65b126ac-2543-4cca-8001-ca75313fb90b.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent news, there have been several developments in the tech world. Firstly, it has been announced that App Service Linux now supports NFS, allowing users to mount Azure Storage as a local share. This new feature provides greater flexibility and convenience for developers working with App Service Linux. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additionally, there is news regarding Azure Data Explorer Cluster. It has reached General Availability for migrating Virtual Network injected clusters to Private Endpoints. This enhancement ensures a more secure and controlled environment for data exploration and analysis.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Furthermore, the FHIR service has made an important update. It now supports up to 100 TB of storage, which is a significant increase from previous limitations. This expanded storage capacity enables healthcare organizations to store and manage larger volumes of healthcare data efficiently.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In other tech news, AWS has made several noteworthy announcements. Amazon Q and Amazon PartyRock Hackathon are now available in AWS Glue, offering users more powerful and versatile tools for data processing and analysis. Additionally, CDK Migrate has been introduced, providing a seamless way to migrate infrastructure-as-code projects to AWS Cloud Development Kit (CDK).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;These recent developments showcase the continuous advancements in cloud computing and data management. With the introduction of new tools, products, and projects, developers and organizations can enhance their capabilities and improve efficiency in various domains.
    </summary></entry></feed>