<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Business and Market</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_business_and_market.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_business_and_market.xml</id><updated>2024-07-15T16:07:22Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>CEO Pay Scale Shake-Up: Marico's Saugata Gupta Takes a Hit</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_business_and_market.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-07-15T16:07:22Z</published><updated>2024-07-15T16:07:22Z</updated><id>6c589ab3-363c-4b6e-b932-6b5fdb568d49</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_business_and_market.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/6c589ab3-363c-4b6e-b932-6b5fdb568d49.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world news, Saugata Gupta, the CEO of Marico, has lost his top spot in the FMCG CEO pay scale. Meanwhile, the Nifty has hit a new record with SBI, NTPC, and ITC leading the gains in the midday market update. Vizhinjam is attracting shipping lines as cargo handling at the Colombo Port has been delayed. A survey reveals that two out of three people prefer companies not to use AI for customer service. BluSmart has raised Rs 200 crore from MS Dhoni Family Office and ReNew's Sumant Sinha. The Delhi High Court has clarified the legality of leaving a job before the lock-in period ends. Ashok Leyland has secured its largest order for fully-built buses from MSRTC. The IAF has honored braveheart soldiers at Air Force Station Sarsawa on the occasion of 25 years of Kargil. Hindalco Industries is set to sell land to Birla Estates' unit for Rs 595 crore. According to Citi, the high RBI dividend and improved tax collection will allow fiscal headroom in the Budget 2024.
    </summary></entry></feed>