<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Tech</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml</id><updated>2024-08-12T16:07:33Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Mastering Local Editing: Unleashing the Power of Angular 13 and Ionic 5</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-08-12T16:07:33Z</published><updated>2024-08-12T16:07:33Z</updated><id>37376f84-770f-43fd-85f7-8ff6cdb032ed</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_tech.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/37376f84-770f-43fd-85f7-8ff6cdb032ed.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of technology, there have been some interesting developments. Firstly, there is a guide available on how to edit an Angular Ionic app locally. This guide specifically focuses on projects using Angular version 13 and Ionic version 5. It provides step-by-step instructions on how to make edits and modifications to these types of apps, allowing developers to customize and enhance their projects.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additionally, a new trick has been discovered for taking screenshots of webpages using the dev console. This handy tool allows users to capture the contents of a webpage, including any dynamic elements or changes made through JavaScript. By utilizing this trick, individuals can easily document and share specific web content.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the realm of game development, a practical guide has been released for using Pygame. This guide aims to provide a comprehensive understanding of the Surface Object, a fundamental component in Pygame game development. It covers various aspects of working with the Surface Object, including its properties, methods, and practical examples.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Furthermore, a new approach to designing software architectures in highly unpredictable projects has been introduced. This approach involves sketching out the extremes, allowing developers to consider and plan for various scenarios and potential challenges. By taking into account the unpredictable nature of these projects, developers can create more robust and adaptable software architectures.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, there is an exciting announcement for developers. Gamescom 2024 will be hosting an event where developers can gather and uncover various QA testing tools, including PerfDog. This event provides an opportunity for developers to explore and learn about the latest tools and techniques in quality assurance testing, enhancing their ability to deliver high-quality games and software.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, there is a discussion surrounding the different package managers for Node.js. The article explores the pros and cons of npm, yarn, and pnpm, which are popular package managers used in Node.js development. It aims to help developers make informed decisions when choosing the most suitable package manager for their projects.
    </summary></entry></feed>