<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Tech</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml</id><updated>2024-04-30T16:06:18Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>"Banking on Innovation: State Bank of India's Digital Transformation Journey"&lt;br&gt;"Unleashing the Power of GraphQL: A Step-by-Step Guide for Success"&lt;br&gt;"The Future of Customer Communication: State Bank of India's Tech Revolution"&lt;br&gt;"EcoXpert Partner Program: Revolutionizing Solutions with Damien Dhellemmes"&lt;br&gt;"Thriving in a Disengaged Environment: Career Advancement Strategies"</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-04-30T16:06:18Z</published><updated>2024-04-30T16:06:18Z</updated><id>067f2d3c-536e-4995-8c2f-a3a96fc230ce</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_tech.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/067f2d3c-536e-4995-8c2f-a3a96fc230ce.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent news, the State Bank of India has taken a significant step towards digitization by deploying HCLSoftware technology to enhance customer communication. This move aims to streamline and modernize the bank's communication channels, providing customers with a more efficient and convenient banking experience. By leveraging HCLSoftware's advanced solutions, the State Bank of India is embracing digital transformation and staying ahead in the ever-evolving banking industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In another development, a practical guide titled "From Basics to Supergraph: A practical guide for your GraphQL adoption journey" has been released. This guide offers valuable insights and step-by-step instructions for organizations looking to adopt GraphQL, a query language for APIs. With the increasing popularity of GraphQL, this guide serves as a comprehensive resource to help businesses navigate their adoption journey and harness the full potential of this technology.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additionally, an interview with Damien Dhellemmes sheds light on the EcoXpert Partner Program. This program is designed to continuously evolve and enhance solution excellence in the field of eco-friendly technologies. Dhellemmes discusses the importance of this program and how it enables partners to stay at the forefront of innovative solutions, contributing to a sustainable future.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, for individuals facing disengaged bosses, there are strategies to advance in their careers. Despite the challenges posed by a disengaged boss, it is crucial to focus on personal growth and development. This can be achieved by seeking out additional responsibilities, taking initiative, and seeking mentorship from other leaders within the organization. By proactively managing their own career paths, individuals can overcome the obstacles presented by a disengaged boss and continue to progress professionally.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, there is no specific information provided in the given news articles.
    </summary></entry></feed>