<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Tech</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml</id><updated>2024-06-12T16:08:08Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Powering the Future: Unraveling the Potential of Data Center Battery Storage and AI</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-06-12T16:08:08Z</published><updated>2024-06-12T16:08:08Z</updated><id>721b33ee-c97a-4264-b09c-149ec23cc592</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_tech.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/721b33ee-c97a-4264-b09c-149ec23cc592.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world today, there are several noteworthy events and developments. Firstly, a chef from the Greek Blue Zone Ikaria has shared three plant-based recipes that are inspired by the island's inhabitants who often live to be 100 years old. These recipes offer insights into the healthy and sustainable diet followed by the people of Ikaria, contributing to their longevity. Additionally, a video tutorial on creating and deploying a web app with Python and Azure has been released. This tutorial provides valuable guidance for developers interested in utilizing these technologies to build and launch web applications. Furthermore, there have been advancements in HTML layout elements and techniques, as well as responsive web designs. These developments in HTML allow for more dynamic and user-friendly web pages, enhancing the overall browsing experience. Lastly, HTML computer code elements have also seen progress, enabling developers to create more sophisticated and interactive websites. These tools, products, and projects demonstrate the continuous innovation and evolution happening in the technology and culinary sectors, offering exciting opportunities for individuals and businesses alike.
    </summary></entry></feed>