<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Science and Research</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_science_and_research.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_science_and_research.xml</id><updated>2024-07-01T16:04:46Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Unraveling the Foundations: Exploring the Intricacies of Buildings, Immunotherapy, Psychoactives, and More</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_science_and_research.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-07-01T16:04:46Z</published><updated>2024-07-01T16:04:46Z</updated><id>5d8ea3b9-4ae8-49a3-8da9-8a55b7908b12</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_science_and_research.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/5d8ea3b9-4ae8-49a3-8da9-8a55b7908b12.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world today, there have been several developments across various fields. In the realm of engineering, a study titled "A Failure Analysis of the Long-Term Overturning Stability of Concrete Continuous Single-Column Pier Bridges Considering Creep and Overloaded Vehicles" was conducted, focusing on the stability of bridge structures. Additionally, another study titled "Enhancing Construction Performance: A Critical Review of Performance Measurement Practices at the Project Level" aimed to improve construction practices by evaluating performance measurement techniques. Furthermore, a study on "Thermal Load Prediction in Residential Buildings Using Interpretable Classification" explored methods to predict thermal loads in residential buildings.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the field of healthcare, the world of immunotherapy has seen advancements. An article titled "The World of Immunotherapy Needs More Than PD-1/PD-L1—Two of the New Kids on the Block: LAG-3 and TIGIT" discussed the importance of exploring new avenues beyond the PD-1/PD-L1 pathway in immunotherapy. Additionally, a study titled "Probiotics Alter the Microbial and Behavioral Consequences of Methamphetamine Exposure in a Sex-Selective Manner" highlighted the potential of probiotics in mitigating the negative effects of methamphetamine exposure.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the domain of materials science, a research paper titled "Highly Efficient Phosphazene-Derivative-Based Flame Retardant with Comprehensive and Enhanced Fire Safety and Mechanical Performance for Polycarbonate" introduced a new flame retardant with improved fire safety and mechanical properties for polycarbonate materials.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, in the field of psychology, a study titled "Mothers’ Responses to Children’s Emotions and Children’s Behavior: The Mediating Role of Children’s Emotion Regulation" explored the relationship between maternal responses to children's emotions and children's behavior, with a focus on the mediating role of children's emotion regulation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As for new tools, products, or projects, there is a mention of an AI model in the study titled "Development of an AI Model Utilizing Buildings’ Thermal Mass to Optimize Heating Energy and Indoor Temperature in a Historical Building Located in a Cold Climate." This AI model aims to optimize heating energy and indoor temperature in historical buildings by utilizing the buildings' thermal mass.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the field of energy transition, the journal Resources published a paper titled "Hydrogen in Energy Transition: The Problem of Economic Efficiency, Environmental Safety, and Technological Readiness of Transportation and Storage." This paper discusses the challenges related to the economic efficiency, environmental safety, and technological readiness of hydrogen transportation and storage in the context of the energy transition.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, these developments in engineering, healthcare, materials science, psychology, and energy transition showcase the diverse range of research and innovation happening in the world today.
    </summary></entry></feed>