<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-09-01T16:07:04Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>The Cloud Chronicles: Unleashing Innovation with AWS Config Conformance Packs, Google Cloud's Memorystore, and AWS Amplify's New Function Capabilities</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-09-01T16:07:04Z</published><updated>2024-09-01T16:07:04Z</updated><id>a4607f4b-6752-4a9f-bfce-6c6db94abf70</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/a4607f4b-6752-4a9f-bfce-6c6db94abf70.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent news, AWS Config has expanded its availability by introducing conformance packs in 12 additional AWS Regions. This enhancement allows users to easily assess and manage the compliance of their AWS resources across a broader range of regions. Meanwhile, Google Cloud has launched Memorystore for Valkey, an open-source key-value service. This new offering provides developers with a reliable and scalable solution for storing and retrieving data in a simple key-value format. Additionally, Google Cloud is collaborating with emerging startups to drive the next wave of innovation. By leveraging the power of Google Cloud's infrastructure and services, these startups are able to develop groundbreaking solutions and contribute to technological advancements. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools and capabilities, AWS Amplify has introduced exciting function capabilities. Users can now schedule cron jobs and stream logs, enabling them to automate tasks and gain real-time insights into their applications. This enhancement enhances the functionality and flexibility of AWS Amplify, empowering developers to build and deploy applications more efficiently. Furthermore, AWS Control Tower has expanded its capabilities by allowing Organizational Units to contain up to 1,000 accounts. This update provides organizations with greater flexibility in managing and organizing their AWS accounts within Control Tower. Lastly, AWS Deadline Cloud now supports Windows Server 2022 in service-managed fleets. This compatibility enhancement ensures that users can seamlessly leverage the latest version of Windows Server in their rendering workloads, further enhancing the performance and efficiency of their projects.
    </summary></entry></feed>