<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Science and Research</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_science_and_research.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_science_and_research.xml</id><updated>2024-06-15T16:07:16Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>The Power Source Revolution: Exploring Yttrium-Based Complexes in Zinc Batteries</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_science_and_research.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-06-15T16:07:16Z</published><updated>2024-06-15T16:07:16Z</updated><id>2de3d2fb-01a7-46d4-b75b-092778443c5a</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_science_and_research.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/2de3d2fb-01a7-46d4-b75b-092778443c5a.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent news, several significant developments have taken place in various fields. Researchers have made progress in the field of battery technology with the discovery of a water-insoluble yttrium-based complex that acts as a dual-ionic electrolyte additive, enhancing the stability of aqueous zinc metal batteries. Another breakthrough in the field of catalysis has been achieved by synergizing cobalt phthalocyanine on a carbon nitride surface, boosting the selective oxidation of nitrogen to nitric acid. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the field of bioengineering, scientists have successfully engineered an anisotropic skeletal muscle organoid-on-a-chip, which allows for the study of muscle response under intermittent hypoxia. Additionally, liquid crystal elastomer hollow fibers have been developed as artificial muscles, capable of large and rapid actuation through a thermal-pneumatic enhanced effect.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Advancements in materials science have also been made, with the creation of 3D printed silk fibroin-based hydrogels that possess tunable adhesion and stretchability, making them ideal for wearable sensing applications. Surface sulfur decoration over Mo2C has enabled coordinated adsorption/desorption kinetics, boosting the hydrogen evolution reaction. Furthermore, a polyamidoxime-coated coconut haustorium derived magnetic biochar adsorbent with photothermal conversion capabilities has been developed for highly efficient uranium recovery from nuclear wastewater.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the realm of energy storage, researchers have achieved ultra-high capacity and stable dual-ion batteries with fast kinetics through the use of HOF supermolecules derived 3D nitrogen-oxygen co-doped nanocarbon anodes. Dielectric polymers have also been enhanced through fluorine incorporation, resulting in improved energy storage, reduced loss, and enhanced processability. Lastly, a novel oxide KCsMoP2O9 single crystal has demonstrated ultralow detection limits and anisotropic X-ray detection behaviors, opening up new possibilities in the field of sensing and imaging.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, the advancements mentioned above highlight the development of various innovative technologies. These include the water-insoluble yttrium-based complex for stable aqueous zinc metal batteries, the anisotropic skeletal muscle organoid-on-a-chip, and the liquid crystal elastomer hollow fibers as artificial muscles. Additionally, the 3D printed silk fibroin-based hydrogels, polyamidoxime-coated coconut haustorium derived magnetic biochar adsorbent, and HOF supermolecules derived 3D nitrogen-oxygen co-doped nanocarbon anodes represent new materials and products with unique properties and applications. These advancements demonstrate the continuous progress being made in various scientific and technological fields, paving the way for further innovation and development.
    </summary></entry></feed>