<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-04-23T16:05:12Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>"Data Dominance: Unleashing the Power of Cortex Framework for Competitive Advantage"&lt;br&gt;"Unleashing the Ninja Van: Revolutionizing Core Applications with Cloud Containers"&lt;br&gt;"Building a Serverless Data Warehouse: Harnessing the Power of Amazon EMR, Athena, and Dolphinscheduler"&lt;br&gt;"Unleashing the DolphinScheduler: Integrating Apache Dolphinscheduler for Resource Consumption Analysis"&lt;br&gt;"Mastering EMR Serverless: Optimization and Integration Strategies for a Serverless Data Warehouse"&lt;br&gt;"Revolutionizing Azure Databricks: Changes to Billing Meter for Materialized Views and Streaming Tables"</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-04-23T16:05:12Z</published><updated>2024-04-23T16:05:12Z</updated><id>93aa3f87-cf23-4978-82f8-2ad7faf231a2</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/93aa3f87-cf23-4978-82f8-2ad7faf231a2.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world, there have been several developments in the field of data management and cloud computing. Cortex Framework has introduced new solutions that allow businesses to utilize data as a competitive edge. These solutions provide advanced tools and techniques for analyzing and leveraging data effectively.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another significant development is the cloud container platform offered by Ninja Van. This platform aims to deliver flexibility, stability, and scalability to core applications. By utilizing cloud containers, businesses can optimize their operations and ensure smooth functioning of their applications.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additionally, there have been advancements in building serverless data warehouses in hybrid deployment environments. Amazon EMR Serverless, Amazon Athena, Apache Dolphinscheduler, as well as local TiDB and HDFS, are being used to construct these data warehouses. These solutions enable seamless synchronization of data between cloud and on-premises environments, providing businesses with efficient data management capabilities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Furthermore, Apache Dolphinscheduler has been integrated into the data warehouse setup, allowing for better resource consumption analysis at the level of Line of Business (LOB). This integration enhances the overall performance and optimization of the data warehouse.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, there are updates regarding the billing meter for Azure Databricks materialized views and streaming tables. Starting from 1 May 2024, there will be changes in the billing structure for these services, which will impact businesses utilizing Azure Databricks for their data processing and analytics needs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, the mentioned developments highlight the emergence of advanced data management solutions and cloud computing platforms. These advancements provide businesses with the ability to harness the power of data, optimize their operations, and make informed decisions. The integration of Apache Dolphinscheduler and the upcoming changes in Azure Databricks billing further enhance the capabilities and efficiency of data processing and analytics.
    </summary></entry></feed>