<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.fun/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.fun/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-10-21T16:10:03Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Cloud Chronicles: Unpacking AWS Innovations and Data Dynamics</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.fun/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-10-21T16:10:03Z</published><updated>2024-10-21T16:10:03Z</updated><id>0955b564-6000-4d06-abe6-1b71a5df6e51</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.fun/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/0955b564-6000-4d06-abe6-1b71a5df6e51.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent developments within the tech world, Amazon has made significant strides in enhancing its cloud services and tools. The launch of Amazon DataZone now includes support for AWS IAM Identity Center account instances, streamlining user management and access control. Additionally, Amazon RDS has improved its Multi-AZ deployment capabilities by introducing two readable standbys that now support AWS IAM database authentication, enhancing security and availability. The AWS Marketplace has expanded its reach by supporting offers in four new currencies and allowing non-US bank accounts for disbursement, making it more accessible to a global audience. Furthermore, AWS Data Exchange has introduced APIs for data grants, facilitating programmatic data sharing, while the AWS Lambda console has upgraded its features to support real-time log analytics through Amazon CloudWatch Logs Live Tail. In the realm of model evaluation, Amazon Bedrock now allows users to evaluate custom model imports, providing more flexibility in assessing model performance. The AWS Lambda console also features a new dashboard that surfaces key function insights via built-in Amazon CloudWatch Metrics Insights. Moreover, Amazon Aurora PostgreSQL and Amazon DynamoDB have officially launched zero ETL integration with Amazon Redshift, simplifying data workflows. Lastly, QuickSight has introduced support for subfolders in restricted folders, enabling more governed data sharing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;### New Tools, Products, or Projects:&lt;br&gt;1. **Amazon DataZone**: Now supports AWS IAM Identity Center account instances.&lt;br&gt;2. **Amazon RDS**: Multi-AZ deployment with two readable standbys now supports AWS IAM database authentication.&lt;br&gt;3. **AWS Marketplace**: Expanded to support offers in four new currencies and non-US bank accounts for disbursement.&lt;br&gt;4. **AWS Data Exchange**: New APIs for programmatic data sharing via data grants.&lt;br&gt;5. **AWS Lambda Console**: Real-time log analytics via Amazon CloudWatch Logs Live Tail.&lt;br&gt;6. **Amazon Bedrock**: Model evaluation now supports custom model imports.&lt;br&gt;7. **AWS Lambda Console**: New dashboard for key function insights using Amazon CloudWatch Metrics Insights.&lt;br&gt;8. **Amazon Aurora PostgreSQL &amp; Amazon DynamoDB**: Launched zero ETL integration with Amazon Redshift.&lt;br&gt;9. **QuickSight**: Added support for subfolders in restricted folders for governed data sharing.
    </summary></entry></feed>