<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-03-25T16:07:01Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>1. "Navigating the Future: Exploring the Transition to Azure Maps Web SDK"&lt;br&gt;2. "Defending the Cloud: Unpacking the Retirement of Compliance Features in Microsoft Defender"&lt;br&gt;3. "Farewell to the A-Series: Understanding the Retirement of Basic and Standard VMs on HDInsight"&lt;br&gt;4. "Saying Goodbye to HDInsight 4.0: Migrating Your Clusters to Azure HDInsight 5.1"&lt;br&gt;5. "Cost Management in Transition: Bid Farewell to Connector for AWS"&lt;br&gt;6. "Simplified Node Communication: The Retirement of Default Internet Outbound Access"&lt;br&gt;7. "Grafana Evolution: Action Recommended for Azure Managed Grafana Users"&lt;br&gt;8. "Node 20 LTS Upgrade: The Deadline for App Service Apps"&lt;br&gt;9. "Continued Support: Updating to Azure Functions Service Bus Extension v5.x"&lt;br&gt;10. ".NET 7 Farewell: The Urgency to Upgrade Azure Functions Resources to .NET 8"</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-03-25T16:07:01Z</published><updated>2024-03-25T16:07:01Z</updated><id>77f47bc7-d3ce-49a9-8625-b42061d4d3fc</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/77f47bc7-d3ce-49a9-8625-b42061d4d3fc.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of technology, there have been several updates and retirements announced by Microsoft. Firstly, the Azure Maps Native SDK for Android and iOS will be retired on 31 March 2025. Users are advised to transition to using the Azure Maps Web SDK in a web view. Additionally, certain compliance features in Microsoft Defender for Cloud will be retired on September 30, 2025. This indicates a shift in the focus of the platform's security measures. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Furthermore, Basic and Standard A-series VMs on HDInsight will retire on 31 August 2024. Users are encouraged to migrate their HDInsight clusters to version 5.1 of Azure HDInsight, which will be retired on 31 March 2025. This suggests an upgrade in the capabilities and performance of the HDInsight service. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of cost management, the support for Connector for AWS in Cost Management will end on 31 March 2025. This may require users to find alternative solutions for managing their costs and expenses. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moreover, the default Internet outbound access for Simplified node communication Batch pools without public IP addresses will be retired on 30 September 2025. This change may impact the accessibility and connectivity of certain Batch pools. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of specific tools and projects, it is recommended to update to using Grafana version 10 for Azure Managed Grafana. This update may bring new features and improvements to the Grafana platform. Additionally, users are required to upgrade their App Service apps to Node 20 LTS by 30 April 2025, indicating a shift towards a more advanced and efficient Node version. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Furthermore, it is advised to update to Azure Functions Service Bus extension v5.x by 31 March 2025 for continued support. This update may enhance the functionality and performance of Azure Functions. Lastly, the support for .NET 7 will end on 14 May 2024, urging users to upgrade their Azure Functions resources to .NET 8. This upgrade may bring new features and improvements to the Azure Functions framework. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, these updates and retirements in the world of technology showcase the continuous evolution and advancements in various Microsoft services and tools. Users are encouraged to stay updated and make the necessary transitions to ensure smooth operations and optimal performance.
    </summary></entry></feed>