<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-02-17T08:06:12Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>1. "Chilled Bytes: Unleashing the Power of Azure Blob Storage Cold Tier"&lt;br&gt;2. "The AI Advocate: Navigating AI Policy and Building Strong Relationships"&lt;br&gt;3. "24/7 Tech Love: Exploring the Exciting Session Catalog"&lt;br&gt;4. "Revolutionizing Monitoring: Introducing Amazon CloudWatch Synthetics Runtimes"</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-02-17T08:06:12Z</published><updated>2024-02-17T08:06:12Z</updated><id>56d4b882-d1de-4a4c-a627-3ba274878716</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/56d4b882-d1de-4a4c-a627-3ba274878716.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of technology, some exciting developments have taken place. Azure Blob Storage Cold Tier support is now generally available on Change Feed and Object Replication. This means that users can now easily access and manage their data stored in Azure Blob Storage, even in colder storage tiers. Additionally, the AI Alliance has emerged, focusing on how to establish friendly relationships and influence AI policy. This initiative aims to bring together experts and stakeholders to collaborate on shaping the future of AI in a responsible and ethical manner. In other news, the highly anticipated '24 love' event has released its full session catalog, offering a diverse range of sessions for attendees to choose from. Lastly, Amazon CloudWatch Synthetics has introduced new versions, including NodeJS/Puppeteer Runtime versions 6.2 and 5.2, as well as Python/Selenium Runtime version 2.1. These updates enhance the capabilities of CloudWatch Synthetics, allowing developers to monitor and test their applications more effectively. With these advancements, the world of technology continues to evolve, bringing new tools, projects, and possibilities for users and developers alike.
    </summary></entry></feed>