<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-03-23T16:07:06Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>"The Tech Upgrade Show: Stay Ahead with the Latest Innovations and Retirements"</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-03-23T16:07:06Z</published><updated>2024-03-23T16:07:06Z</updated><id>7550c62d-aae5-429d-9a3a-2ba87eb21fe6</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/7550c62d-aae5-429d-9a3a-2ba87eb21fe6.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of technology, there are several important updates and changes that you should be aware of. Firstly, it is crucial to upgrade your App Service apps to Node 20 LTS by 30 April 2025. This upgrade will ensure that your apps are running on the latest and most secure version of Node.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additionally, Azure HDInsight 4.0 will be retired on 31 March 2025. If you have any HDInsight clusters, it is recommended to migrate them to version 5.1 to continue receiving support and updates.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For users of Azure Managed Grafana, it is highly recommended to update to Grafana version 10. This update will provide you with the latest features and improvements for your Azure Managed Grafana environment.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some compliance features in Microsoft Defender for Cloud will be retired on September 30, 2025. It is important to stay updated on these changes and ensure that your security measures are up to date.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Furthermore, the Azure Maps Native SDK for Android and iOS will be retired on 31 March 2025. To continue using Azure Maps, it is advised to transition to the Azure Maps Web SDK in a web view.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of virtual machines, the Basic and Standard A-series VMs on HDInsight will retire on 31 August 2024. If you are currently using these VMs, it is recommended to plan for a migration to alternative options.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another important update pertains to Simplified node communication Batch pools without public IP addresses. The default Internet outbound access for these pools will be retired on 30 September 2025. It is essential to make the necessary adjustments to ensure continued connectivity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the realm of software, support for .NET 7 will end on 14 May 2024. If you have Azure Functions resources, it is crucial to upgrade them to .NET 8 to avoid any compatibility issues.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, the Connector for AWS in Cost Management will no longer be supported after 31 March 2025. If you are currently using this connector, it is recommended to explore alternative options for managing your costs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, there is no specific information provided in the news. However, it is always advisable to stay updated with the latest announcements and releases from Microsoft and other technology providers to discover new tools, products, and projects that may be relevant to your needs.
    </summary></entry></feed>