<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-08-31T16:07:40Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>The Cloud Chronicles: Unleashing Innovation with AWS Config, Control Tower, and Google Cloud</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-08-31T16:07:40Z</published><updated>2024-08-31T16:07:40Z</updated><id>a39e973d-417b-40f6-acd7-21bbd6fbd5c5</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/a39e973d-417b-40f6-acd7-21bbd6fbd5c5.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent news, AWS has expanded its Config conformance packs to 12 additional AWS Regions, allowing users to ensure compliance across a wider range of regions. Additionally, AWS Control Tower now allows Organizational Units to contain up to 1,000 accounts, providing greater flexibility and scalability for managing accounts within an organization. On the other hand, Google Cloud has been collaborating with emerging startups to drive the next wave of innovation, leveraging its powerful infrastructure and services. In another development, AWS Deadline Cloud has announced support for Windows Server 2022 in service-managed fleets, enabling users to efficiently manage their rendering workloads. Furthermore, AWS Amplify has introduced new function capabilities, including scheduled cron jobs and streaming logs, enhancing the flexibility and functionality of the platform. Lastly, Google Cloud has launched Memorystore for Valkey, an open-source key-value service that offers reliable and scalable storage for developers. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, AWS Config conformance packs and AWS Control Tower's expanded capabilities provide organizations with improved compliance management and account scalability. Google Cloud's collaboration with startups aims to foster innovation and drive technological advancements. AWS Deadline Cloud's support for Windows Server 2022 enhances rendering workload management. AWS Amplify's new function capabilities offer developers more flexibility and control over their applications. Lastly, Google Cloud's Memorystore for Valkey provides developers with a reliable and scalable key-value service for their storage needs.
    </summary></entry></feed>