<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-03-31T16:04:40Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>1. "Retirement Roadmap: Navigating Azure Storage C++ Client Libraries and More"&lt;br&gt;2. "Farewell to Custom .Net Deserializers: Azure Stream Analytics Retirement"&lt;br&gt;3. "Windows Server 2022 and k8s 1.34: A Retirement Journey"&lt;br&gt;4. "Redis Enterprise and Enterprise Flash: Bid Farewell to Every-write AOF Persistence"&lt;br&gt;5. "Azure Data Factory's Memory Optimized Data Flows: Retiring for Better Performance"&lt;br&gt;6. "Saying Goodbye to Standard_NC Azure Virtual Machines: Prepare for Retirement"&lt;br&gt;7. "The Final Countdown: Support for .NET 6 Ends, Azure Functions Upgrade to .NET 8"&lt;br&gt;8. "Ubuntu 20.04 LTS and Batch Pools: Retirement on the Horizon"&lt;br&gt;9. "APIOps Migration: Transforming Git Repositories with Automated Deployments"</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-03-31T16:04:40Z</published><updated>2024-03-31T16:04:40Z</updated><id>163c6ac3-50a7-4198-9082-4c45eadb2172</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/163c6ac3-50a7-4198-9082-4c45eadb2172.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of technology, several retirements and changes have been announced. Firstly, the legacy Azure Storage C++ client libraries will be retired on 29 March 2025, followed by the retirement of the Custom .Net deserializer for Azure Stream Analytics on 30 September 2024. Additionally, Windows Server 2022 will retire with k8s 1.34 in March 2027. Another retirement notice is regarding the Every-write AOF persistence on Azure Cache for Redis Enterprise and Enterprise Flash, which will be retired on 1 April 2025. The retirement of the Custom .net deserializer for Azure Stream Analytics is also scheduled for 30 September 2024. Furthermore, Memory Optimized Data Flows in Azure Data Factory will be retired, and users are advised to utilize General Purpose for better performance at a lower price. Standard_NC6s_v3, Standard_NC12s_v3, and Standard_NC24s_v3 Azure virtual machines will be retired on September 30, 2025. It is important to note that support for .NET 6 will end on 12 November 2024, urging users to upgrade their Azure Functions apps to .NET 8. Lastly, the support for Ubuntu 20.04 LTS for Batch pools will be retired on 23 April 2025. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, there is an exciting development called APIOps. Users are encouraged to migrate their Git Repository to automated deployments with APIOps by 15 March 2025. This new project aims to streamline and enhance the deployment process, providing a more efficient and automated approach. It offers a promising solution for developers and organizations looking to optimize their deployment workflows.
    </summary></entry></feed>