<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Tech</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml</id><updated>2024-08-01T16:05:30Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>The Future of 3D Data Prep: RapidPipeline Unleashed at SIGGRAPH 2024</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-08-01T16:05:30Z</published><updated>2024-08-01T16:05:30Z</updated><id>211a719e-c248-4923-98c2-24bd4d2687b1</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_tech.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/211a719e-c248-4923-98c2-24bd4d2687b1.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent news, the technology world has seen some exciting developments. One of the highlights is the release of RapidPipeline at SIGGRAPH 2024. This groundbreaking tool has revolutionized the process of 3D data preparation, making it as easy as ordering a pizza. With RapidPipeline, professionals in the field can now streamline their workflow and save valuable time and resources.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the field of artificial intelligence, OpenAI has made significant strides with the testing of their latest model, GPT-4o. This long-output version of the AI system allows for the generation of up to 64,000 tokens in a single instance. However, it comes at a cost, with a price of $6 for every million tokens input and $18 for the output. This advancement showcases the continuous progress being made in the field of AI and its potential applications.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the realm of sustainability, colocation data centers have found new ways to reduce carbon emissions in the AI world. Sponsored content highlights three methods that these centers can employ to minimize their environmental impact. By implementing energy-efficient practices and utilizing renewable energy sources, these data centers can contribute to a greener future.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additionally, Riello UPS has introduced their modular Multi Power2, which aims to raise efficiency to unparalleled heights. This innovative product offers a flexible and scalable solution for power protection in data centers. By optimizing energy usage and reducing wastage, Multi Power2 contributes to a more sustainable and cost-effective infrastructure.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the world of news publishing, AI search engine Perplexity has launched a revenue-sharing program with six publishers. This initiative allows publishers to monetize their content by partnering with Perplexity. By leveraging AI technology, Perplexity aims to enhance the discoverability and accessibility of news articles while providing a new revenue stream for publishers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;These recent developments showcase the continuous advancements and innovations in the technology sector. From streamlining 3D data preparation to reducing carbon emissions and enabling revenue sharing in news publishing, these tools, products, and projects are shaping the world we live in.
    </summary></entry></feed>