<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Science and Research</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_science_and_research.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_science_and_research.xml</id><updated>2024-03-23T16:06:21Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Podcast Title: "Cutting Through the Diagnosis: Exploring Intravascular Hematolymphoid Entities"&lt;br&gt;Podcast Title: "Pufferfish Predicaments: Unraveling the Health Impacts in the Eastern Mediterranean"&lt;br&gt;Podcast Title: "Global Efforts, Global Emergency: Tackling Polio Outbreaks with Novel Oral Vaccines"&lt;br&gt;Podcast Title: "Basil's Battle: Unveiling the Impact of Rhizobacteria and Insect Herbivory on Essential Oil Production"&lt;br&gt;Podcast Title: "Through the Retina: Understanding Arterial Occlusions and Their Diagnosis"&lt;br&gt;Podcast Title: "The Oral Connection: Unraveling the Synergistic Effects of P. gingivalis and F. nucleatum on Oral Health"&lt;br&gt;Podcast Title: "Preserving Freshness: Exploring Biogenic Amine Levels in Edible Film-Coated Chicken"&lt;br&gt;Podcast Title: "Aligning Smiles: Evaluating the Use of Clear Aligners in Growing Patients"&lt;br&gt;Podcast Title: "Breathing for Wellbeing: Investigating the Effects of Nostril Breathing on the Mind"&lt;br&gt;Podcast Title: "Tracing Ternary Relations: Insights from Bandler-Kohout Compositions in Mathematics"</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_science_and_research.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-03-23T16:06:21Z</published><updated>2024-03-23T16:06:21Z</updated><id>17d612c7-72d9-4f0e-af57-4d3ca50801cf</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_science_and_research.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/17d612c7-72d9-4f0e-af57-4d3ca50801cf.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent news, several interesting developments have taken place across various fields. In the field of diagnostics, a review titled "Cutaneous Intravascular Hematolymphoid Entities" was published in the journal Diagnostics. This review explores the various entities related to blood and lymphatic disorders affecting the skin. Moving on to human health impacts, a study published in Biology titled "Assessment of Human Health Impacts from Invasive Pufferfish" focuses on the attacks, poisonings, and fatalities caused by these fish in the Eastern Mediterranean region. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Addressing a global health emergency, the journal Pathogens features a paper titled "Novel Oral Polio Vaccine Type 2 Use for Polio Outbreak Response." This study highlights the global efforts made to combat polio outbreaks using a new oral vaccine. Shifting to the realm of plants, the journal Plants presents a study titled "Simultaneous Impact of Rhizobacteria Inoculation and Leaf-Chewing Insect Herbivory on Essential Oil Production and VOC Emissions in Ocimum basilicum." This research investigates the effects of both beneficial bacteria and insect herbivory on the production of essential oils in basil plants.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the medical field, the journal Medicina published a narrative review titled "Aetiology, Diagnosis, and Treatment of Arterial Occlusions of the Retina." This review provides insights into the causes, diagnosis, and treatment options for arterial occlusions affecting the retina. Additionally, the International Journal of Molecular Sciences (IJMS) features a study titled "Co-Culture of P. gingivalis and F. nucleatum Synergistically Elevates IL-6 Expression via TLR4 Signaling in Oral Keratinocytes." This research explores the interaction between two bacteria and their impact on the expression of IL-6 in oral keratinocytes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moving on to food science, the journal Foods presents a study titled "Determination of Biogenic Amine Level Variations upon Storage, in Chicken Breast Coated with Edible Protective Film." This research investigates the changes in biogenic amine levels in chicken breast when coated with an edible protective film during storage. In the field of child health, the journal Children features a systematic review titled "Clear Aligners in the Growing Patient." This review examines the use of clear aligners in orthodontic treatment for growing patients.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, in the field of neuroscience, the journal Brain Sciences published a pilot study titled "Breathing Right… or Left! The Effects of Unilateral Nostril Breathing on Psychological and Cognitive Wellbeing." This study explores the effects of unilateral nostril breathing on psychological and cognitive wellbeing. In the field of mathematics, the journal Mathematics presents a study titled "Traces of Ternary Relations Based on Bandler–Kohout Compositions." This research focuses on the traces of ternary relations using Bandler-Kohout compositions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, there is no specific information provided in the news articles.
    </summary></entry></feed>