<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-09-12T16:08:15Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>The Power Duo: Microsoft and Oracle Revolutionize Data and AI Integration in Oracle Database@Azure</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-09-12T16:08:15Z</published><updated>2024-09-12T16:08:15Z</updated><id>d8d63dcd-ff3e-4018-9445-0e2c8e466a6e</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/d8d63dcd-ff3e-4018-9445-0e2c8e466a6e.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent news, Microsoft and Oracle have collaborated to enhance the capabilities of Oracle Database@Azure by integrating data and artificial intelligence (AI) technologies. This partnership aims to provide users with a more seamless and efficient experience when working with Oracle Database on the Azure cloud platform. By leveraging AI, users can gain valuable insights from their data and make informed decisions. This integration will enable businesses to harness the power of both Oracle Database and Azure's advanced data and AI tools, ultimately driving innovation and productivity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In addition to this collaboration, Amazon has introduced a new feature that allows users to directly utilize Apache Spark on Amazon EMR Serverless through Amazon SageMaker Studio. This integration simplifies the process of running Apache Spark applications on EMR Serverless, making it more accessible and user-friendly. With this new tool, developers can leverage the power of Apache Spark for big data processing without the need to manage infrastructure or worry about scaling resources. This advancement in cloud computing technology empowers users to efficiently analyze and process large datasets, enabling them to derive valuable insights and drive data-driven decision-making.
    </summary></entry></feed>