<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Science and Research</title><link href="https://novasparkxx.github.io/trend_science_and_research.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://novasparkxx.github.io/trend_science_and_research.xml</id><updated>2024-01-31T19:28:29Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Trend Science and Research report on Wed, 31 Jan 2024 19:28:29</title><link href="https://novasparkxx.github.io/trend_science_and_research.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-01-31T19:28:29Z</published><updated>2024-01-31T19:28:29Z</updated><id>cd577671-676e-46da-bd38-7bfdea2a92cd</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://imgproxy.nanxiongnandi.com/P_O89MPBYlhmFIfXN1-KWHdQIOZ40lkQcMHMZlMdWf8/w:1280/aHR0cHM6Ly9pbWcu/bmFueGlvbmduYW5k/aS5jb20vMjAyNDAx/L0J1a2hhbnNhblNl/b3VsLmpwZw.jpg" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/cd577671-676e-46da-bd38-7bfdea2a92cd.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        Based on the provided news articles, several developments have taken place in various fields. In the medical field, a study published in JCM highlights the importance of systemic inflammatory response and the NUn score as early predictors of anastomotic leakage after esophageal reconstructive surgery. This research can potentially improve patient outcomes and guide surgical decision-making.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the field of technology, Sensors presents an improved nested U-Net network for fluorescence in situ hybridization cell image segmentation. This advancement in image analysis can enhance the accuracy and efficiency of cell imaging techniques, leading to better understanding and diagnosis of various diseases.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Atmosphere focuses on the improvement of PM2.5 forecast in China through ground-based multi-pollutant emission source inversion. This research aims to provide more accurate and reliable air quality predictions, contributing to better public health management and environmental policies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;BDCC introduces a simultaneous wireless information and power transfer-based multi-hop uneven clustering routing protocol for EH-Cognitive Radio Sensor Networks. This innovation enables efficient data transmission and power management in sensor networks, enhancing their performance and energy sustainability.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the field of environmental science, Remote Sensing presents a lake ice thickness retrieval method with ICESat-2-assisted CryoSat-2 echo peak selection. This research provides a valuable tool for monitoring and understanding changes in ice thickness, which is crucial for climate studies and water resource management.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the construction industry, Infrastructures focuses on the identification and ranking of factors affecting the delay risk of high-rise construction projects. By utilizing the AHP and VIKOR methods, this study offers insights into project management strategies and risk mitigation in the construction sector.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nanomaterials presents research on micro lubrication and heat transfer in a wedge-shaped channel slider with convex surface texture based on the lattice Boltzmann method. This study explores innovative techniques for improving lubrication and heat transfer in mechanical systems, potentially enhancing their efficiency and lifespan.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Axioms discusses the exponential stability of dynamical systems on time scales, with an application to multi-agent systems. This research contributes to the understanding and control of complex systems, offering insights into stability analysis and optimization in various fields.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, Metabolites highlights the role of metabolomics in preclinical drug safety assessment. This review article discusses the current status and future trends of metabolomics, emphasizing its potential in improving drug development and safety evaluation processes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, these studies and developments showcase the continuous progress and innovation in various scientific and technological fields, contributing to advancements in healthcare, environmental monitoring, construction management, and more.
    </summary></entry></feed>