<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-08-26T16:07:54Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Trailblazing Agent Performance: Unveiling Amazon Connect Contact Lens</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-08-26T16:07:54Z</published><updated>2024-08-26T16:07:54Z</updated><id>afce07f9-e9c3-4452-884a-098aca40184f</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/afce07f9-e9c3-4452-884a-098aca40184f.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of technology, several updates and developments have taken place. Firstly, Amazon Connect Contact Lens has introduced a new feature that provides an audit trail for changes made to an agent's performance evaluation. This will enhance transparency and accountability in evaluating agent performance.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Secondly, Amazon Q has undergone improvements and now offers more detailed information about user subscriptions and associated resources. This enhancement will enable users to have a better understanding of their subscriptions and manage them effectively.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Furthermore, CloudFormation has introduced a new feature that simplifies resource discovery and template review in the IaC (Infrastructure as Code) Generator. This will streamline the process of creating and managing resources, making it more efficient and user-friendly.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the field of artificial intelligence, there have been significant advancements as well. A practical guide has been released to help users maximize their LLM (Low Latency Mode) serving throughput for GPUs on GKE (Google Kubernetes Engine). This guide will assist in optimizing the performance of AI models running on GPUs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moving on to regional updates, AWS Resource Access Manager is now available in the AWS Asia Pacific (Malaysia) Region. This expansion will provide users in that region with improved access and management of their AWS resources.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additionally, Amazon EC2 C7i-flex instances are now accessible in the US East (N. Virginia) Region. This expansion will offer users in that region more options and flexibility in utilizing EC2 instances.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the realm of SAP (Systems, Applications, and Products), AWS Systems Manager has introduced console integration for application-aware stop and start of SAP. This integration will simplify the management of SAP applications, allowing for more efficient control and operation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moreover, Amazon Bedrock has introduced select FMs (Feature Models) for batch inference at 50% of the on-demand inference price. This will enable users to perform batch inference at a reduced cost, making it more accessible and affordable.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, Amazon Data Firehose is now available in the AWS Asia Pacific (Malaysia) region. This expansion will provide users in that region with a reliable and scalable data streaming service for their data processing needs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, the advancements mentioned above highlight the continuous innovation and improvement in various areas of technology. These developments aim to enhance user experience, optimize performance, and expand accessibility to resources and services.
    </summary></entry></feed>