<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Tech</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml</id><updated>2024-07-11T16:06:33Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Config Conundrums: Solving the 'Please delete the RemediationConfiguration and try again' Issue in AWS</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-07-11T16:06:33Z</published><updated>2024-07-11T16:06:33Z</updated><id>14d00e1e-9dfc-4118-83a7-de9d04ba2cf7</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_tech.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/14d00e1e-9dfc-4118-83a7-de9d04ba2cf7.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent news, there has been a solution found for the problem that arises when deleting AWS Config rules. The issue of encountering the "Please delete the RemediationConfiguration and try again" message has been resolved. This development will provide users with a smoother experience when managing AWS Config rules and configurations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additionally, a new tool has been introduced that allows users to utilize an SQL editor for batch execution of SQL files. This tool is particularly useful for those working with MySQL and SQLynx. With the SQL editor, users can efficiently execute multiple SQL files in a batch, streamlining their workflow and enhancing productivity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In other news, it has been revealed that wealthy individuals have the ability to purchase their way into Hong Kong residency. This controversial practice has led to a majority of applicants coming from just two small countries. The news sheds light on the influence of wealth in immigration policies and raises questions about fairness and equality in the process.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, the introduction of the SQL editor for batch execution of SQL files is a significant development. This tool will greatly benefit individuals and organizations working with MySQL and SQLynx, allowing for efficient and streamlined execution of multiple SQL files. It showcases the continuous advancements in technology and the efforts to enhance productivity and ease of use in the field of database management.
    </summary></entry></feed>