<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Business and Market</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_business_and_market.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_business_and_market.xml</id><updated>2024-06-01T16:07:53Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>The Split Story: Uncovering the Hidden Truths of Nvidia's Stock Split</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_business_and_market.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-06-01T16:07:53Z</published><updated>2024-06-01T16:07:53Z</updated><id>f2ce2df7-d21c-4ddc-baef-995e28983bcd</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_business_and_market.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/f2ce2df7-d21c-4ddc-baef-995e28983bcd.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world news, Nvidia has announced a stock split, but investors should focus on a more important matter. Hyundai has reported a 7% increase in sales, driven by the popularity of SUVs. VW celebrates the 50th anniversary of the Passat with a new estate-only version, tested on UK roads. A Chennai-Mumbai IndiGo flight had to make an emergency landing due to a bomb threat, but the situation was resolved and all 172 passengers are safe. As the possibility of Trump winning the election looms, markets are concerned about the potential impact of new trade wars. SEBI has introduced a Rumour Verification Framework, requiring the top 100 companies to verify market rumors starting from June 1. Microsoft has agreed to pay off a cloud industry group to settle an EU antitrust complaint. A cheap stock has experienced a 94% decline, raising questions about whether it presents an investment opportunity. The IMD predicts that the Southwest Monsoon will likely reach Madhya Pradesh by June 15. Lastly, there is a new and potentially risky asset class gaining attention in the market.
    </summary></entry></feed>