<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://novasparkxx.github.io/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://novasparkxx.github.io/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-02-02T20:04:40Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>1. "Retirement of Support for Log Alert Rules with Cross-Workspace Queries"&lt;br&gt;2. "Consuming Cloud Storage Objects on GKE with Kubernetes API - Part I"&lt;br&gt;3. "Azure Virtual Network Manager Security Admin Rule Now Available in 30 Regions"&lt;br&gt;4. "Exploring the Ransomware Dilemma: To Pay or Not To Pay?"&lt;br&gt;5. "29 No-Cost Ways to Advance Your Cloud Career in February"&lt;br&gt;6. "New Chat Experience with AWS Glue: Integrating Amazon Q Dataset (Preview)"&lt;br&gt;7. "Benefits of Moving to S/4 HANA on Google Cloud for Deutsche Börse Group"&lt;br&gt;8. "Private Preview: Azure Site Recovery Support for Azure Trusted Launch VMs (Windows OS)"</title><link href="https://novasparkxx.github.io/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-02-02T20:04:40Z</published><updated>2024-02-02T20:04:40Z</updated><id>4d39cde7-4e4b-4cb0-abba-c800714ab880</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://imgproxy.nanxiongnandi.com/P_O89MPBYlhmFIfXN1-KWHdQIOZ40lkQcMHMZlMdWf8/w:1280/aHR0cHM6Ly9pbWcu/bmFueGlvbmduYW5k/aS5jb20vMjAyNDAx/L0J1a2hhbnNhblNl/b3VsLmpwZw.jpg" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/4d39cde7-4e4b-4cb0-abba-c800714ab880.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world news, it has been announced that support for log alert rules that use cross-workspace queries with resource names or qualified name identifiers will be retired on May 31, 2024. This change will affect the way log alert rules are handled and will require users to adapt to new methods. Additionally, there is a report that explores the crucial question of whether to pay or not to pay when faced with ransomware attacks. This report delves into the various factors that organizations should consider when making this decision. In the technology sector, there are several new tools, products, and projects. One such development is the availability of Azure Virtual Network Manager security admin rule in 30 regions. This tool allows for enhanced security management within virtual networks. Another interesting project is the introduction of a new chat experience in AWS Glue, called Amazon Q dataset integration. This feature utilizes natural language processing to facilitate data integration tasks. Furthermore, there are 29 no-cost ways to advance one's cloud career this February, providing individuals with valuable resources and opportunities for professional growth. Lastly, Deutsche Börse Group has announced the significant benefits of moving to S/4 HANA on Google Cloud, highlighting the advantages of this migration for the organization. In the realm of Azure, there is a private preview of Azure Site Recovery support for Azure Trusted Launch VMs with Windows OS, offering enhanced recovery capabilities for virtual machines. These developments showcase the continuous evolution and innovation happening in the technology and cloud computing sectors.
    </summary></entry></feed>