<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Business and Market</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_business_and_market.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_business_and_market.xml</id><updated>2024-06-25T16:08:41Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Behind Closed Vaults: Unraveling the Bankers' Role in Putin's Money Trail</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_business_and_market.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-06-25T16:08:41Z</published><updated>2024-06-25T16:08:41Z</updated><id>b2f8eeaa-4018-4ec8-bcb5-d1ea89b0a18f</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_business_and_market.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/b2f8eeaa-4018-4ec8-bcb5-d1ea89b0a18f.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent news, bankers who assisted a close associate of Russian President Vladimir Putin in transferring money through Swiss bank accounts have lost their appeal. The individuals involved were found to have aided in the movement of funds, which has raised concerns about potential illicit activities. Meanwhile, India's Minister of Defense, Rajnath Singh, has assured the Chief Minister of Telangana, K. Chandrashekar Rao, that he will investigate the issue of land transfer in Secunderabad Cantt. This assurance comes after allegations of irregularities and corruption surrounding the transfer of land in the area. In the financial realm, the stock market has experienced a significant surge, with the Sensex index jumping 400 points and the Nifty index reaching the 23,600 level. Top gainers in this rally include Axis Bank, HDFC Bank, ICICI, and SBI. On the aviation front, Japan's low-cost carrier, Zipair, has announced plans to expand its fleet and routes. The CEO of Zipair has stated that the airline aims to add two aircraft and routes every year, highlighting its commitment to growth and development. Lastly, the Material Recycling Association is advocating for a reduction in the Goods and Services Tax (GST) rate on metal waste in order to boost the circular economy. The association believes that a lower tax rate would incentivize recycling and contribute to a more sustainable approach to waste management.
    </summary></entry></feed>