<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Tech</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml</id><updated>2024-09-18T16:09:01Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>File Rename Revolution: One-Click PowerShell Magic &amp; 3D Rig Adventures!</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-09-18T16:09:01Z</published><updated>2024-09-18T16:09:01Z</updated><id>cbcc0b76-f2cd-47cb-ac8d-56c2b204f175</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_tech.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/cbcc0b76-f2cd-47cb-ac8d-56c2b204f175.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent news, the tech world has been buzzing with innovative tools and projects that enhance productivity and creativity. One standout development is the introduction of a PowerShell script that allows users to rename multiple files in sequence with just one click on Windows systems. This feature is particularly beneficial for those who manage large volumes of files, streamlining the organization process and saving valuable time. Meanwhile, in the realm of entertainment and design, a detailed 3D rig of the Bracer Phoenix from the popular film "Pacific Rim" has been unveiled. This intricate model showcases the advanced technology used in film production and offers fans and creators alike a deeper appreciation for the artistry involved in bringing such colossal machines to life on screen.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;### New Tools, Products, or Projects:&lt;br&gt;1. **PowerShell File Renaming Script**: A user-friendly script that enables batch renaming of files in Windows, enhancing efficiency for file management tasks.&lt;br&gt;2. **3D Rig of Bracer Phoenix**: A sophisticated 3D model from "Pacific Rim," providing a resource for animators and designers to study and utilize in their projects.
    </summary></entry></feed>