<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-09-27T16:09:08Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Cloud Chronicles: Unpacking AWS Innovations and PostgreSQL Power Plays!</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-09-27T16:09:08Z</published><updated>2024-09-27T16:09:08Z</updated><id>b7098860-dd7d-4559-9eb0-22aec5742471</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/b7098860-dd7d-4559-9eb0-22aec5742471.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent developments within the tech world, Amazon Web Services (AWS) has made significant strides in enhancing its cloud offerings. PostgreSQL 17.0 is now available in the Amazon RDS Database preview environment, allowing users to leverage the latest features of this popular relational database. Additionally, Amazon FSx for Lustre has introduced new performance metrics and an enhanced monitoring dashboard, improving the user experience for high-performance computing workloads. AWS Lambda has expanded its capabilities by supporting SnapStart for Java functions in the AWS GovCloud (US) Regions, streamlining the deployment process for developers. For those looking to advance their careers in artificial intelligence, AWS Educate has launched a pathway to become an AWS Certified AI Practitioner. Furthermore, Amazon Kinesis Data Streams has announced support for Attribute-Based Access Control (ABAC), enhancing security and access management. In Europe, Amazon MemoryDB is now available in the AWS Spain region, broadening its global reach. The week also saw the introduction of Amazon EC2 X8g instances, Amazon Q generative SQL for Amazon Redshift, and an updated AWS SDK for Swift. Lastly, Amazon EKS and Amazon EKS Distro have upgraded their support to Kubernetes version 1.31, ensuring users have access to the latest container orchestration features.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;### New Tools, Products, and Projects:&lt;br&gt;1. **PostgreSQL 17.0** - Available in Amazon RDS Database preview environment.&lt;br&gt;2. **Amazon FSx for Lustre** - New performance metrics and enhanced monitoring dashboard.&lt;br&gt;3. **AWS Lambda** - Now supports SnapStart for Java functions in AWS GovCloud (US) Regions.&lt;br&gt;4. **AWS Educate** - Pathway to AWS Certified AI Practitioner.&lt;br&gt;5. **Amazon Kinesis Data Streams** - Support for Attribute-Based Access Control (ABAC).&lt;br&gt;6. **Amazon MemoryDB** - Now available in the AWS Europe (Spain) region.&lt;br&gt;7. **Amazon EC2 X8g Instances** - New instance type introduced.&lt;br&gt;8. **Amazon Q** - Generative SQL for Amazon Redshift.&lt;br&gt;9. **AWS SDK for Swift** - Updated version released.&lt;br&gt;10. **Amazon EKS and EKS Distro** - Support for Kubernetes version 1.31.
    </summary></entry></feed>