<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Tech</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml</id><updated>2024-05-18T16:06:39Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>"Unveiling the Literary Treasure Trove: Unraveling Words from Scanned Books with Python and OpenCV"</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-05-18T16:06:39Z</published><updated>2024-05-18T16:06:39Z</updated><id>53957333-eed5-4491-bf1b-2bfccc6d2c6f</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_tech.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/53957333-eed5-4491-bf1b-2bfccc6d2c6f.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of technology, a new tutorial has been released on extracting words from scanned books using Python and OpenCV. This step-by-step guide provides insights into the process of extracting text from scanned images, offering a valuable resource for researchers and developers. Meanwhile, OPPO Find X7 Ultra, a popular smartphone, has received a new software update. The update includes the addition of a 25-megapixel mode and support for Ultra HDR format photography, enhancing the camera capabilities of the device. This update brings exciting new features to OPPO users, allowing them to capture and view stunning high-resolution photos. Additionally, in the realm of programming, a comprehensive tutorial has been published on getting started with task scheduling and Cron jobs in Node.js with MongoDB. This tutorial serves as a useful guide for developers, providing them with the necessary knowledge and tools to efficiently schedule tasks and automate processes using Node.js and MongoDB. These advancements in technology and software offer innovative solutions and opportunities for users and developers alike.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Tools, Products, or Projects:&lt;br&gt;- Python and OpenCV Tutorial: This tutorial provides a step-by-step guide on extracting words from scanned books using Python and OpenCV. It offers valuable insights and techniques for researchers and developers working with scanned images.&lt;br&gt;- OPPO Find X7 Ultra Software Update: The latest software update for OPPO Find X7 Ultra introduces new features, including a 25-megapixel mode and support for Ultra HDR format photography. This update enhances the camera capabilities of the smartphone, allowing users to capture and view high-resolution photos.&lt;br&gt;- Node.js and MongoDB Task Scheduling Tutorial: A comprehensive tutorial has been published on getting started with task scheduling and Cron jobs in Node.js with MongoDB. This tutorial equips developers with the necessary knowledge and tools to efficiently automate processes and schedule tasks using Node.js and MongoDB.
    </summary></entry></feed>