<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-02-07T08:06:53Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>"The Future of Business Operations: Unveiling ERP and SCM Trends in 2024, Part 2"&lt;br&gt;"Breaking Down AWS Glue, Amazon Q, and CDK Migrate: A Weekly Recap - February 5th, 2024"&lt;br&gt;"Revolutionizing Data Management: Migrating Azure Data Explorer Cluster to Private Endpoints"&lt;br&gt;"Expanding Possibilities: 100 TB Storage Support for the FHIR Service Now Available"&lt;br&gt;"Seamless Integration: Mounting Azure Storage as a Local Share in App Service Linux with NFS Support"</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-02-07T08:06:53Z</published><updated>2024-02-07T08:06:53Z</updated><id>8e333bc1-514a-4bc7-89d5-fe0d46dd4170</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/8e333bc1-514a-4bc7-89d5-fe0d46dd4170.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of technology, there have been several developments and announcements that will shape the future. One of the key areas of focus is Enterprise Resource Planning (ERP) and Supply Chain Management (SCM). In 2024, we can expect significant advancements in these fields.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;AWS, the leading cloud computing platform, has introduced new features and tools that will enhance data integration and analysis. One of these tools is Amazon Glue, which now includes Amazon Q and Amazon PartyRock Hackathon. These additions will provide users with more efficient ways to manage and process their data.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another important development is the availability of migrating Virtual Network injected Azure Data Explorer Cluster to Private Endpoints. This announcement will enable businesses to securely transfer their data to private endpoints, ensuring better protection and control over their information.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Furthermore, the FHIR service, which is a standard for exchanging healthcare information electronically, now supports up to 100 TB of storage. This upgrade will allow healthcare organizations to store and manage a larger volume of patient data, leading to improved healthcare delivery and research.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In addition to these advancements, there is a new tool available for App Service Linux users. They can now mount Azure Storage as a local share using NFS (Network File System). This feature will provide a seamless integration between Azure Storage and App Service Linux, allowing for easier file management and access.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, the world of technology is constantly evolving, and these developments in ERP, SCM, and various tools and services demonstrate the ongoing efforts to improve data management, security, and efficiency. With these advancements, businesses and organizations can expect enhanced capabilities and better utilization of their resources.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Tools, Products, or Projects:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. Amazon Glue with Amazon Q and Amazon PartyRock Hackathon: These additions to Amazon Glue will provide users with more efficient ways to manage and process their data, enhancing data integration and analysis.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Migration of Virtual Network injected Azure Data Explorer Cluster to Private Endpoints: This new feature allows businesses to securely transfer their data to private endpoints, ensuring better protection and control over their information.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Increased storage capacity for the FHIR service: The FHIR service now supports up to 100 TB of storage, enabling healthcare organizations to store and manage a larger volume of patient data for improved healthcare delivery and research.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. Mounting Azure Storage as a local share in App Service Linux using NFS: App Service Linux users can now seamlessly integrate Azure Storage with their applications, allowing for easier file management and access.
    </summary></entry></feed>