<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-05-22T16:06:45Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>"The API Cache Chronicles: Unleashing the Power of Azure OpenAI Semantic Caching"&lt;br&gt;"Securing the Future: Exploring Azure Web Application Firewall Integration in Microsoft Copilot"&lt;br&gt;"AWS Weekly Roundup: IPv6 Load Balancers, Amazon S3 Pricing Updates, and More!"&lt;br&gt;"Gateway to Success: Embracing gRPC APIs with Azure API Management Self-hosted Gateway"</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-05-22T16:06:45Z</published><updated>2024-05-22T16:06:45Z</updated><id>3ff10f35-c0d4-4b9f-8b59-e940c0124dfc</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/3ff10f35-c0d4-4b9f-8b59-e940c0124dfc.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent news, there have been several developments in the technology world. One of the highlights is the public preview of Azure OpenAI Semantic Caching policy in Azure API Management. This new feature allows users to enhance the performance of their applications by leveraging AI-powered semantic caching. Additionally, Microsoft Copilot for Security now offers integration with Azure Web Application Firewall (WAF) in its public preview. This integration provides an added layer of security for web applications, ensuring protection against common threats. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In other news, Amazon Web Services (AWS) has made some updates and announcements. One of the notable updates is the introduction of IPv6 support for application load balancers. This enhancement allows applications to handle IPv6 traffic, enabling better connectivity and scalability. Furthermore, Amazon S3 pricing has been updated, providing customers with more flexibility and cost optimization options. Lastly, AWS has introduced Amazon EC2 Flex instances, which offer a new way to save costs by utilizing spare EC2 capacity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As for new tools, products, or projects, Azure API Management now offers GA support for gRPC APIs in its self-hosted gateway. This means that developers can now easily manage and expose gRPC APIs through Azure API Management, enabling seamless integration and scalability. This addition expands the capabilities of Azure API Management, providing more options for API management and integration.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, these recent developments showcase the continuous advancements in the technology industry, offering new features and enhancements to improve performance, security, and cost optimization for various applications and services.
    </summary></entry></feed>