<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-08-25T16:07:13Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>The AI Edge: Unleashing the Power of Amazon Bedrock, GKE, and Azure Phi Models</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-08-25T16:07:13Z</published><updated>2024-08-25T16:07:13Z</updated><id>4ff85748-d7e6-4b17-a69c-0df1a88e8309</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/4ff85748-d7e6-4b17-a69c-0df1a88e8309.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of technology, several developments have taken place recently. Amazon has introduced a new service called Bedrock, which offers select FMs (Framework Models) for batch inference at 50% of the on-demand inference price. This will provide cost-effective options for businesses utilizing AI models. Additionally, there is a choice between self-hosted GKE (Google Kubernetes Engine) and managed Vertex AI for hosting AI models, allowing organizations to select the most suitable option for their needs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Azure has also made advancements in the AI domain with the introduction of the Phi model, streamlined RAG (Retrieval-Augmented Generation), and custom generative AI models. These tools aim to enhance the capabilities of AI systems and provide more efficient and customized solutions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of infrastructure, Amazon Data Firehose is now available in the AWS Asia Pacific (Malaysia) region. This expansion allows businesses in that region to benefit from the data delivery service offered by Amazon. Furthermore, AWS Systems Manager has integrated with SAP console, enabling application-aware stop and start of SAP systems, enhancing the management and efficiency of SAP deployments.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;CloudFormation, a service for managing infrastructure as code, has introduced new features to simplify resource discovery and template review in the IaC (Infrastructure as Code) Generator. This will streamline the process of creating and managing infrastructure resources.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon Connect Contact Lens, a contact center analytics tool, now provides an audit trail for changes made to an agent's performance evaluation. This feature enhances transparency and accountability in contact center operations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon Q, a service for managing customer subscriptions, has introduced more detailed information about user subscriptions and associated resources. This will provide businesses with better insights into their customer base and subscription services.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, Amazon Route 53 Resolver Endpoints are now available in the Asia Pacific (Malaysia) region. This expansion improves the performance and reliability of DNS resolution in that region.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;These recent developments in the tech industry showcase the continuous efforts to enhance AI capabilities, expand infrastructure services, and improve customer experience across various platforms and regions.
    </summary></entry></feed>