<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Tech</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml</id><updated>2024-02-16T20:05:22Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>1. "Moss Magic: Unleashing Unreal Engine 5's Custom Moss Shader &amp; Burned Fire Decal"&lt;br&gt;2. "iOS in Europe: The End of Home Screen Web Apps Confirmed by Apple"&lt;br&gt;3. "LAN Legends: Mastering DNS and DHCP the Old-School Way"&lt;br&gt;4. "Unveiling Microsoft Graph Connectors: A Deep Dive into Search Relevance"&lt;br&gt;5. "iPaaS Unleashed: Maximizing Your Digital Transformation Potential"&lt;br&gt;6. "Inside Google Zurich: Exploring Projects and ML Opportunities"</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-02-16T20:05:22Z</published><updated>2024-02-16T20:05:22Z</updated><id>fa23b582-0b5b-4168-84b7-6b40eb0cb17d</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_tech.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/fa23b582-0b5b-4168-84b7-6b40eb0cb17d.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of technology, there have been some interesting developments recently. One notable news is the tutorial on creating a custom moss shader and burned fire decal in Unreal Engine 5. This tutorial provides insights into the process of designing realistic moss and fire effects in the popular game development engine.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In other news, Apple has confirmed that home screen web apps will no longer be functional on European iOS devices. This decision has raised concerns among users who heavily rely on web apps for various purposes. It remains to be seen how this change will impact the user experience and whether alternative solutions will be provided.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On a different note, an article discusses the traditional approach to managing DNS and DHCP for local area networks. The author emphasizes the effectiveness of this old-fashioned method and highlights its reliability. This serves as a reminder that sometimes sticking to proven techniques can yield better results than adopting newer, untested solutions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additionally, Microsoft Graph Connectors' search relevance is explored in a detailed analysis. The article delves into the inner workings of this feature, shedding light on how it enhances search results and improves user experience. It provides valuable insights for developers and organizations utilizing Microsoft Graph Connectors.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Furthermore, a thought-provoking piece encourages businesses to go beyond just implementing integration platform as a service (iPaaS) during their digital transformation. The article emphasizes the importance of maximizing the potential of iPaaS and leveraging it to its fullest extent. It offers practical tips and strategies to extract more value from digital transformation initiatives.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, it is worth mentioning Google Zurich. While the specific projects they are working on are not mentioned, Google Zurich is known for its contributions to various fields of technology. As for hiring in the field of machine learning, it is advisable to check Google's official job listings or reach out to their recruitment team for the most up-to-date information.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, these recent developments in the tech world highlight the continuous evolution of technology and the need for businesses and individuals to stay informed and adapt to changes.
    </summary></entry></feed>