<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Tech</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml</id><updated>2024-04-15T16:05:56Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>"Unraveling the Supply Chain Maze: DCD&gt;Talks with Martin Kelly of Kirby"</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-04-15T16:05:56Z</published><updated>2024-04-15T16:05:56Z</updated><id>b6a4ac33-83cd-4802-aec3-26a56ca21101</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_tech.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/b6a4ac33-83cd-4802-aec3-26a56ca21101.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent news, there have been talks with Martin Kelly, the representative from Kirby, regarding the challenges faced by supply chains. The discussion revolved around finding effective solutions to overcome these issues. Supply chain problems have become increasingly prevalent in various industries, causing disruptions and delays in the delivery of goods and services. Martin Kelly shed light on the strategies employed by Kirby to tackle these challenges, emphasizing the importance of collaboration and adaptability. By working closely with suppliers and implementing innovative approaches, Kirby has managed to mitigate the impact of supply chain issues and ensure a smooth flow of operations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In addition to the news, it is worth mentioning a valuable tip for developers working with Angular Signals. When utilizing the component life cycle hook "afterRender," it is advisable to avoid using the ".update()" operation. This cautionary advice stems from potential conflicts that may arise between the two functionalities. By refraining from employing the ".update()" operation in conjunction with "afterRender," developers can prevent any unintended consequences and ensure the seamless functioning of their applications. This tip serves as a helpful reminder for developers seeking to optimize their Angular Signal implementations and enhance the overall performance of their projects.
    </summary></entry></feed>