<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-03-30T16:04:59Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>1. "Tech Transitions: Navigating Azure's Retirement Roadmap"&lt;br&gt;2. "Redis Enterprise and Flash: AOF Persistence on Azure Cache's Final Countdown"&lt;br&gt;3. "APIOps: Streamlining Git Repository Migrations for Automated Deployments"&lt;br&gt;4. "Bid Farewell to Ubuntu 20.04 LTS: Retirement Notice for Batch Pools"&lt;br&gt;5. "Windows Server 2022 and k8s 1.34: March 2027 Retirement Announcement"&lt;br&gt;6. "Azure VM Retirement Alert: Saying Goodbye to Standard_NC Series"&lt;br&gt;7. "Data Factory Evolution: Embracing General Purpose for Better Performance"&lt;br&gt;8. "Audio API Evolution: From Long Audio to Batch Synthesis"&lt;br&gt;9. "Azure Maps: Navigating Retirement of Web SDK and Service Module"&lt;br&gt;10. "Azure API Management: Embrace Azure Monitor Dashboards Before Retirement"</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-03-30T16:04:59Z</published><updated>2024-03-30T16:04:59Z</updated><id>3110a982-3cc3-4985-92ca-2d01e9e020ac</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/3110a982-3cc3-4985-92ca-2d01e9e020ac.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of technology, several changes and retirements are taking place in various tools, products, and projects. Firstly, the Every-write AOF persistence on Azure Cache for Redis Enterprise and Enterprise Flash will be retired on 1 April 2025. This indicates a shift in the storage options available for these platforms. Additionally, the support for Basic and Standard A-series VM families in Batch pools will be retired on 31 August 2024, prompting users to explore alternative options.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another significant change is the migration of Git Repositories to automated deployments with APIOps. Users are encouraged to complete this migration by 15 March 2025, which will streamline the deployment process and enhance efficiency. Furthermore, the support for Ubuntu 20.04 LTS in Batch pools will be retired on 23 April 2025, signaling the need for users to update their systems accordingly.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the future, Windows Server 2022 will retire with k8s 1.34 in March 2027, indicating a shift towards newer versions and technologies. Similarly, Standard_NC6s_v3, Standard_NC12s_v3, and Standard_NC24s_v3 Azure virtual machines will be retired on September 30, 2025, prompting users to consider alternative virtual machine options.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In Azure Data Factory, the retirement of Memory Optimized Data Flows is announced, with users advised to utilize General Purpose for better performance at a lower price. This change aims to optimize data processing and cost-effectiveness. Additionally, the Long Audio API will be retired on 31 March 2027, urging users to migrate to the new batch synthesis API for audio-related tasks.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Furthermore, the Azure Maps Web SDK Map Control version 2.0.x and Azure Maps Service Module will be retired on 30 September 2026. Users are advised to update their map-related applications to ensure compatibility and access to the latest features. Lastly, users of Azure API Management are encouraged to begin using Azure Monitor-based dashboards before the built-in analytics dashboards are retired on 15 March 2027. This transition will provide users with more comprehensive monitoring and analytics capabilities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, the provided news does not mention any specific additions.
    </summary></entry></feed>