<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Business and Market</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_business_and_market.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_business_and_market.xml</id><updated>2024-06-03T16:08:32Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>The Inflation Battle: Turkey's Struggle to Tame the Beast</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_business_and_market.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-06-03T16:08:32Z</published><updated>2024-06-03T16:08:32Z</updated><id>e6f60ccf-25a9-4b04-9f71-06805da0c414</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_business_and_market.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/e6f60ccf-25a9-4b04-9f71-06805da0c414.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world news, Turkey is facing a severe inflation crisis, with the inflation rate expected to reach a peak close to 75%. This economic situation is causing significant challenges for the country and its citizens. Meanwhile, former US President Donald Trump, in an attempt to appeal to young voters, has joined the popular social media platform TikTok, despite previously attempting to ban it. This move is seen as a strategic political move to connect with a younger demographic. In the global health sector, Axis Securities has initiated coverage with a buy rating, highlighting the highest-standard care and high complexity work involved. In India, both Amul and Mother Dairy have increased the prices of milk by Rs 2 per litre, citing various factors for the hike. Air India has issued new guidelines after a 30-hour flight delay, following a notice from the Directorate General of Civil Aviation (DGCA). In the corporate world, Mrs. Bectors' fourth-quarter results have been reviewed by ICICI Securities, with the consensus being that it is more of the same, which is viewed positively. A PMLA court has stated that the failure to arrest Vijay Mallya, Nirav Modi, and Mehul Choksi on time enabled them to flee the country, highlighting the need for improved law enforcement. Heidelberg Cement's fourth-quarter review shows results below expectations, leading Axis Securities to maintain a hold rating. On the technology front, AMD has announced the development of future AI chips, which will accelerate the rollout of new models. Lastly, Axis Securities has reviewed the fourth-quarter results of the cement industry, noting that higher volume and easing cost pressure have driven Ebitda growth.
    </summary></entry></feed>