<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-04-11T16:05:40Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>1. "Unlocking the Cloud: Extensible Key Management and Azure Key Vault"&lt;br&gt;2. "From Beginner to Pro: A Journey of Cloud and AI Skills at AWS Skills Center"&lt;br&gt;3. "Defending the Cloud: Azure Database for MySQL with Defender for Cloud"&lt;br&gt;4. "Efficiency Unleashed: Introducing ML Productivity Goodput"&lt;br&gt;5. "Preserving Data: Long-term Retention for Azure Database for MySQL"&lt;br&gt;6. "AWS Weekly Recap: EC2 G6 Instances, Mistral Large on Amazon Bedrock, and Deadline Cloud"&lt;br&gt;7. "Securing Connections: VPN with Azure Managed Instance for Apache Cassandra"&lt;br&gt;8. "Empowering Savings: New RBAC Roles for Azure Savings Plan for Compute"&lt;br&gt;9. "Networking Made Easy: Azure Database for PostgreSQL with Azure Private Link"</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-04-11T16:05:40Z</published><updated>2024-04-11T16:05:40Z</updated><id>1f14fe1f-9527-4331-9e27-7beddae2ec04</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/1f14fe1f-9527-4331-9e27-7beddae2ec04.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of technology, several significant developments have taken place recently. Firstly, Azure Key Vault for SQL Server on Linux has reached general availability, allowing for extensible key management. This feature provides enhanced security and control for SQL Server on Linux users. Additionally, a learner at the AWS Skills Center shared his success story of growing his cloud and AI skills, highlighting the valuable resources and training available at the center.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another noteworthy update is the general availability of Defender for Cloud, which now supports Azure Database for MySQL - Flexible Server. This integration enhances the security of MySQL databases on Azure, ensuring protection against potential threats. Furthermore, Azure Database for MySQL - Flexible Server has introduced long-term retention in its public preview, enabling users to store data for extended periods.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the realm of AWS, various advancements have been made. Amazon EC2 G6 instances, Mistral Large on Amazon Bedrock, and AWS Deadline Cloud are among the new tools and services introduced. These offerings aim to enhance performance, scalability, and efficiency for AWS users.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moreover, Azure Managed Instance for Apache Cassandra now offers a virtual private network (VPN) feature, providing secure and private communication between instances. This development ensures the protection of sensitive data and enhances overall network security.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additionally, Azure savings plan for compute has introduced new RBAC roles, expanding the range of options available to users. These roles enable more granular control and management of Azure savings plans.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, Azure Database for PostgreSQL - Flexible Server has achieved general availability for networking with Azure Private Link. This feature allows for secure and private communication between PostgreSQL instances and other Azure resources, enhancing data protection and network security.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, these recent developments in the technology landscape have brought about enhanced security, improved efficiency, and expanded capabilities for users across various platforms and services.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Tools, Products, or Projects:&lt;br&gt;- Azure Key Vault for SQL Server on Linux: Provides extensible key management for enhanced security.&lt;br&gt;- AWS Skills Center: Offers valuable resources and training for learners to develop cloud and AI skills.&lt;br&gt;- Defender for Cloud: Supports Azure Database for MySQL - Flexible Server, ensuring database security.&lt;br&gt;- Long-term retention for Azure Database for MySQL - Flexible Server: Allows for extended data storage.&lt;br&gt;- Amazon EC2 G6 instances: Enhances performance and scalability on AWS.&lt;br&gt;- Mistral Large on Amazon Bedrock: A new tool for improved efficiency on AWS.&lt;br&gt;- AWS Deadline Cloud: A service aimed at optimizing performance and productivity on AWS.&lt;br&gt;- Virtual private network (VPN) with Azure Managed Instance for Apache Cassandra: Ensures secure communication between instances.&lt;br&gt;- New RBAC roles for Azure savings plan for compute: Provides more granular control and management options.&lt;br&gt;- Azure Database for PostgreSQL - Flexible Server networking with Azure Private Link: Enhances data protection and network security.
    </summary></entry></feed>