<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-07-27T16:05:08Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Cloud Chronicles: Unleashing Digital Transformation with AWS Training and Azure AI Updates</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-07-27T16:05:08Z</published><updated>2024-07-27T16:05:08Z</updated><id>3639b4b1-4cf0-4911-bb61-e784fd59a315</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/3639b4b1-4cf0-4911-bb61-e784fd59a315.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of technology, there have been several significant developments. One such development is the announcement of leveraging AWS Training to enable workforce in achieving digital transformation. This training program aims to equip individuals with the necessary skills and knowledge to adapt to the rapidly changing digital landscape.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additionally, Azure AI has introduced Phi-3 fine-tuning and new generative AI models, among other updates. These advancements empower organizations to customize and scale their AI applications, allowing them to harness the full potential of artificial intelligence.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Furthermore, Amazon has expanded its EC2 D3en instances to the Asia Pacific (Jakarta) region. This expansion provides businesses in that region with access to high-performance computing resources, enabling them to meet their growing computational needs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of data transfer, AWS DataSync has expanded its support for agentless cross-region data transfers. This expansion now includes opt-in regions, allowing organizations to seamlessly transfer data between different regions without the need for agents.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, in the realm of Amazon Bedrock, an exciting announcement has been made regarding the introduction of Llama 3.1 405B, 70B, and 8B models from Meta. These models are expected to enhance the capabilities of Amazon Bedrock, providing users with more advanced and efficient tools for their projects.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, these developments highlight the continuous efforts in the tech industry to improve and innovate, ultimately driving digital transformation and empowering organizations worldwide.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Tools, Products, or Projects:&lt;br&gt;- AWS Training for workforce digital transformation&lt;br&gt;- Azure AI updates including Phi-3 fine-tuning and new generative AI models&lt;br&gt;- Availability of Amazon EC2 D3en instances in Asia Pacific (Jakarta) region&lt;br&gt;- Expanded support for agentless cross-region data transfers in AWS DataSync&lt;br&gt;- Introduction of Llama 3.1 405B, 70B, and 8B models in Amazon Bedrock from Meta.
    </summary></entry></feed>