<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-09-08T16:08:15Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>The Oracle's Multitenant Journey: Unveiling Amazon RDS and its Powerful OEM and OLS Options</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-09-08T16:08:15Z</published><updated>2024-09-08T16:08:15Z</updated><id>70fce810-f855-469b-ad2f-7ea6288155b0</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/70fce810-f855-469b-ad2f-7ea6288155b0.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of technology, there have been some exciting developments recently. Amazon RDS for Oracle has made significant advancements by introducing support for OEM (Oracle Enterprise Manager) and OLS (Oracle Label Security) options. This enhancement allows users to leverage the Multitenant configuration, providing greater flexibility and efficiency in managing their Oracle databases on the Amazon RDS platform.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moving on to another innovation, the Gerald R. Ford International Airport has implemented ChromeOS powered digital signage to enhance the passenger experience. These digital signages serve as guides, providing directions and important information to travelers. With the help of ChromeOS, the airport can easily update and manage the content displayed on these signages, ensuring accurate and real-time information for passengers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the realm of customer service, Amazon Connect Contact Lens has introduced new features to automate agent performance evaluations. Contact Lens, an AI-powered analytics tool, now supports additional ways to evaluate and assess the performance of customer service agents. This automation not only saves time but also provides valuable insights into agent-customer interactions, enabling businesses to improve their customer service quality and efficiency.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, there have been several noteworthy developments. One such example is the introduction of Amazon RDS for Oracle's support for OEM and OLS options with Multitenant configuration. This advancement empowers users to efficiently manage their Oracle databases on the Amazon RDS platform, enhancing their overall database management experience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additionally, the implementation of ChromeOS powered digital signage at the Gerald R. Ford International Airport showcases the potential of technology in improving the passenger experience. These digital signages serve as interactive guides, providing travelers with accurate and real-time information, ensuring a smooth and hassle-free journey.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Furthermore, the new features added to Amazon Connect Contact Lens highlight the continuous efforts to enhance customer service. With the ability to automate agent performance evaluations, businesses can gain valuable insights into customer interactions, enabling them to optimize their customer service operations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, these recent developments in technology demonstrate the ongoing advancements and innovations that are shaping the world, making processes more efficient, and improving user experiences.
    </summary></entry></feed>