<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Tech</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml</id><updated>2024-02-19T20:05:41Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>1. "Powering Up: Exploring Centiel's Versatile UPS Line"&lt;br&gt;2. "3D Adventures: Recreating the DC Joker Comic Book Cover"&lt;br&gt;3. "Unlocking Unity's Shaders: Insights from 'The Unity Shaders Bible' Author"&lt;br&gt;4. "Inside MailChimp MLE: A Look at the Future in 2024"&lt;br&gt;5. "The Mystery of Descending Satellites: Earth's Unpredictable Encounters"&lt;br&gt;6. "Don't Miss Out: Grab a Lifetime Babbel Subscription for $150"&lt;br&gt;7. "Mastering Time: Triggering Events in OutSystems"&lt;br&gt;8. "Tech Companies on President's Day: Holiday or Not?"</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-02-19T20:05:41Z</published><updated>2024-02-19T20:05:41Z</updated><id>e19a0201-d88a-4413-a84c-d766819343ed</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_tech.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/e19a0201-d88a-4413-a84c-d766819343ed.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world today, Centiel has announced the expansion of its StratusPower product line, offering a versatile range of uninterruptible power supply (UPS) solutions. These UPS systems now range from 10 kW to an impressive 3.75 MW, providing businesses with a wide range of options to meet their power backup needs. This expansion showcases Centiel's commitment to providing reliable and scalable power solutions for various industries.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the realm of digital art, there has been an exciting development as a talented artist has recreated the iconic DC Joker comic book cover in 3D using Blender and ZBrush. This impressive feat demonstrates the power of modern digital tools in bringing imagination to life and pushing the boundaries of artistic expression.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For those interested in technical art and game development, the author of "The Unity Shaders Bible" shares insights on utilizing Unity for technical art. This book serves as a valuable resource for artists and developers looking to enhance their skills and create visually stunning experiences within the Unity game engine.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the tech industry, there is speculation about the future of MailChimp MLE (Machine Learning Engineer) positions. The question arises whether it will be a desirable career path in 2024. This discussion highlights the evolving nature of technology and the importance of staying up-to-date with the latest trends and skills in the field.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In other news, there is uncertainty surrounding the exact timing of a descending satellite's impact on Earth this week. The unpredictability of such events raises questions about our ability to accurately predict and prepare for potential space debris hazards.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For language enthusiasts, there is a limited-time offer to get a lifetime subscription to Babbel, a popular language learning platform, for only $150. This sale presents an excellent opportunity for individuals to immerse themselves in a new language and expand their linguistic abilities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, for developers using OutSystems, a guide on how to trigger events at pre-defined time intervals has been released. This valuable resource provides insights into effectively managing time-based events within the OutSystems platform, enhancing productivity and efficiency in application development.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Tools, Products, or Projects:&lt;br&gt;- Centiel's expanded StratusPower UPS product line, offering versatile power backup solutions.&lt;br&gt;- The recreation of the DC Joker comic book cover in 3D using Blender and ZBrush.&lt;br&gt;- "The Unity Shaders Bible," a comprehensive guide for utilizing Unity for technical art.&lt;br&gt;- Speculation on the future of MailChimp MLE positions in 2024.&lt;br&gt;- Uncertainty surrounding the timing of a descending satellite's impact on Earth.&lt;br&gt;- A one-day sale offering a lifetime subscription to Babbel language learning platform.&lt;br&gt;- A guide on triggering events at pre-defined time intervals in OutSystems.
    </summary></entry></feed>