<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-06-13T16:07:13Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Tech Talk: Boosting Search Retrieval Rates and AI Apps with Cloud SQL and Vector Support</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-06-13T16:07:13Z</published><updated>2024-06-13T16:07:13Z</updated><id>778d0a9e-0849-4e29-93cd-fa6ed098cdcd</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/778d0a9e-0849-4e29-93cd-fa6ed098cdcd.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent news, Lightricks has made significant advancements in search retrieval rates by implementing vector support in Cloud SQL. This development has resulted in a remarkable 40% increase in search retrieval rates, enhancing the overall user experience. Additionally, AWS has introduced several new features and services, including the introduction of Amazon API Gateway and Amazon Q. These additions aim to provide users with more efficient and streamlined experiences within the AWS ecosystem. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Furthermore, LangChain has unveiled its new tool, VectorStore, which enables the rapid development of AI applications. By utilizing VectorStore in Cloud SQL for PostgreSQL, developers can build powerful AI apps quickly and efficiently. In another exciting development, Google has been recognized as a Leader in the Cybersecurity Incident Response Services Forrester Wave, Q2 2024. This recognition highlights Google's commitment to providing top-notch cybersecurity services and solutions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additionally, a new Privileged Access Manager has been introduced, allowing users to transition from always-on privileges to on-demand access. This tool enhances security measures by providing more controlled and restricted access to privileged accounts. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the realm of cloud technology, Amazon Web Services (AWS) has released a guide on deploying WAF (Web Application Firewall) with Centralized Logging using OpenSearch Light Engine. This guide aims to help users reduce the monitoring costs associated with Amazon WAF logs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, Veo, a company specializing in actionable insights, has partnered with Google Cloud to leverage its powerful infrastructure. By utilizing Google Cloud, Veo can accelerate the generation of actionable insights, enabling businesses to make informed decisions based on data-driven analysis.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For those interested in the intersection of AI and cybersecurity, Google Cloud is hosting the latest Google Cloud Security Talks. These talks provide valuable insights into the integration of AI technologies in the field of cybersecurity, offering a glimpse into the future of digital defense.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, these recent developments showcase the continuous advancements in cloud technology, AI applications, cybersecurity, and access management. These tools, products, and projects aim to enhance user experiences, improve security measures, and provide innovative solutions for businesses and individuals alike.
    </summary></entry></feed>