<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-04-20T16:04:54Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>"The Cloud Chronicles: Navigating Azure's Evolution and Retirement Dates"</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-04-20T16:04:54Z</published><updated>2024-04-20T16:04:54Z</updated><id>62f56e6f-d5bc-48ac-a578-b756efb2f05f</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/62f56e6f-d5bc-48ac-a578-b756efb2f05f.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent news, several changes and updates have been announced in the world of technology. Firstly, Azure Site Recovery has introduced a Public Preview of Disaster Recovery for Shared Disks, allowing users to enhance their data protection and recovery capabilities. However, it is important to note that the Cloud Services (classic) deployment model will be retiring on 31 August 2024, along with five Azure classic networking services. Additionally, the retirement of .Net Standard user-defined functions for Azure Stream Analytics is scheduled for 30 September 2024. Azure Advisor, a valuable tool for optimizing cloud resources, will no longer display aggregated potential yearly savings starting from 30 September 2024. Furthermore, the support for Azure Notification Hubs' Firebase Cloud Messaging (FCM) legacy API will be deprecated by July 2024.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the brighter side, there are some exciting new tools and products being introduced. The Bulk delete operation for the FHIR service in Azure Health Data Services has reached general availability, providing users with a convenient way to manage and delete large amounts of data. Additionally, Sweden Central now offers the availability of HBv4-series and HX-series VMs, expanding the range of virtual machine options for users in that region.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, it is important to be aware that App Service Environment version 1 and version 2 will be retired on 31 August 2024. Users should plan accordingly and consider migrating to newer versions or alternative solutions to ensure uninterrupted service.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, these updates and changes reflect the continuous evolution and improvement of technology, providing users with new features and options while also requiring them to adapt to retiring services and versions.
    </summary></entry></feed>