<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Tech</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.fun/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.fun/podcast/trend_tech.xml</id><updated>2024-12-12T16:08:43Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Blender &amp; Beyond: Crafting Lush Landscapes and Navigating Choices in Assassin's Creed</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.fun/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-12-12T16:08:43Z</published><updated>2024-12-12T16:08:43Z</updated><id>b5670f02-85d6-476b-8c1a-329cf7ed7aa2</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.fun/cover/trend_tech.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/b5670f02-85d6-476b-8c1a-329cf7ed7aa2.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent news, the world of 3D design and gaming has seen exciting developments. A new add-on for Blender, a popular open-source 3D creation suite, has been released, allowing artists to easily add stylized grass to their scenes. This tool aims to enhance the visual appeal of 3D environments, making it simpler for creators to achieve lush, vibrant landscapes without extensive manual work. Meanwhile, in the gaming realm, the latest installment of the Assassin's Creed franchise, titled "Assassin's Creed Shadows," has introduced a Canon Mode. This innovative feature caters to players who prefer not to make difficult choices in narrative-driven games, allowing them to experience the story without the pressure of decision-making. These advancements reflect the ongoing evolution of creative tools and gaming experiences, catering to the diverse preferences of artists and gamers alike.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;### New Tools, Products, or Projects:&lt;br&gt;1. **Blender Add-On for Stylized Grass**: A new add-on designed for Blender that simplifies the process of adding realistic grass to 3D scenes, enhancing the overall aesthetic of digital environments.&lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt;2. **Assassin's Creed Shadows - Canon Mode**: A new gameplay feature in the Assassin's Creed series that allows players to experience the narrative without making choices, providing a more streamlined storytelling experience for those who prefer a guided path.
    </summary></entry></feed>