<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-03-24T16:06:13Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Tech Talk: Navigating Azure's Retirement Roadmap</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-03-24T16:06:13Z</published><updated>2024-03-24T16:06:13Z</updated><id>bf96a809-bdd1-4ec4-95dc-5640e54b0f99</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/bf96a809-bdd1-4ec4-95dc-5640e54b0f99.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent news, several important announcements have been made regarding various Azure products and services. Firstly, it has been announced that the Azure Maps Creator Feature State Service Versions will be retired on 31 March 2025. This retirement will affect the functionality of Azure Maps Creator, so users are advised to take necessary actions accordingly. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additionally, Simplified node communication Batch pools without public IP addresses will also be retired on 30 September 2025. This change will impact the default internet outbound access for these batch pools, and users should make the required adjustments before the specified date.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Furthermore, the support for Connector for AWS in Cost Management will come to an end on 31 March 2025. Users relying on this connector are encouraged to explore alternative solutions to ensure uninterrupted cost management.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another retirement announcement is regarding the support for .NET 7, which will end on 14 May 2024. Users are advised to upgrade their Azure Functions resources to .NET 8 to continue receiving support and benefits.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moreover, the Azure HDInsight 4.0 version will be retired on 31 March 2025. Users are recommended to migrate their HDInsight clusters to version 5.1 to avoid any disruptions in their operations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of tools and projects, it is recommended to update to using Grafana version 10 for Azure Managed Grafana. This update will ensure continued support and access to the latest features and improvements.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additionally, some compliance features in Microsoft Defender for Cloud will be retired on September 30, 2025. Users should stay informed about these changes and make any necessary adjustments to their compliance strategies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, the Azure Maps Native SDK for Android and iOS will be retired on 31 March 2025. Users are advised to transition to using the Azure Maps Web SDK in a web view to continue utilizing Azure Maps functionality seamlessly.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, it is important to upgrade App Service apps to Node 20 LTS by 30 April 2025. This upgrade will ensure compatibility and access to the latest features and enhancements.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;These announcements highlight the need for users to stay updated with the retirement dates and take appropriate actions to ensure a smooth transition and uninterrupted access to Azure services.
    </summary></entry></feed>