<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-03-03T16:04:42Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>"The Encryption Evolution: Securing Premium SSD v2 and Ultra Disks Across the Globe"&lt;br&gt;"AI Unleashed: Exploring the Potential of Generative AI with BigQuery and Vertex AI"&lt;br&gt;"Revolutionizing Network Security: Public Preview of Internet Inbound for Virtual WAN Hubs"&lt;br&gt;"Farewell to the Past: Cloud Services (classic) Deployment Model Bids Adieu"&lt;br&gt;"Empowering Gen AI: Unleashing the Potential of Google Cloud Databases"</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-03-03T16:04:42Z</published><updated>2024-03-03T16:04:42Z</updated><id>9da5abd0-5b14-4a73-8beb-57f9949ecdfe</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/9da5abd0-5b14-4a73-8beb-57f9949ecdfe.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent news, it has been announced that the General Availability of Encryption at host for Premium SSD v2 and Ultra Disks is now available in more regions. This development allows users to enhance the security of their data by encrypting it at the host level, providing an extra layer of protection. Additionally, Google Cloud is introducing the power of generative AI with BigQuery and Vertex AI. This integration enables users to leverage the capabilities of generative AI to unlock new insights and drive innovation in their businesses. In another exciting update, the public preview of Internet inbound for Network Virtual Appliances in Virtual WAN Hubs has been launched. This feature allows users to establish inbound internet connectivity for their Network Virtual Appliances, enhancing their networking capabilities. Furthermore, it has been announced that the Cloud Services (classic) deployment model will be retiring on 31 August 2024. Users are encouraged to transition to newer deployment models to ensure continued support and access to the latest features. Lastly, Google Cloud databases are now equipped with new capabilities to power gen AI applications. These enhancements enable users to leverage the full potential of gen AI by utilizing the advanced capabilities of Google Cloud databases. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, Google Cloud continues to innovate and provide cutting-edge solutions. The introduction of Encryption at host for Premium SSD v2 and Ultra Disks in more regions showcases Google Cloud's commitment to data security and privacy. The integration of generative AI with BigQuery and Vertex AI opens up new possibilities for businesses to harness the power of AI and drive meaningful insights. The public preview of Internet inbound for Network Virtual Appliances in Virtual WAN Hubs expands the networking capabilities of users, allowing for enhanced connectivity. Additionally, the retirement of the Cloud Services (classic) deployment model signifies Google Cloud's focus on newer and more efficient deployment models. Lastly, the new capabilities of Google Cloud databases further empower users to leverage gen AI applications and unlock the full potential of their data. These developments highlight Google Cloud's dedication to providing innovative tools and solutions to meet the evolving needs of businesses.
    </summary></entry></feed>