<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-06-14T16:06:41Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>The Secure AI Revolution: Exploring the Intersection of Cybersecurity and Artificial Intelligence</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-06-14T16:06:41Z</published><updated>2024-06-14T16:06:41Z</updated><id>3610d0d1-d323-4d74-8492-9bb55823cac5</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/3610d0d1-d323-4d74-8492-9bb55823cac5.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the latest news, Google Cloud Security Talks are focusing on the intersection of AI and cybersecurity. This highlights the growing importance of utilizing artificial intelligence in protecting against cyber threats. Additionally, Google has been recognized as a Leader in the Cybersecurity Incident Response Services Forrester Wave, Q2 2024. This recognition showcases Google's expertise and effectiveness in responding to cybersecurity incidents.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Furthermore, there is a new tool called Privileged Access Manager that allows users to move from always-on privileges to on-demand access. This tool enhances security by granting access only when necessary, reducing the risk of unauthorized access and potential breaches.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In other news, AWS has introduced several new tools and products. One of them is Amazon API Gateway, which provides a fully managed service for creating, deploying, and managing APIs at scale. Another new addition is Amazon Q, a service that enables developers to build quantum applications using quantum circuits, simulators, and hardware.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moreover, LangChain VectorStore in Cloud SQL for PostgreSQL is now available, allowing developers to build generative AI applications quickly. This tool provides a powerful and efficient way to store and retrieve vectors, enabling faster development and deployment of AI applications.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, Lightricks, a company specializing in image and video editing, has improved its search retrieval rates by 40% with the help of vector support in Cloud SQL. This enhancement allows for more accurate and efficient retrieval of search results, enhancing the user experience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, these developments in the world of technology highlight the increasing focus on AI and cybersecurity, as well as the continuous innovation in cloud services and tools to empower developers and businesses.
    </summary></entry></feed>