<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Tech</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml</id><updated>2024-06-03T16:08:06Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Shein's Journey to the London Stock Exchange: Inside the Fashion Empire</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-06-03T16:08:06Z</published><updated>2024-06-03T16:08:06Z</updated><id>619ea6b8-1d24-4bcc-8e6b-626798d4d0ef</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_tech.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/619ea6b8-1d24-4bcc-8e6b-626798d4d0ef.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world news, Shein, a popular online fashion retailer, is reportedly planning to file a prospectus to the London Stock Exchange later this month. This move indicates the company's intention to go public and expand its presence in the global market. Meanwhile, Dish, a leading provider of satellite television services, is offering an ultimate basketball viewing experience for fans. With advanced features and high-quality broadcasts, Dish aims to enhance the enjoyment of basketball enthusiasts. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the technology sector, Microsoft has introduced new features for its Microsoft 365 suite. These include an enhanced version control system and improved backup capabilities for scaled storage management. These updates aim to provide users with better control and security over their data. Additionally, AMD, a prominent semiconductor company, has announced the launch of new AI chips. This development comes as competition intensifies with industry giants Nvidia and Intel. The new AI chips from AMD are expected to offer improved performance and efficiency in artificial intelligence applications.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the software development front, an individual shares their experience of creating a RestAPI using AWS Lambda and API Gateway. These Amazon Web Services tools enable developers to build and deploy scalable and serverless applications with ease. Finally, Qualcomm, a leading chip manufacturer, is looking to target all form factors with its System-on-Chips (SoCs) that power Copilot+ PCs. This indicates Qualcomm's ambition to provide powerful and versatile chips for various computing devices.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In summary, Shein's plan to file a prospectus, Dish's focus on enhancing the basketball viewing experience, Microsoft's updates to its Microsoft 365 suite, AMD's announcement of new AI chips, the use of AWS Lambda and API Gateway for RestAPI creation, and Qualcomm's aim to target all form factors with its SoCs are the notable happenings in the world.
    </summary></entry></feed>