<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-02-29T16:06:43Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>"The Cosmos Connection: Unleashing the Power of Azure SDKs for Azure Cosmos DB with PostgreSQL"&lt;br&gt;"PostgreSQL Powerhouse: Exploring the Latest Minor Versions Supported by Azure Database for PostgreSQL - Flexible Server"&lt;br&gt;"Cosmic Command: Mastering Azure CLI for Azure Cosmos DB with PostgreSQL"&lt;br&gt;"Virtual Voyage: Navigating the Public Preview of Internet Inbound for Network Virtual Appliances in Virtual WAN Hubs"</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-02-29T16:06:43Z</published><updated>2024-02-29T16:06:43Z</updated><id>31628f5d-43ae-441a-a5e3-3bae71f7ce7b</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/31628f5d-43ae-441a-a5e3-3bae71f7ce7b.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent news, there have been several developments in the tech world. Firstly, it has been announced that Azure SDKs now support Azure Cosmos DB for PostgreSQL, which is great news for developers using this database management system. This general availability of the SDKs will provide enhanced functionality and ease of use for those working with Azure Cosmos DB.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additionally, Azure Database for PostgreSQL - Flexible Server now supports the latest minor versions of PostgreSQL. This general availability update ensures that users can take advantage of the most up-to-date features and improvements in their PostgreSQL deployments on Azure.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Furthermore, Azure CLI now offers support for Azure Cosmos DB for PostgreSQL. This means that developers can utilize the command-line interface to manage and interact with their Azure Cosmos DB instances, providing a more efficient and streamlined experience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In other exciting news, there is a public preview of internet inbound for Network Virtual Appliances in Virtual WAN Hubs. This development allows for greater flexibility and control over network traffic in virtual WAN environments. With this feature, users can now direct inbound internet traffic to specific network virtual appliances within their virtual WAN hubs, enabling more secure and efficient network management.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, the aforementioned updates highlight the continuous improvement and expansion of Azure's offerings. The support for Azure Cosmos DB for PostgreSQL through Azure SDKs and Azure CLI demonstrates Microsoft's commitment to providing developers with robust and user-friendly tools for database management. Additionally, the introduction of internet inbound for Network Virtual Appliances in Virtual WAN Hubs showcases Azure's dedication to enhancing network capabilities and security in virtual environments. These advancements contribute to the overall growth and innovation in the tech industry.
    </summary></entry></feed>