<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Tech</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml</id><updated>2024-05-16T16:07:05Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>"Caching the Way: Unleashing the Power of Server-side Cache for YugabyteDB Sequences"&lt;br&gt;"Breaking the Mold: Navigating Nspgl's 'DISCARD SEQUENCES' with YugabyteDB Server-side Cache"&lt;br&gt;"The Cache Chronicles: Exploring the Workaround for Nspgl's 'DISCARD SEQUENCES' in YugabyteDB"&lt;br&gt;"Sequences Unleashed: Tackling Nspgl's 'DISCARD SEQUENCES' with YugabyteDB's Server-side Cache"&lt;br&gt;"From Photoshop to Pho-Stop: Adobe's Stance on 'Photoshop' as a Verb or Noun"&lt;br&gt;"The Language of Design: Adobe's Disapproval of 'Photoshop' as a Verb or Noun"&lt;br&gt;"Unveiling Adobe's Verbal Veto: The Controversy Surrounding 'Photoshop' as a Verb or Noun"&lt;br&gt;"Animating the React Native Way: Crafting Play/Pause Controls with Lottie in React Native"&lt;br&gt;"Unlocking Animation Magic: Building Play/Pause Controls with Lottie in React Native"&lt;br&gt;"Lottie and React Native: A Dynamic Duo for Play/Pause Controls and Animation"</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-05-16T16:07:05Z</published><updated>2024-05-16T16:07:05Z</updated><id>fbaafc92-6103-488d-88ec-5bb71ffb301a</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_tech.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/fbaafc92-6103-488d-88ec-5bb71ffb301a.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent news, a new server-side cache has been developed for YugabyteDB sequences in order to address the issue of Nspgl's "DISCARD SEQUENCES" command. This cache serves as a workaround for the problem, providing a more efficient and reliable solution. YugabyteDB, a distributed SQL database, can now benefit from this server-side cache to enhance its performance and ensure the seamless functioning of sequences.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In another development, Adobe has expressed its disapproval of the use of the term "Photoshop" as a verb or noun. The company, known for its popular image editing software, believes that the term should only be used to refer to their product and not as a generic term for any photo editing action. This stance aims to protect the brand and maintain its distinct identity in the market.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Furthermore, a fascinating project called React Native Animation has emerged, focusing on building Play/Pause controls with Lottie in React Native. Lottie is a library that allows developers to add high-quality animations to their applications. With React Native Animation, developers can now create interactive and visually appealing Play/Pause controls using Lottie's capabilities. This project opens up new possibilities for creating engaging user interfaces and enhancing the overall user experience in React Native applications.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the realm of technology, these developments showcase the continuous innovation and problem-solving efforts within the industry. The server-side cache for YugabyteDB sequences addresses a specific issue, improving the performance of the distributed SQL database. Meanwhile, Adobe's disapproval of the use of "Photoshop" as a generic term highlights the importance of brand protection and maintaining distinct identities. Lastly, the React Native Animation project introduces exciting possibilities for creating captivating user interfaces using Lottie in React Native applications. These advancements demonstrate the ever-evolving nature of technology and its impact on various aspects of our lives.
    </summary></entry></feed>