<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-02-27T16:07:22Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>"The Tech Edge: Exploring Azure's Latest Innovations in Protocols, API Management, and AI Coding Assistance"</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-02-27T16:07:22Z</published><updated>2024-02-27T16:07:22Z</updated><id>94720729-3cec-4aa7-b45b-133892548b03</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/94720729-3cec-4aa7-b45b-133892548b03.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of technology, some exciting developments have taken place. Azure Application Gateway, a popular service, has introduced support for TLS and TCP protocols in its public preview. This enhancement allows users to have more flexibility and security when managing their applications. Additionally, Azure API Management Developer Portal has unveiled enhanced features aimed at increasing developer productivity. These new features provide developers with improved tools and resources to streamline their work and create more efficient applications. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In other news, Tabnine, an AI coding assistant, has introduced a new feature called RAG (Red, Amber, Green) to generate contextual code. This innovative addition helps developers by providing suggestions and auto-completing code based on the current context, making coding faster and more accurate. This tool is expected to greatly benefit programmers and enhance their coding experience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Furthermore, NTT Data and Schneider Electric have joined forces to fuse their data for stronger 'Edge' IT. This collaboration aims to leverage the power of data to enhance IT infrastructure at the edge, enabling more efficient and reliable operations. By combining their expertise, NTT Data and Schneider Electric hope to create a stronger and more resilient IT ecosystem.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;These new tools, products, and projects demonstrate the continuous advancements in technology and the commitment of companies to improve user experiences and optimize operations. With the introduction of TLS and TCP support in Azure Application Gateway, enhanced features in Azure API Management Developer Portal, the contextual code generation feature in Tabnine, and the collaboration between NTT Data and Schneider Electric, the tech industry is constantly evolving to meet the ever-changing needs of users and businesses.
    </summary></entry></feed>