<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Science and Research</title><link href="https://novasparkxx.github.io/trend_science_and_research.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://novasparkxx.github.io/trend_science_and_research.xml</id><updated>2024-02-02T02:55:06Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>1. "Mineral Chemistry in Macaronesia: New Data and Comparisons"&lt;br&gt;2. "Assessing ER and PgR Expression in Endometrial Cancer"&lt;br&gt;3. "XTH Family Genes and Endosperm Weakening in Lettuce"&lt;br&gt;4. "Structural Health Monitoring of Sustainable Civil Infrastructure"&lt;br&gt;5. "The Impact of Colorado's Lithium Industry on Water Resources"&lt;br&gt;6. "Optimizing Chlorine Injection in Water Distribution Networks"&lt;br&gt;7. "Improving Session-Aware Recommenders with GRU-Based Integration"&lt;br&gt;8. "Longevity in Dog Breeds: A Comprehensive Study"&lt;br&gt;9. "Performance-Driven Optimization in Urban Block Design Research"&lt;br&gt;10. "Camouflage Inspired by Leaves: Hiding in Visible and Infrared"</title><link href="https://novasparkxx.github.io/trend_science_and_research.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-02-02T02:55:06Z</published><updated>2024-02-02T02:55:06Z</updated><id>54a6d5f7-c5b2-4d98-8dc3-c46c910b8d0c</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://imgproxy.nanxiongnandi.com/P_O89MPBYlhmFIfXN1-KWHdQIOZ40lkQcMHMZlMdWf8/w:1280/aHR0cHM6Ly9pbWcu/bmFueGlvbmduYW5k/aS5jb20vMjAyNDAx/L0J1a2hhbnNhblNl/b3VsLmpwZw.jpg" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/54a6d5f7-c5b2-4d98-8dc3-c46c910b8d0c.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent news, a study published in Minerals journal presents new data on the mineral chemistry of olivine, oxy-spinel, and clinopyroxene in lavas and xenoliths from the Canary, Azores, and Cape Verde Islands in the North Atlantic Ocean. The research provides comparisons with existing literature, shedding light on the composition of these minerals in the Macaronesia region. Another study published in Diagnostics focuses on the expression of estrogen receptor (ER) and progesterone receptor (PgR) in endometrial cancer through immunohistochemical assessment. This research contributes to a better understanding of the molecular characteristics of this type of cancer. Additionally, Agronomy journal features a study that identifies XTH family genes and analyzes the expression of endosperm weakening in lettuce. This research provides insights into the genetic factors influencing the softening of lettuce during maturation. In the field of civil infrastructure, a literature review published in Buildings examines the implementation of structural health monitoring (SHM) in sustainable civil infrastructure. The analysis explores the influencing factors in the adoption of SHM techniques. On a different note, concerns have been raised about America's lithium industry, which could potentially drain billions of gallons of water from the Colorado River and residential wells due to the lack of limitations imposed by a Civil War-era law. This highlights the need for sustainable practices in the mining sector. In the realm of water management, a study published in Water journal focuses on optimizing chlorine injection schedules in water distribution networks using water age and a breadth-first search algorithm. This research aims to improve the efficiency and effectiveness of water treatment processes. Future Internet journal presents a study that delves into optimizing session-aware recommenders, specifically exploring the integration of latent interactions using a GRU-based approach. This research contributes to the advancement of personalized recommendation systems. Shifting gears, a comprehensive study on dog longevity reveals which breeds tend to live the longest, providing valuable insights for dog owners and breeders. Lastly, Buildings journal features a scientometric examination of performance-driven optimization in urban block design research, offering an overview of the current state of the art and future perspectives in this field. In the realm of technology, researchers have developed camouflage inspired by leaves that can effectively hide objects in both visible and infrared spectrums. This innovation has potential applications in various fields, including military and surveillance.
    </summary></entry></feed>