<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Science and Research</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_science_and_research.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_science_and_research.xml</id><updated>2024-02-13T08:06:44Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Podcast Title: "Beyond the Surface: Unveiling Hidden Wonders of Science and History"</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_science_and_research.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-02-13T08:06:44Z</published><updated>2024-02-13T08:06:44Z</updated><id>ada4063a-120b-4944-b36f-c6e67c4b37ae</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_science_and_research.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/ada4063a-120b-4944-b36f-c6e67c4b37ae.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent news, a publisher correction was made regarding the absence of 3a0 charge density wave order in the infinite-layer nickelate NdNiO2. Additionally, an author correction was issued for a comparative study of auto-contouring softwares in the delineation of organs at risk in lung cancer and rectal cancer. In technology news, a study suggests that Apple's Vision Pro may have the potential to rewire people's brains, distort their perception of the world, and even cause a condition known as "simulator sickness." Archaeologists have also made an exciting discovery, uncovering what could be the largest Stone Age megastructure in Europe, a submerged wall. In the field of physics, an article explores why string theory has been unfairly maligned and proposes ways to test it. Another author correction was made for machine learning-based approaches in identifying human blood cells with CRISPR-mediated fetal chromatin domain ablations. In astronomy, it has been found that most newborn black holes emit gas so forcefully that they almost stop spinning. Furthermore, researchers have discovered that residual ANTXR1+ myofibroblasts after chemotherapy can inhibit anti-tumor immunity through the YAP1 signaling pathway. In the realm of health, zinc has provided a new clue as to why loud noise causes hearing loss. Lastly, scientists studying ocean transform faults have described a previously unknown part of the geological carbon cycle. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, there is no specific information provided in the given news articles.
    </summary></entry></feed>