<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.fun/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.fun/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-10-18T16:09:37Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Cloud Currents: Navigating the Latest AWS Innovations</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.fun/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-10-18T16:09:37Z</published><updated>2024-10-18T16:09:37Z</updated><id>bb8e851c-3488-49e8-bad3-9ebb68fbb6b5</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.fun/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/bb8e851c-3488-49e8-bad3-9ebb68fbb6b5.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent developments within the tech world, Amazon Web Services (AWS) has made significant strides to enhance its offerings and improve user experience. The AWS Marketplace has expanded its capabilities by supporting transactions in four new currencies and allowing disbursement to non-US bank accounts, making it more accessible to a global audience. Additionally, Amazon S3 has introduced new region and bucket name filtering options for its ListBuckets API, streamlining data management processes. The Amazon Managed Service for Prometheus has also been updated to allow users to configure a minimum firing period for alerts, enhancing monitoring capabilities. In terms of database management, Amazon RDS Multi-AZ deployments now support AWS IAM database authentication with two readable standbys, improving security and flexibility. Furthermore, Amazon DataZone has launched support for AWS IAM Identity Center account instances, facilitating better identity management. QuickSight has introduced subfolder support in restricted folders, enabling governed data sharing, while the AWS Lambda console has enhanced its functionality with real-time log analytics via Amazon CloudWatch Logs Live Tail and a new dashboard for key function insights. Lastly, the AWS Marketplace now allows for the self-service creation of single AMI product listings specifically for AWS GovCloud (US) Regions, and a zero ETL integration between Amazon Aurora PostgreSQL, Amazon DynamoDB, and Amazon Redshift has officially launched, simplifying data workflows.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;### New Tools, Products, and Projects:&lt;br&gt;1. **AWS Marketplace Currency Support**: Now supports four new currencies and non-US bank accounts for disbursement.&lt;br&gt;2. **Amazon S3 Enhancements**: New region and bucket name filtering for the ListBuckets API.&lt;br&gt;3. **Amazon Managed Service for Prometheus**: Minimum firing period configuration for alerts.&lt;br&gt;4. **Amazon RDS Multi-AZ Deployment**: Supports AWS IAM database authentication with two readable standbys.&lt;br&gt;5. **Amazon DataZone**: Now supports AWS IAM Identity Center account instances.&lt;br&gt;6. **QuickSight**: Introduced subfolder support in restricted folders for governed data sharing.&lt;br&gt;7. **AWS Lambda Console**: Real-time log analytics via Amazon CloudWatch Logs Live Tail and a new metrics insights dashboard.&lt;br&gt;8. **AWS GovCloud (US) AMI Listings**: Self-service creation of single AMI product listings.&lt;br&gt;9. **Zero ETL Integration**: Official launch of integration between Amazon Aurora PostgreSQL, Amazon DynamoDB, and Amazon Redshift.
    </summary></entry></feed>