<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-06-08T16:07:06Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Deep Dive: Exploring Centralized Network Traffic Inspection with Gateway Load Balancer and Palo Alto Firewall</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-06-08T16:07:06Z</published><updated>2024-06-08T16:07:06Z</updated><id>78433f98-9f0f-4c17-bc8c-0838787cd229</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/78433f98-9f0f-4c17-bc8c-0838787cd229.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of technology, there have been several developments and updates. One notable news is the implementation of centralized deep inspection of network traffic using Gateway Load Balancer and Palo Alto Firewall. This integration allows for more efficient and effective monitoring of network traffic.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another update comes from AWS, where they have introduced the Amazon EC2 U7i instance, Bedrock Converse API, and celebrated AWS World IPv6 Day. These advancements aim to enhance the performance and capabilities of AWS services.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Azure has also made significant progress with the general availability of vCore-based Azure Cosmos DB for MongoDB, which now supports Mongo Ver 7.0. This update provides European customers with more options and flexibility in utilizing Azure services.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Google has focused on empowering European customers with the power of choice through their Sovereign Cloud. This initiative allows customers to have more control over their data and comply with local regulations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additionally, Azure has added support for Azure Monitor log search alert rules in Resource Health. This feature enables users to effectively monitor and manage their resources in Azure.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of security, Amazon Web Services (AWS) has released a deployment guide for their WAF (Web Application Firewall) using Centralized Logging with OpenSearch Light Engine. This guide helps users reduce the cost of monitoring Amazon WAF logs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Azure Cosmos DB has introduced continuous backup for accounts using Azure Synapse Link in public preview. This feature ensures that data is consistently backed up, providing users with peace of mind.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Furthermore, Azure Cosmos DB now offers multi-select delete in Data Explorer, which is now generally available. This functionality simplifies data management and improves efficiency for users.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the realm of artificial intelligence, Google Cloud and SAP are collaborating to forge a path to enduring business innovation. This partnership aims to leverage AI technologies to drive innovation and growth in businesses.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, Azure has introduced public preview for online migration in migration service Azure Database for PostgreSQL. This feature allows for seamless and efficient migration of PostgreSQL databases to Azure.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Tools, Products, or Projects:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;- Gateway Load Balancer and Palo Alto Firewall integration for centralized deep inspection of network traffic&lt;br&gt;- Amazon EC2 U7i instance, Bedrock Converse API, and AWS World IPv6 Day&lt;br&gt;- General availability of vCore-based Azure Cosmos DB for MongoDB supporting Mongo Ver 7.0&lt;br&gt;- Google Sovereign Cloud, providing European customers with the power of choice&lt;br&gt;- Added support for Azure Monitor log search alert rules in Resource Health&lt;br&gt;- Deployment guide for WAF using Centralized Logging with OpenSearch Light Engine&lt;br&gt;- Public preview of Azure Cosmos DB continuous backup for accounts using Azure Synapse Link&lt;br&gt;- General availability of multi-select delete in Azure Cosmos DB with Data Explorer&lt;br&gt;- Collaboration between Google Cloud and SAP for enduring business innovation&lt;br&gt;- Public preview of online migration in migration service Azure Database for PostgreSQL
    </summary></entry></feed>