<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Science and Research</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_science_and_research.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_science_and_research.xml</id><updated>2024-09-12T16:08:01Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Crystal Energy: Unleashing the Power of Ferroelectric/Piezoelectric Materials</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_science_and_research.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-09-12T16:08:01Z</published><updated>2024-09-12T16:08:01Z</updated><id>e0c86212-31a6-4a84-b3b8-87be1af39291</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_science_and_research.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/e0c86212-31a6-4a84-b3b8-87be1af39291.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of energy harvesting, the latest research in ferroelectric/piezoelectric materials is being explored. A study published in Crystals, Volume 14, Pages 806, delves into the physical properties and current applications of these materials. These materials have the potential to harness energy from various sources and convert it into usable electricity, paving the way for more sustainable energy solutions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meanwhile, Metals, Volume 14, Pages 1036, presents insights gained through Density Functional Theory (DFT) regarding the physical properties of layered compounds LiMnSe2 and LiMnTe2. This research provides valuable information for the development of advanced materials with potential applications in various fields.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The impact of environmental regulation on the employment effect of high-tech industries is investigated in a study published in Sustainability, Volume 16, Pages 7960. Using a spatial Durbin model, researchers analyze the relationship between environmental regulations and employment in the high-tech sector. This research sheds light on the complex interplay between environmental policies and economic growth.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Photonics, Volume 11, Pages 859, introduces a channel correlation-based adaptive power transmission technique for free-space optical communications. This innovative approach aims to enhance the reliability and efficiency of optical communication systems, opening up new possibilities for high-speed data transmission.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the field of civil engineering, a study focuses on the effects of degraded durability on the long-term stability of in-service slopes with reinforced concrete support structures. This research, which can be found in an article titled "Effects of degraded durability on the long-term stability of in-service slopes with reinforced concrete support structures," highlights the importance of maintaining the structural integrity of infrastructure for long-term safety.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Metrology, Volume 4, Pages 457-468, presents practical approaches for determining the structural resolution capability of X-ray Computed Tomography (CT) measurement tasks. This research contributes to the improvement of CT measurement accuracy and reliability, benefiting a wide range of industries that rely on precise measurements.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the medical field, Biomedicines, Volume 12, Pages 2080, explores the evolving landscape of recurrent and metastatic head and neck cancer, with a particular focus on the role of immunotherapy. This comprehensive review provides valuable insights into the potential of immunotherapy as a treatment option for these challenging cancers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Genes, Volume 15, Pages 1198, introduces the concept of phylo-epigenetics in phylogeny analyses and evolution. This emerging field combines the study of genetic and epigenetic factors to gain a deeper understanding of evolutionary processes and relationships between species.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, in the realm of computer vision and artificial intelligence, Applied Sciences, Volume 14, Pages 8200, presents an improved method for detecting multi-class bad traffic signs. The study proposes the use of ensemble models and test time augmentation based on Yolov5 models, enhancing the accuracy and efficiency of traffic sign recognition systems.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;These diverse research findings showcase the continuous advancements and innovations happening across various scientific disciplines, paving the way for a brighter and more technologically advanced future.
    </summary></entry></feed>