<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Tech</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml</id><updated>2024-05-07T16:07:32Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>"React Revolution: Unleashing v18 with WASM and Rust - Dive into the Event System"</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-05-07T16:07:32Z</published><updated>2024-05-07T16:07:32Z</updated><id>9f94c47a-e5c5-41ea-b817-670e4666ee38</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_tech.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/9f94c47a-e5c5-41ea-b817-670e4666ee38.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of technology, there have been some interesting developments. One notable news is the implementation of React v18 from scratch using WebAssembly (WASM) and Rust. This new approach aims to enhance the performance and efficiency of React, a popular JavaScript library for building user interfaces. By utilizing WASM and Rust, developers can expect faster rendering and improved user experience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another topic that caught attention is the importance of setting responsive mode to 320px when checking the "mobile layout" of web pages. This practice ensures that websites are properly optimized for mobile devices, as 320px is the width of most smartphones. By testing the mobile layout at this specific width, developers can identify and fix any issues related to responsiveness, ensuring a seamless experience for mobile users.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the business world, Mirxes, a company preparing for its listing in Hong Kong, reported significant losses of $70.4 million alongside a revenue of $24.2 million. This financial update sheds light on the challenges faced by the company and highlights the need for strategic measures to improve profitability.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On a more positive note, Peak XV's Surge led a seed round of funding worth $2.75 million for an Indian log analytics firm. This investment will enable the analytics firm to further develop its capabilities and expand its reach in the market. It showcases the growing interest and support for innovative startups in the technology sector.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, Hyperzod, a company specializing in hyperlocal solutions, introduced a new service that promises lightning-fast delivery from click to doorstep. Their hyperlocal solution aims to revolutionize the delivery industry by providing swift and efficient delivery services. With this new offering, customers can expect their orders to be delivered in record time, enhancing convenience and customer satisfaction.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, there is no specific information provided in the given news. However, it is worth mentioning that the implementation of React v18 using WASM and Rust can be considered as a significant project in the technology field. This development showcases the continuous efforts to improve and optimize popular frameworks for better performance and user experience.
    </summary></entry></feed>