<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-02-20T08:06:15Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>"The Azure Backup Breakthrough: Unleashing Premium SSD v2 and Ultra Disks for VM Support"&lt;br&gt;"Revolutionizing Azure Backup: Harnessing Premium SSD v2 and Ultra Disks for VMs"&lt;br&gt;"Mastering Azure Backup: Unveiling Premium SSD v2, Ultra Disks, and Azure Monitor Logs Connector"&lt;br&gt;"Unleashing the Power of Azure Backup: Premium SSD v2, Ultra Disks, and Dynamic Time Ranges"&lt;br&gt;"The Future of Azure Backup: Premium SSD v2, Ultra Disks, and Dynamic Azure Monitor Logs Connector"</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-02-20T08:06:15Z</published><updated>2024-02-20T08:06:15Z</updated><id>bb2891fd-aa69-437d-989b-339840df20a6</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/bb2891fd-aa69-437d-989b-339840df20a6.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world, two significant developments have taken place in the realm of Azure Backup. Firstly, the support for Azure Virtual Machines (VMs) utilizing Premium SSD v2 has been made generally available. This enhancement allows users to back up their VMs efficiently using the advanced capabilities of Premium SSD v2. Secondly, the support for Azure VMs utilizing Ultra disks in Azure Backup has also been made generally available. This feature enables users to leverage the high-performance Ultra disks for their VM backups, ensuring faster and more reliable data protection. These updates in Azure Backup provide users with more options and flexibility in safeguarding their virtual machines and data.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In addition to these advancements, a new preview feature has been introduced in Azure Monitor. Users can now execute the Azure Monitor Logs connector on an exact time range provided dynamically. This feature allows for more precise monitoring and analysis by specifying the desired time range for log data retrieval. By leveraging this preview feature, users can gain deeper insights into their system's performance and troubleshoot issues more effectively.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Tools, Products, or Projects:&lt;br&gt;- Support for Azure VMs using Premium SSD v2 in Azure Backup: Users can now utilize the advanced capabilities of Premium SSD v2 to back up their Azure VMs efficiently.&lt;br&gt;- Support for Azure VMs using Ultra disks in Azure Backup: Users can leverage the high-performance Ultra disks for their Azure VM backups, ensuring faster and more reliable data protection.&lt;br&gt;- Execute Azure Monitor Logs connector on exact time range provided dynamically (preview): Users can now specify the desired time range for log data retrieval in Azure Monitor, enabling more precise monitoring and analysis.
    </summary></entry></feed>