<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Tech</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml</id><updated>2024-07-29T16:06:12Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Lambda Showdown: Unveiling the Java 21 Performance Battle - x86 vs arm64</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-07-29T16:06:12Z</published><updated>2024-07-29T16:06:12Z</updated><id>5db38366-4826-4e9a-af6f-585a86a2b55f</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_tech.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/5db38366-4826-4e9a-af6f-585a86a2b55f.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of technology, there have been some interesting developments recently. One notable news is the comparison of AWS Lambda performance with Java 21, specifically focusing on the x86 and arm64 architectures. This study, titled "AWS Lambda performance with Java 21: x86 vs arm64 - Part 1 Initial measurements," aims to understand the differences in performance between these two architectures and how it affects the overall efficiency of AWS Lambda.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another news article sheds light on the best practices for writing clean, efficient, and scalable code in Node.js. Titled "Unlocking Node.js Success: Best Practices for Clean, Efficient, and Scalable Code," this article provides valuable insights into optimizing Node.js applications for better performance and scalability. It serves as a guide for developers to enhance their coding skills and create high-quality applications.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;JavaScript developers can benefit from another informative article titled "Unlocking the Secrets: Avoid These Common JavaScript Pitfalls to Supercharge Your Development Skills!" This piece highlights common pitfalls in JavaScript development and offers tips to avoid them. By steering clear of these pitfalls, developers can supercharge their skills and deliver more robust and efficient JavaScript code.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the gaming world, the long-awaited release of "7 Days to Die" out of early access has finally happened after 11 years. This survival horror game has garnered a dedicated fan base over the years, and its exit from early access marks a significant milestone. Players can now enjoy the full version of the game, complete with all the updates and improvements made during its development.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, there is exciting news for Unreal Engine 5 (UE5) users. An upgraded version of the Fluid Flux Add-on for UE5 is almost here. This add-on enhances the fluid simulation capabilities of UE5, allowing developers to create stunning and realistic fluid effects in their games and simulations. With the upgraded version on the horizon, UE5 users can look forward to even more advanced fluid simulations in their projects.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Tools, Products, or Projects:&lt;br&gt;- AWS Lambda performance comparison study between x86 and arm64 architectures with Java 21.&lt;br&gt;- Best practices guide for clean, efficient, and scalable code in Node.js.&lt;br&gt;- Tips to avoid common JavaScript pitfalls and improve development skills.&lt;br&gt;- "7 Days to Die" released from early access after 11 years.&lt;br&gt;- Upgraded version of the Fluid Flux Add-on for UE5, enhancing fluid simulation capabilities.
    </summary></entry></feed>