<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Business and Market</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_business_and_market.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_business_and_market.xml</id><updated>2024-08-18T16:07:35Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>The Tea Trail: Empowering Tea Workers in the Aftermath of Wayanad Landslides</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_business_and_market.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-08-18T16:07:35Z</published><updated>2024-08-18T16:07:35Z</updated><id>21bc9fa0-5d6b-48d8-8c1e-c6bed8d73a47</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_business_and_market.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/21bc9fa0-5d6b-48d8-8c1e-c6bed8d73a47.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent news, Harrisons Malayalam, a prominent tea company, has announced relief measures for tea workers who have been affected by the devastating landslides in Wayanad. The company aims to support these workers during this difficult time and help them recover from the aftermath of the natural disaster. In another financial development, ITI Mutual Fund has set an ambitious target of achieving ₹1 lakh crore in assets under management (AUM) within the next five years. This reflects the company's confidence in its investment strategies and its commitment to growth. Shifting our focus to international affairs, India's holdings of US government securities have reached $242 billion, marking the highest level in a year. This indicates India's continued interest in investing in the US economy and strengthening bilateral ties. On a more personal note, an individual is seeking legal advice after giving a friend £3,000 while under the influence of alcohol. The person is now questioning whether they have any legal grounds to retrieve the money. Lastly, an individual who drives an electric car and is moving into a rented property wonders if they can request their landlord to install an electric vehicle (EV) charger. This raises the question of the tenant's rights and the landlord's responsibilities in accommodating EV owners.
    </summary></entry></feed>