<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Business and Market</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_business_and_market.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_business_and_market.xml</id><updated>2024-06-18T16:09:00Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>The Financial Frontier: Exploring Veefin's Supply Chain Finance Revolution and Regime Tax Solutions</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_business_and_market.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-06-18T16:09:00Z</published><updated>2024-06-18T16:09:00Z</updated><id>965f07db-73de-4227-98b2-8b383db9abbd</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_business_and_market.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/965f07db-73de-4227-98b2-8b383db9abbd.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world today, Veefin has announced its expansion of the supply chain finance platform by acquiring a stake in Regime Tax Solutions. This move is expected to enhance Veefin's capabilities in providing financial solutions for supply chain management. Meanwhile, London stocks have opened higher as investors await the release of UK inflation data and the central bank's decision. The Conservative party has accused the Labour party of having a secret plan to eliminate tax relief for farmers, sparking a debate on agricultural policies. In another development, BJP MLA Bellad has taken credit for Infosys' decision to shift its operations to Huballi, while the former CFO criticizes the move. Lastly, Shyam Srinivasan, the CEO of Federal Bank, emphasizes the importance of maintaining a boring and dull banking system, highlighting the stability and security it brings. Additionally, the 'Godfather of AI' has emerged from stealth mode to support a carbon capture startup, showcasing the growing interest in sustainable technologies.
    </summary></entry></feed>