<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Science and Research</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_science_and_research.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_science_and_research.xml</id><updated>2024-07-03T16:04:40Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Structures Uncovered: Exploring the Science Behind Buildings and Stability</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_science_and_research.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-07-03T16:04:40Z</published><updated>2024-07-03T16:04:40Z</updated><id>f7b972e3-979a-4b20-9d81-f9844a4c43e8</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_science_and_research.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/f7b972e3-979a-4b20-9d81-f9844a4c43e8.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent news, several studies and research papers have been published in various scientific journals. In the field of construction, a study published in Buildings, Vol. 14, Pages 2027, focused on the effect of water-binder ratio on the carbonation resistance of raw sea sand alkali-activated slag concrete and the distribution of chloride ions after carbonation. This research aims to improve the durability of concrete structures in coastal areas.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another study, published in Applied Sciences, Vol. 14, Pages 5804, delved into the seismic stability of bedding slopes using a pseudo-dynamic method and its numerical validation. This research contributes to the understanding of slope stability and can aid in the design and construction of safer infrastructure.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the realm of cybersecurity, a paper published in Applied Sciences, Vol. 14, Pages 5805, explored collaboration practices for the cybersecurity of supply chains to critical infrastructure. With the increasing reliance on interconnected systems, this study highlights the importance of securing supply chains to protect critical infrastructure from cyber threats.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moving on to medical research, a case report and literature review on Mollaret's Meningitis caused by Herpes Simplex Virus 2 was published in Microorganisms, Vol. 12, Pages 1363. This report provides valuable insights into the diagnosis and management of this rare neurological condition.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the field of immunology, Biomedicines, Vol. 12, Pages 1469, published a study that explores the immune system at a cellular level using flow cytometry. This research sheds light on the intricate workings of the immune system and its implications for various diseases and conditions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Biomolecules, Vol. 14, Pages 789, featured a review on alginate-based electrospun nanofibers and their drug-controlled release profiles. This review discusses the potential applications of these nanofibers in controlled drug delivery systems, offering new possibilities for targeted therapies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the medical field, JCM, Vol. 13, Pages 3903, presents a meta-analysis and pilot study on the assessment of two transferase-based liver enzymes in patients chronically infected with Hepatitis B Virus. This research aims to improve the diagnosis and management of liver fibrosis in these patients.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shifting focus to the realm of psychology, Societies, Vol. 14, Pages 110, examines the effects of work-family conflict and facilitation profiles on work engagement. This study provides insights into the factors that influence work engagement and can contribute to the development of strategies to enhance employee well-being.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the field of materials science, Metals, Vol. 14, Pages 783, investigates the influence of high-temperature deformation on the dissolution of δ-Ferrite in stainless steels. This research contributes to the understanding of the behavior of stainless steels under high-temperature conditions, which is crucial for various industrial applications.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, Symmetry, Vol. 16, Pages 835, presents a study on the effects of presentation side and emotional valence on auditory recognition in younger and older adults. This research explores the cognitive processes involved in auditory recognition and provides insights into age-related differences in auditory perception.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, there is no specific information provided in the given news.
    </summary></entry></feed>