<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Business and Market</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_business_and_market.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_business_and_market.xml</id><updated>2024-07-23T16:07:55Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Margin Matters: Unpacking MRPL's Q1 Results and the Impact of Weak Gross Refining Margins</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_business_and_market.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-07-23T16:07:55Z</published><updated>2024-07-23T16:07:55Z</updated><id>7d6e9169-9d05-41fd-8405-2cea225eaadb</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_business_and_market.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/7d6e9169-9d05-41fd-8405-2cea225eaadb.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world news, the first quarter results of MRPL (Mangalore Refinery and Petrochemicals Limited) have been reviewed and it has been reported that weak gross refining margins have dragged down the company's earnings, according to Prabhudas Lilladher. Additionally, the announcement of Budget 2024 has had significant impacts on the financial market. Stocks have tumbled and the rupee has reached a record low after the government raised capital gains tax. However, there have been some positive developments as well, with tourism stocks gaining due to corridor plans for religious sites. In the international market, Barclays has raised its 2024 S&amp;P 500 price target, showing optimism for the future. On the automotive front, Volkswagen is facing challenges in China but is looking to grow in the US market through electric vehicles. In the budget, railway stocks have declined due to a lack of allotment to the sector. The government has also made changes to the capital gains exemption limit and increased short-term and long-term capital gains tax. On a more positive note, the budget has highlighted the potential benefits for two-wheeler sales through rural and job-related initiatives. Lastly, in the UK, the London IPO for Canal+ has been seen as a "big loss" for President Macron, as stated by Maggie Pagano.
    </summary></entry></feed>