<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.fun/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.fun/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-10-16T16:15:02Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>AWS Unlocked: Navigating the Latest Innovations in Cloud Database and Beyond</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.fun/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-10-16T16:15:02Z</published><updated>2024-10-16T16:15:02Z</updated><id>5494ef5e-6ee3-4bfb-a61e-1bb502cabc7b</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.fun/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/5494ef5e-6ee3-4bfb-a61e-1bb502cabc7b.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent developments within the tech world, Amazon Web Services (AWS) has made significant strides in enhancing its cloud offerings. The company has expanded its Amazon RDS (Relational Database Service) to support M7g and R7g database instances in additional AWS Regions, allowing for improved performance and scalability. Moreover, Amazon RDS for MariaDB has been updated to support version 11.4, introducing new password validation options to bolster security. The availability of Amazon EC2 C7i-flex instances has also been extended to more regions, providing users with flexible compute options. In the realm of data integration, Amazon Aurora PostgreSQL now features zero-ETL integration with Amazon Redshift, streamlining data workflows, while Amazon DynamoDB has similarly launched its zero-ETL integration with Redshift, enhancing data accessibility and analytics capabilities. Additionally, Amazon RDS has introduced 1-click connectivity to EC2 instances in the AWS GovCloud (US) Regions, simplifying deployment processes for government clients. Amazon EFS (Elastic File System) has doubled its read throughput capacity to 60 GiB/s, catering to high-demand applications. In a move to improve search functionality, Amazon Q Business has launched a feature that utilizes connector metadata to enhance search relevance. The AWS access portal has also been updated to provide a more streamlined sign-in experience for users of the AWS Console Mobile App. Lastly, Amazon OpenSearch Serverless has expanded its availability to the Asia Pacific (Seoul) and Europe (Zurich) regions, further broadening its global reach.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;### New Tools, Products, and Projects:&lt;br&gt;1. **Amazon RDS**: Now supports M7g and R7g database instances in more AWS Regions.&lt;br&gt;2. **Amazon RDS for MariaDB**: Updated to support MariaDB 11.4 with enhanced password validation options.&lt;br&gt;3. **Amazon EC2 C7i-flex Instances**: Expanded availability in additional AWS Regions.&lt;br&gt;4. **Amazon Aurora PostgreSQL**: Introduced zero-ETL integration with Amazon Redshift.&lt;br&gt;5. **Amazon DynamoDB**: Launched zero-ETL integration with Amazon Redshift.&lt;br&gt;6. **Amazon RDS**: Added 1-click connectivity to EC2 instances in AWS GovCloud (US) Regions.&lt;br&gt;7. **Amazon EFS**: Increased read throughput capacity to 60 GiB/s.&lt;br&gt;8. **Amazon Q Business**: New feature for improved search relevance using connector metadata.&lt;br&gt;9. **AWS Access Portal**: Streamlined sign-in for the AWS Console Mobile App.&lt;br&gt;10. **Amazon OpenSearch Serverless**: Now available in Asia Pacific (Seoul) and Europe (Zurich) regions.
    </summary></entry></feed>