<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-02-14T08:05:41Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>"Scaling Character.AI: Unleashing the Power of AlloyDB and Spanner for Growth"&lt;br&gt;</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-02-14T08:05:41Z</published><updated>2024-02-14T08:05:41Z</updated><id>9d7203b1-f880-4f5b-9a7f-d9b9ea0041f9</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/9d7203b1-f880-4f5b-9a7f-d9b9ea0041f9.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of technology, several new developments have taken place. Firstly, Azure Firewall has introduced two new features that are now generally available. Flow Trace Logs allow users to track the flow of network traffic, providing valuable insights into network security. Additionally, Autoscaling based on the number of connections enables automatic adjustment of resources to meet demand.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another exciting update is the availability of Zone Redundant Storage for Azure Disks in Canada Central. This feature ensures data redundancy and high availability by replicating data across multiple availability zones.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of virtual machine scale sets, a new upgrade policy using Flexible Orchestration is now in public preview. This allows for more efficient and customizable upgrades, enhancing the overall management of virtual machine scale sets.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Furthermore, there is a change in policy regarding log search alerts. Sending log search alerts to unauthorized target resources will no longer be supported, ensuring better security and control over log data.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Azure Firewall has also introduced Parallel IP Group update support, which is now in public preview. This feature allows for simultaneous updates to IP groups, improving efficiency and management of firewall rules.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the realm of cloud monitoring, Cloud Monitoring now offers PromQL alerting and the ability to import dashboards from Grafana. This integration enhances the monitoring capabilities and provides more flexibility in creating and managing alerts and dashboards.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, the article mentions the scaling of Character.AI and how AlloyDB for PostgreSQL and Spanner met their growing needs. Unfortunately, no further details are provided about this specific project.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, these new tools, products, and projects showcase the continuous innovation and improvement happening in the technology industry, particularly in the realm of cloud computing and network security.
    </summary></entry></feed>