<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-04-01T16:06:16Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>1. "Tech Talk: Navigating the Retirement of Azure Maps and Azure Maps Service"&lt;br&gt;2. "Data Factory Decoded: Maximizing Performance with General Purpose Data Flows"&lt;br&gt;3. "Future-Proof Your Apps: Upgrading Azure Functions from .NET 6 to .NET 8"&lt;br&gt;4. "Windows Server 2022 Retirement: What it Means for Kubernetes Users"&lt;br&gt;5. "Stream Analytics Evolution: Saying Goodbye to Custom .Net Deserializer"&lt;br&gt;6. "Chef Cookbooks Sunset: Azure CycleCloud's Transition to Cluster-Init Projects"&lt;br&gt;7. "Functionality Shift: The End of In-Process Model for .NET Apps in Azure Functions"&lt;br&gt;8. "APIOps Revolution: Streamlining Git Repository Deployments"&lt;br&gt;9. "Dashboard Dilemma: Migrating to Azure Monitor-Based Dashboards in API Management"&lt;br&gt;10. "Audio API Transition: Embracing the New Batch Synthesis API"</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-04-01T16:06:16Z</published><updated>2024-04-01T16:06:16Z</updated><id>95786f9c-0b24-44c2-b9b1-229df3aad0d8</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/95786f9c-0b24-44c2-b9b1-229df3aad0d8.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of technology, several retirements and changes are taking place. Firstly, the Azure Maps Web SDK Map Control version 2.0.x and Azure Maps Service Module will be retired on 30 September 2026. This indicates that users will need to transition to newer versions or alternative tools for their mapping needs. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additionally, Memory Optimized Data Flows in Azure Data Factory are being retired. Users are advised to utilize the General Purpose option, which offers better performance at a lower price. This change aims to optimize data processing and cost-efficiency within Azure Data Factory.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another retirement notice concerns the support for .NET 6, which will end on 12 November 2024. Users are encouraged to upgrade their Azure Functions apps to .NET 8 to ensure compatibility and access the latest features.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Furthermore, Windows Server 2022 will retire with k8s 1.34 in March 2027. This indicates that users will need to plan for the transition to newer versions or alternative server options by that time.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of specific tools and projects, the Custom .Net deserializer for Azure Stream Analytics will be retired on 30 September 2024. Users relying on this deserializer will need to find alternative solutions for their stream analytics needs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Azure CycleCloud support for Chef run_lists and cookbooks in cluster-init projects is also ending on 31 March 2025. Users utilizing these features will need to explore other options for managing their cluster-init projects within Azure CycleCloud.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moreover, the in-process model for .NET apps in Azure Functions will no longer be supported after 10 November 2026. Users are advised to adapt their .NET apps to alternative models to ensure continued functionality.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On a different note, there are new tools and projects emerging. One such example is the opportunity to migrate Git Repositories to automated deployments with APIOps by 15 March 2025. This offers a streamlined and efficient approach to managing code deployments.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additionally, Azure API Management is introducing Azure Monitor–based dashboards, which users are encouraged to begin using before the retirement of the built-in analytics dashboards on 15 March 2027. This transition aims to enhance monitoring capabilities and provide a more comprehensive analytics experience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, the Long Audio API will be retired on 31 March 2027. Users are advised to migrate to the new batch synthesis API, which offers improved audio processing capabilities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;These retirements and new projects highlight the ever-evolving nature of technology and the need for users to stay updated and adapt to the changing landscape.
    </summary></entry></feed>