<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-02-04T03:38:11Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>"The Cloud Chronicles: Unleashing the Power of Amazon RDS and Azure Site Recovery"</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-02-04T03:38:11Z</published><updated>2024-02-04T03:38:11Z</updated><id>aa78247d-d102-4b7b-8546-c321a2f4beba</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/aa78247d-d102-4b7b-8546-c321a2f4beba.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of technology, there have been several notable developments. Firstly, Amazon RDS for PostgreSQL has introduced support for Trusted Language Extensions, specifically the croaring-rs and num-bigint crate. This enhancement allows users to leverage these extensions for improved functionality and performance within their PostgreSQL databases.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moving on to Microsoft Azure, a new feature called Azure Site Recovery has entered its Private Preview phase. This feature provides support for Azure Trusted Launch VMs running on the Windows operating system. With Azure Site Recovery, users can ensure the security and integrity of their virtual machines during the launch process.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;However, there is also news of retirement. Log alert rules that utilize cross-workspace queries with resource names or qualified name identifiers will be retired on 31 May 2024. This change indicates a shift in focus towards more efficient and streamlined log alerting mechanisms within the Azure ecosystem.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On a positive note, Azure Virtual Network Manager security admin rule has become generally available in 30 regions. This feature enables users to manage and enforce security policies within their virtual networks, enhancing the overall security posture of their Azure infrastructure.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, there is an interesting project that explores the consumption of Cloud Storage objects on Google Kubernetes Engine (GKE) using the Kubernetes API. This project, titled "Consuming Cloud Storage objects on GKE using the Kubernetes API - Part I," aims to provide users with a seamless and efficient way to interact with Cloud Storage objects within their GKE clusters.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, the aforementioned project on consuming Cloud Storage objects on GKE using the Kubernetes API stands out. This initiative showcases the continuous efforts to improve the integration and interoperability between different cloud services, enabling users to leverage the full potential of their cloud infrastructure.
    </summary></entry></feed>