<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-04-22T16:05:25Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>"The Ever-Changing Azure: Navigating the Latest Updates and Retirements"</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-04-22T16:05:25Z</published><updated>2024-04-22T16:05:25Z</updated><id>52bf5a2f-fd0c-4dde-8758-1d8ab3b6dfa6</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/52bf5a2f-fd0c-4dde-8758-1d8ab3b6dfa6.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of technology, several changes and updates are set to take place in the coming years. Azure Advisor, a tool that provides recommendations for optimizing Azure resources, will no longer display aggregated potential yearly savings starting from September 30, 2024. This change aims to enhance the accuracy and relevance of the recommendations provided.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another significant development is the retirement of the Cloud Services (classic) deployment model on August 31, 2024. This retirement indicates a shift towards newer and more advanced deployment models, ensuring better performance and efficiency for cloud services.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Furthermore, Azure Stream Analytics will retire the use of .Net Standard user-defined functions on September 30, 2024. This change encourages developers to explore alternative methods for stream analytics, promoting innovation and improved functionality.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the realm of healthcare, Azure Health Data Services introduces a new feature called the Bulk delete operation for the FHIR service, which has now become generally available. This feature allows for efficient deletion of large volumes of data, streamlining data management processes in the healthcare industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additionally, App Service Environment versions 1 and 2 will be retired on August 31, 2024. This retirement signifies the transition towards newer versions that offer enhanced features and improved performance for hosting web applications.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moreover, five Azure classic networking services are also set to retire on August 31, 2024. This retirement reflects the continuous evolution of networking technologies, as newer and more advanced services take their place.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of disaster recovery, Azure Site Recovery introduces a new feature called DR for Shared Disks, which is currently in the public preview phase. This feature enables the replication and recovery of shared disks, providing enhanced data protection and business continuity for organizations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, the support for Azure Notification Hubs' Firebase Cloud Messaging (FCM) legacy API will be deprecated by July 2024. This deprecation encourages users to migrate to newer versions and APIs, ensuring compatibility and improved functionality.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;These updates and changes in the world of technology showcase the continuous evolution and innovation within the industry. As new tools, products, and projects emerge, users are encouraged to adapt and embrace these advancements to stay at the forefront of technological progress.
    </summary></entry></feed>