<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Tech</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml</id><updated>2024-08-10T16:06:18Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Unraveling the Mystery: Exploring the Lambda Quota Disparity in AWS Accounts</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-08-10T16:06:18Z</published><updated>2024-08-10T16:06:18Z</updated><id>ced13cd2-d94b-476e-bbba-6e2411e7cb81</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_tech.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/ced13cd2-d94b-476e-bbba-6e2411e7cb81.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent news, it has been discovered that the Lambda quota for a new AWS account is lower than the Lambda quota for other existing AWS accounts. This discrepancy has raised questions among users as to why new accounts are being given a lower quota. While AWS has not provided an official statement on the matter, experts speculate that this could be a measure to prevent misuse or abuse of the Lambda service by new users. By imposing a lower quota, AWS may be aiming to ensure that new accounts gradually familiarize themselves with the service and its capabilities before granting them full access to higher quotas. This approach could help maintain the stability and performance of the Lambda service for all users.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In other news, a comprehensive guide has been released for students looking to obtain a free Microsoft Azure certification. This guide offers valuable insights and tips on how to boost one's resume without incurring any financial burden. With the increasing demand for Azure skills in the job market, this guide serves as a valuable resource for students who wish to enhance their career prospects without breaking the bank. It provides step-by-step instructions on how to prepare for the certification exam, access free learning resources, and gain practical experience through hands-on projects. This initiative by Microsoft highlights their commitment to empowering students and making valuable certifications accessible to all.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Furthermore, AWS has introduced a new project that allows users to build their own music app using AWS S3 Bucket Static Web Hosting. This project provides developers with a platform to showcase their creativity and technical skills by creating a fully functional music app. By leveraging the power of AWS S3 Bucket Static Web Hosting, developers can easily store and distribute their music files, create user-friendly interfaces, and implement advanced features such as playlist management and personalized recommendations. This project not only encourages innovation but also demonstrates the versatility and scalability of AWS services in the realm of web development.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, an inspiring journey has been shared by a developer who transitioned from being a frontend developer to a full-stack developer with Ruby on Rails. This personal account highlights the challenges, learning experiences, and growth that can be achieved through dedication and perseverance. The developer shares valuable insights into the process of acquiring new skills, mastering different technologies, and expanding one's professional horizons. This story serves as a motivation for aspiring developers who aspire to broaden their skillset and take on more comprehensive projects. It showcases the potential for personal and professional growth within the field of software development.
    </summary></entry></feed>