<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://novasparkxx.github.io/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://novasparkxx.github.io/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-02-02T02:55:43Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>1. "Azure Virtual Network Manager Security Admin Rule Now Available in 30 Regions"&lt;br&gt;2. "AWS Glue Introduces New Chat Experience with Amazon Q Dataset Integration"&lt;br&gt;3. "Retirement of Log Alert Rules with Cross-Workspace Queries on May 31, 2024"&lt;br&gt;4. "29 No-Cost Ways to Boost Your Cloud Career in February"&lt;br&gt;5. "Deutsche Börse Group Benefits from Moving to S/4 HANA on Google Cloud"&lt;br&gt;6. "To Pay or Not to Pay: Exploring the Crucial Ransomware Question"&lt;br&gt;7. "Consume Cloud Storage Objects on GKE with Kubernetes API - Part I"&lt;br&gt;8. "Private Preview: Azure Site Recovery Support for Azure Trusted Launch VMs (Windows OS)"</title><link href="https://novasparkxx.github.io/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-02-02T02:55:43Z</published><updated>2024-02-02T02:55:43Z</updated><id>2c6f374a-23f3-4a03-9d06-213c2e3f6b13</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://imgproxy.nanxiongnandi.com/P_O89MPBYlhmFIfXN1-KWHdQIOZ40lkQcMHMZlMdWf8/w:1280/aHR0cHM6Ly9pbWcu/bmFueGlvbmduYW5k/aS5jb20vMjAyNDAx/L0J1a2hhbnNhblNl/b3VsLmpwZw.jpg" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/2c6f374a-23f3-4a03-9d06-213c2e3f6b13.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of technology, several significant developments have taken place. Azure Virtual Network Manager security admin rule has now become generally available in 30 regions, providing enhanced security measures for virtual networks. AWS Glue has introduced a new chat experience called Amazon Q Dataset Integration, allowing users to interact with the platform using natural language. However, this feature is currently in the preview version. On the other hand, log alert rules that utilize cross-workspace queries with resource names or qualified name identifiers will be retired by May 31, 2024. This change indicates a shift in the approach to log alerting. Additionally, a report has been published exploring the dilemma of whether to pay ransomware demands or not, shedding light on the crucial decision-making process. In the cloud career domain, professionals can find 29 no-cost ways to advance their skills and knowledge this February, providing valuable opportunities for growth. Furthermore, Deutsche Börse Group has experienced significant benefits by migrating to S/4 HANA on Google Cloud, showcasing the advantages of this transition. Lastly, Azure Site Recovery now offers support for Azure Trusted Launch VMs (Windows OS) in a private preview, enabling users to ensure the security and integrity of their virtual machines. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, there are a few noteworthy mentions. Azure Virtual Network Manager's security admin rule becoming generally available in 30 regions signifies the continuous improvement and expansion of Azure's security capabilities. AWS Glue's new chat experience, Amazon Q Dataset Integration, demonstrates the platform's commitment to enhancing user interaction and accessibility. The report exploring the decision of whether to pay ransomware demands or not provides valuable insights into the evolving landscape of cybersecurity. Additionally, the availability of 29 no-cost ways to advance cloud career skills this February offers professionals numerous opportunities for personal and professional growth. Lastly, the private preview of Azure Site Recovery's support for Azure Trusted Launch VMs (Windows OS) showcases Microsoft's dedication to providing robust security features for virtual machines. These developments highlight the ongoing innovation and progress in the technology industry.
    </summary></entry></feed>