<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Tech</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.fun/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.fun/podcast/trend_tech.xml</id><updated>2024-10-29T16:11:20Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Tech Tides: From Penguin Islands to Green Servers - Innovations Shaping Shenzhen and Beyond</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.fun/podcast/trend_tech.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-10-29T16:11:20Z</published><updated>2024-10-29T16:11:20Z</updated><id>e8c99d76-d011-4e03-b0a9-ac9dbaa3ec30</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.fun/cover/trend_tech.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/e8c99d76-d011-4e03-b0a9-ac9dbaa3ec30.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent global developments, Tencent's Penguin Island in Shenzhen is set to complete its first phase and open by the end of the year, marking a significant milestone in the tech giant's expansion into entertainment and leisure. Meanwhile, Fujitsu has partnered with Supermicro to advance the development of environmentally friendly servers and liquid cooling solutions, reflecting a growing trend towards sustainability in the tech industry. At the DCD&gt;Connect event in Virginia, Belden showcased innovative solutions aimed at enhancing mission-critical data center operations, underscoring the importance of reliability in data management. Additionally, Porsche is expanding its research and development workforce in China, focusing on high-tech dashboards and assisted driving technologies, which highlights the automotive industry's shift towards smarter, more connected vehicles.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;### New Tools, Products, or Projects&lt;br&gt;1. **Tencent's Penguin Island**: A new entertainment complex in Shenzhen, expected to open soon, featuring various attractions and experiences.&lt;br&gt;2. **Fujitsu and Supermicro's Green Servers**: A collaboration to produce energy-efficient servers and advanced liquid cooling systems, promoting sustainability in data centers.&lt;br&gt;3. **Belden's Data Center Solutions**: Innovative products designed to support mission-critical operations, showcased at the DCD&gt;Connect event.&lt;br&gt;4. **Porsche's R&amp;D Expansion**: New projects aimed at developing advanced dashboard technologies and assisted driving features, enhancing vehicle intelligence and user experience.
    </summary></entry></feed>