<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Trend Cloud Spotlight</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml</id><updated>2024-06-07T16:06:42Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>The Data Vault: Unleashing the Power of Azure Database and Cosmos DB</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/trend_cloud_spotlight.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-06-07T16:06:42Z</published><updated>2024-06-07T16:06:42Z</updated><id>2b2f6aa8-decc-4311-896a-b45aecd550c4</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/trend_cloud_spotlight.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/2b2f6aa8-decc-4311-896a-b45aecd550c4.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of technology, several significant developments have taken place recently. Firstly, Azure Database for PostgreSQL Flexible Server now offers long-term backup retention, allowing users to securely store their data for extended periods. Additionally, Azure Monitor log search alert rules can now be utilized in Resource Health, providing users with more comprehensive monitoring capabilities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Furthermore, Azure Database for PostgreSQL introduces online migration in its migration service, making it easier for users to migrate their data seamlessly. Another noteworthy update is the general availability of vCore-based Azure Cosmos DB for MongoDB, which now supports Mongo Ver 7.0, enhancing its compatibility and functionality.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In other news, European customers can now benefit from the power of choice with Google Sovereign Cloud, enabling them to have greater control over their data and comply with local regulations. This development highlights the importance of data sovereignty and privacy in today's digital landscape.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moving forward, there are also updates from AWS, including the introduction of Amazon EC2 U7i instances, Bedrock Converse API, and the celebration of AWS World IPv6 Day in June 2024. These advancements showcase AWS's commitment to providing innovative solutions and embracing the latest technologies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moreover, starting July 2024, log search alert rules using linked storage will require the use of a managed identity, ensuring enhanced security and access control. This change aims to protect sensitive data and prevent unauthorized access.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the realm of artificial intelligence, Google Cloud and SAP are joining forces to forge a path to enduring business innovation. This collaboration emphasizes the potential of AI in driving transformative changes and creating new opportunities for businesses.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, Azure Cosmos DB introduces a public preview of continuous backup for accounts using Azure Synapse Link, enabling users to have a seamless and reliable backup solution. Additionally, Azure Cosmos DB now offers the general availability of multi-select delete in Data Explorer, simplifying data management and improving efficiency.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As for new tools, products, or projects, there is no specific information provided in the given news.
    </summary></entry></feed>