<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Voyager</title><link href="https://novasparkxx.github.io/vite.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://novasparkxx.github.io/vite.xml</id><updated>2024-02-01T08:04:13Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Thu, 01 Feb 2024 08:04:13</title><link href="https://novasparkxx.github.io/vite.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-02-01T08:04:13Z</published><updated>2024-02-01T08:04:13Z</updated><id>f20539ff-a0f2-4549-b059-1ce838a8b88d</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://imgproxy.nanxiongnandi.com/P_O89MPBYlhmFIfXN1-KWHdQIOZ40lkQcMHMZlMdWf8/w:1280/aHR0cHM6Ly9pbWcu/bmFueGlvbmduYW5k/aS5jb20vMjAyNDAx/L0J1a2hhbnNhblNl/b3VsLmpwZw.jpg" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/f20539ff-a0f2-4549-b059-1ce838a8b88d.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world today, a study has revealed that whether you flush the toilet with the lid up or down doesn't actually matter. This finding may put an end to the long-standing debate on proper toilet etiquette. In other news, Conexiom has introduced a groundbreaking AI platform that revolutionizes sales order automation. This next-generation technology promises to streamline and enhance the sales process for businesses. Meanwhile, a project focused on exploring dictionaries, classifying variables, and imputing data in the Ames Dataset has been initiated. This endeavor aims to improve data analysis and interpretation in various fields. Additionally, CrowdStrike and At-Bay have joined forces to strengthen cyber resilience among small and medium-sized businesses. This collaboration will provide enhanced cybersecurity solutions to protect against evolving threats. Rockset, a cloud-based search and analytics database, has released a new instance class, solidifying its position as a leading platform in the industry. This development will further enhance data management and analysis capabilities for businesses. Despite economic uncertainty, a survey conducted by Deloitte and Fast Company reveals that companies are investing more in innovation. This demonstrates a commitment to driving progress and growth even in challenging times. In the field of technology, a comprehensive guide titled "Neural Networks Illustrated, Part 1: How Does a Neural Network Work?" has been published, shedding light on the inner workings of this powerful technology. Furthermore, the FBI has successfully removed Chinese malware from small office/home office (SOHO) routers after issuing covert commands. This operation highlights the ongoing efforts to combat cyber threats and protect individuals and businesses. Lastly, for word game enthusiasts, today's "Wordle" hints and clues for Wednesday, February 1st have been released, providing an exciting challenge for players. In the realm of biologics manufacturing, Genentech and C3 AI have collaborated to improve the complex process using artificial intelligence. This partnership aims to optimize production and enhance the quality of biologic drugs. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, the following developments have emerged: &lt;br&gt;1. Conexiom has introduced a next-gen AI platform that revolutionizes sales order automation, promising improved efficiency and effectiveness.&lt;br&gt;2. Rockset has released a new instance class, further enhancing its cloud-based search and analytics database capabilities.&lt;br&gt;3. Genentech and C3 AI have joined forces to improve the complex biologics manufacturing process using AI, aiming to optimize production and enhance drug quality.&lt;br&gt;4. The FBI successfully removed Chinese malware from SOHO routers, showcasing ongoing efforts to combat cyber threats.&lt;br&gt;5. The comprehensive guide "Neural Networks Illustrated, Part 1: How Does a Neural Network Work?" provides valuable insights into the functioning of neural networks.
    </summary></entry></feed>