<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Voyager</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/voyager.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/voyager.xml</id><updated>2024-10-08T16:08:23Z</updated><subtitle>Welcome to "Voyager," the podcast where the frontiers of technology, cybersecurity, and scientific discovery converge. Each week, we embark on a digital odyssey through the vast and ever-evolving landscape of the internet to bring you the most intriguing and vital stories from the realms of tech and science.

In "Voyager," we delve deep into the latest advancements in technology, from groundbreaking gadgets and innovations to the software shaping our digital world. We unravel the complex and fascinating world of cybersecurity, keeping you informed about the latest threats, defenses, and trends that matter in our increasingly connected lives.

But our journey doesn't stop there. We also traverse the exciting universe of scientific discovery, bringing you cutting-edge news, interviews with thought leaders, and insights into the research that's changing our understanding of the world and beyond.

Whether you're a tech enthusiast, a cybersecurity professional, or just curious about the scientific phenomena shaping our future, "Voyager" is your guide through the complex web of modern innovation. Join us as we explore the most compelling stories at the intersection of technology, cybersecurity, and science – stories that inform, inspire, and ignite the imagination.

Subscribe to "Voyager" and stay ahead of the curve in this fast-paced digital age. New episodes drop every week, filled with expert analysis, engaging discussions, and a passion for the marvels of the internet era. Set sail with us on this journey of discovery and exploration – into the heart of what's next.
</subtitle><entry><title>AI Unplugged: Navigating the Future of Tech, Security, and Innovation</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/voyager.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-10-08T16:08:23Z</published><updated>2024-10-08T16:08:23Z</updated><id>9d6b06e1-bd38-439f-b8c0-cbc705174534</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/voyager.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/9d6b06e1-bd38-439f-b8c0-cbc705174534.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent global developments, the tech landscape is witnessing significant advancements in artificial intelligence (AI) and its applications across various sectors. SAP has expanded its support for open-source large language models (LLMs) and transformed its Joule platform into a collaborative agent, enhancing its capabilities for users. Meanwhile, G42 has acquired Abu Dhabi-based cybersecurity firm CPX, aiming to bolster security measures within the AI ecosystem. In the realm of education, the University of Nebraska Omaha has launched its first artificial intelligence degree program, marking a pivotal step in preparing the workforce for future AI challenges. Additionally, IBM has made its Granite LLM accessible through the Generative AI Hub in SAP AI Core, further integrating AI into business solutions. Foxconn is set to construct Taiwan's fastest AI supercomputer using NVIDIA's Blackwell technology, showcasing the race for computational power in AI development. Vodafone and Google are strengthening their AI collaboration across Europe and Africa, while an AI Platform Alliance has emerged to unite system and chip companies, fostering innovation in the industry. Despite these advancements, analysts from Jefferies suggest that truly intelligent smartphones powered by AI are still a few years away.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;### New Tools, Products, and Projects&lt;br&gt;1. **SAP Joule**: Now a collaborative agent with enhanced support for open-source LLMs.&lt;br&gt;2. **IBM Granite LLM**: Available through the Generative AI Hub in SAP AI Core, facilitating business applications of AI.&lt;br&gt;3. **AI Degree Program**: The University of Nebraska Omaha has introduced its first degree program focused on artificial intelligence.&lt;br&gt;4. **Foxconn's AI Supercomputer**: A project to build Taiwan's fastest AI supercomputer using NVIDIA's Blackwell technology.&lt;br&gt;5. **AI Platform Alliance**: A new initiative bringing together system and chip companies to drive AI innovation.&lt;br&gt;6. **G42's Acquisition of CPX**: A strategic move to enhance cybersecurity measures in the AI domain.
    </summary></entry></feed>