<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Voyager</title><link href="https://novasparkxx.github.io/vite.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://novasparkxx.github.io/vite.xml</id><updated>2024-02-02T00:48:34Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Fri, 02 Feb 2024 00:48:34</title><link href="https://novasparkxx.github.io/vite.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-02-02T00:48:34Z</published><updated>2024-02-02T00:48:34Z</updated><id>03f53a29-8712-4ee7-9c7d-11c7f9cdc131</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://imgproxy.nanxiongnandi.com/P_O89MPBYlhmFIfXN1-KWHdQIOZ40lkQcMHMZlMdWf8/w:1280/aHR0cHM6Ly9pbWcu/bmFueGlvbmduYW5k/aS5jb20vMjAyNDAx/L0J1a2hhbnNhblNl/b3VsLmpwZw.jpg" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/03f53a29-8712-4ee7-9c7d-11c7f9cdc131.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world, there have been several interesting developments. The Second Cup Coffee Company has introduced an innovative robot waiter to enhance the customer experience. This new addition aims to provide efficient and personalized service to customers, making their visit to the coffee shop more enjoyable.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the technology realm, there have been some informative articles. One discusses how to create modals with Rails and Hotwire, along with Tailwind CSS. This guide provides developers with step-by-step instructions on incorporating these tools to enhance the user interface and overall functionality of web applications.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Additionally, Nielsen and Nexstar have announced an agreement for local and national TV measurement services. This collaboration aims to provide accurate and comprehensive data on television viewership, enabling broadcasters and advertisers to make informed decisions regarding programming and advertising strategies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For those interested in eCommerce, there is an article on how to build an eCommerce website and integrate email notification using open source tools. This resource offers valuable insights and guidance for individuals or businesses looking to establish an online store and effectively communicate with customers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the field of technology, there is a brief history of DevOps and its link to cloud development environments. This article explores the evolution of DevOps practices and its integration with cloud computing, highlighting the benefits and challenges associated with this approach.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moving on to new tools, products, or projects, there is the introduction of CheerpJ 3.0. This WebAssembly JVM allows real-world applications to run directly in the browser, providing a seamless and efficient user experience. This advancement opens up new possibilities for web-based applications and expands the capabilities of browser-based software.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Furthermore, Azure OpenAI Service is being utilized to generate images with DALL-E in .NET. This integration of artificial intelligence and cloud computing enables developers to create and manipulate images using advanced algorithms, enhancing the creative and visual aspects of software development.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, there is the announcement of the first 'truly' open-source LLM (Language Learning Model) from AI2. This development aims to drive a critical shift in AI development by providing an accessible and collaborative platform for language learning research and innovation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;These recent developments showcase the continuous advancements in technology, customer service, and innovation across various industries.
    </summary></entry></feed>