<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Voyager</title><link href="https://novasparkxx.github.io/vite.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://novasparkxx.github.io/vite.xml</id><updated>2024-02-02T20:02:49Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>"Russian Artillery Shells from North Korea: Ukraine's Struggle for Supplies"&lt;br&gt;"Consider Function URLs Instead of Amazon API Gateway in 2024"&lt;br&gt;"Uno Platform 5.1 Release: Live Wizard, UI Controls, and Performance Boost"&lt;br&gt;"Mezmo Bolsters Sales Leadership with Chef and Apptio Hires"&lt;br&gt;"Grab ZBrush Alphas &amp; Brushes with 50% Discount"&lt;br&gt;"Water Usage by Quebec's Mining and Metal Industry Revealed"&lt;br&gt;"SAP Employees Feel 'Betrayed' by Radical Return-to-Office U-turn"&lt;br&gt;"H2O.ai Reduces Inferencing Cost with Snowflake Integration"&lt;br&gt;"The Dawn of AI Revolutionizing Voice Interaction"&lt;br&gt;"FAST Apps Outperform Viewer Attention Benchmarks for Linear TV and CTV"</title><link href="https://novasparkxx.github.io/vite.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-02-02T20:02:49Z</published><updated>2024-02-02T20:02:49Z</updated><id>fc5405e1-a8a9-48c8-8fe6-3bb6996e9af0</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://imgproxy.nanxiongnandi.com/P_O89MPBYlhmFIfXN1-KWHdQIOZ40lkQcMHMZlMdWf8/w:1280/aHR0cHM6Ly9pbWcu/bmFueGlvbmduYW5k/aS5jb20vMjAyNDAx/L0J1a2hhbnNhblNl/b3VsLmpwZw.jpg" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/fc5405e1-a8a9-48c8-8fe6-3bb6996e9af0.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent news, it has been reported that Russia is acquiring a million artillery shells from North Korea, according to Zelenskyy, the President of Ukraine. This development comes at a time when Ukraine is struggling to secure supplies from its own allies. The situation highlights the challenges Ukraine is facing in obtaining necessary resources for its defense. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the tech world, there have been several noteworthy developments. Amazon API Gateway is being questioned as a viable option for use in 2024, with a suggestion to consider Function URLs instead. This raises discussions about the future of API management and the potential alternatives that may emerge. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Uno Platform has released version 5.1, introducing a Live Wizard, new UI controls, and performance improvements. This update enhances the capabilities and user experience of the platform, providing developers with more tools to create cross-platform applications efficiently. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mezmo, a company specializing in sales, has strengthened its sales leadership by hiring new professionals from Chef and Apptio. This move aims to enhance the company's sales strategies and expand its market reach. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the creative industry, ZBrush is offering a 50% discount on a bundle of alphas and brushes, providing artists with a cost-effective opportunity to enhance their digital sculpting and painting workflows. This promotion enables artists to access a wide range of tools and resources to elevate their artistic creations. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On a different note, data has revealed that Quebec's mining and metal industry consumes billions of liters of water annually. This highlights the significant impact of these industries on water resources and raises concerns about sustainability and environmental conservation. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the corporate world, thousands of employees at SAP, a tech giant, have signed a petition expressing their feeling of being "betrayed" by the company's sudden reversal of its return-to-office plans. This demonstrates the challenges and tensions that arise when companies navigate the complexities of remote work and office policies. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;H2O.ai has made an announcement regarding a breakthrough in reducing the cost of inferencing through its integration with Snowflake. This development has the potential to revolutionize the field of artificial intelligence by making inferencing more cost-effective and accessible, opening up new possibilities for AI applications. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, data has shown that FAST apps outperform viewer attention benchmarks for linear TV and overall connected TV (CTV). This highlights the growing influence and effectiveness of FAST apps in capturing and retaining viewer attention, indicating a shift in consumer preferences towards digital streaming platforms. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In summary, the world has witnessed various developments ranging from geopolitical tensions to technological advancements. These news pieces shed light on the challenges faced by nations, the evolution of technology, and the impact of industries on the environment. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, the highlights include the Uno Platform 5.1 release, the discounted ZBrush alphas and brushes bundle, and the breakthrough in reducing the cost of inferencing with Snowflake integration by H2O.ai. These developments offer enhanced capabilities for developers, cost-effective resources for artists, and advancements in artificial intelligence.
    </summary></entry></feed>