<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Voyager</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/voyager.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/voyager.xml</id><updated>2024-05-30T16:05:48Z</updated><subtitle>Welcome to "Voyager," the podcast where the frontiers of technology, cybersecurity, and scientific discovery converge. Each week, we embark on a digital odyssey through the vast and ever-evolving landscape of the internet to bring you the most intriguing and vital stories from the realms of tech and science.

In "Voyager," we delve deep into the latest advancements in technology, from groundbreaking gadgets and innovations to the software shaping our digital world. We unravel the complex and fascinating world of cybersecurity, keeping you informed about the latest threats, defenses, and trends that matter in our increasingly connected lives.

But our journey doesn't stop there. We also traverse the exciting universe of scientific discovery, bringing you cutting-edge news, interviews with thought leaders, and insights into the research that's changing our understanding of the world and beyond.

Whether you're a tech enthusiast, a cybersecurity professional, or just curious about the scientific phenomena shaping our future, "Voyager" is your guide through the complex web of modern innovation. Join us as we explore the most compelling stories at the intersection of technology, cybersecurity, and science – stories that inform, inspire, and ignite the imagination.

Subscribe to "Voyager" and stay ahead of the curve in this fast-paced digital age. New episodes drop every week, filled with expert analysis, engaging discussions, and a passion for the marvels of the internet era. Set sail with us on this journey of discovery and exploration – into the heart of what's next.
</subtitle><entry><title>The AI Revolution: Unveiling the Future of Global Banking and Cross-Border Payments</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/voyager.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-05-30T16:05:48Z</published><updated>2024-05-30T16:05:48Z</updated><id>63fc9783-8ba7-41e5-9e85-69f0aacf7255</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/voyager.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/63fc9783-8ba7-41e5-9e85-69f0aacf7255.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of technology and finance, several significant developments have taken place recently. Swift, in collaboration with global banks, has launched AI pilots to combat cross-border payments fraud, aiming to enhance security and efficiency in financial transactions. However, concerns have been raised about the environmental impact of AI, as an article highlights how AI models like ChatGPT consume resources at alarming rates. On a positive note, Google has announced a $2 billion investment in Malaysia, primarily focusing on AI and establishing its first data center in the country. This move is expected to boost Malaysia's technological infrastructure and promote AI advancements. Another noteworthy development is the introduction of Large Language Models-Guided Dynamic Adaptation (LLM-DA), a machine learning method that enables reasoning on temporal knowledge graphs (TKGs). This innovation has the potential to revolutionize the way we analyze and utilize data. Trustly, a fintech company backed by BlackRock, has reported a significant increase in profits, but an IPO is still at least a year away. Singapore is actively promoting the establishment of green data centers to meet the growing demand for AI while minimizing energy consumption. In the corporate world, C3.ai has exceeded sales estimates in Q1, leading to a 13.7% jump in its stock value. Additionally, NCino has witnessed a surge in demand for cloud banking services, driven by the integration of AI technology. Lastly, MBZUAI's AI model, K2-65B, has made its global debut, redefining sustainability and performance in the field of artificial intelligence. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, the introduction of LLM-DA stands out as a significant advancement in machine learning. This method allows for effective reasoning on temporal knowledge graphs, enabling more accurate analysis and utilization of data. Additionally, the global debut of MBZUAI's AI model, K2-65B, showcases the continuous progress in sustainable AI solutions. This model aims to redefine performance standards while prioritizing environmental sustainability. These developments highlight the ongoing efforts to enhance AI capabilities and address the challenges associated with its implementation.
    </summary></entry></feed>