<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Voyager</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/voyager.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/voyager.xml</id><updated>2024-02-19T08:04:19Z</updated><subtitle>Welcome to "Voyager," the podcast where the frontiers of technology, cybersecurity, and scientific discovery converge. Each week, we embark on a digital odyssey through the vast and ever-evolving landscape of the internet to bring you the most intriguing and vital stories from the realms of tech and science.

In "Voyager," we delve deep into the latest advancements in technology, from groundbreaking gadgets and innovations to the software shaping our digital world. We unravel the complex and fascinating world of cybersecurity, keeping you informed about the latest threats, defenses, and trends that matter in our increasingly connected lives.

But our journey doesn't stop there. We also traverse the exciting universe of scientific discovery, bringing you cutting-edge news, interviews with thought leaders, and insights into the research that's changing our understanding of the world and beyond.

Whether you're a tech enthusiast, a cybersecurity professional, or just curious about the scientific phenomena shaping our future, "Voyager" is your guide through the complex web of modern innovation. Join us as we explore the most compelling stories at the intersection of technology, cybersecurity, and science – stories that inform, inspire, and ignite the imagination.

Subscribe to "Voyager" and stay ahead of the curve in this fast-paced digital age. New episodes drop every week, filled with expert analysis, engaging discussions, and a passion for the marvels of the internet era. Set sail with us on this journey of discovery and exploration – into the heart of what's next.
</subtitle><entry><title>1. "Cautious Commands: Navigating the `curl|bash` World Safely"&lt;br&gt;2. "From Soldier to Corporate: Breaking Stereotypes about Veterans"&lt;br&gt;3. "AI in K-12 Schools: Untapped Potential and Unpreparedness"&lt;br&gt;4. "Nebula and the Mesh VPN Race: Exploring the Alternatives"&lt;br&gt;5. "Vue 3 Step by Step: Mastering Composition API &amp; TypeScript"&lt;br&gt;6. "Non-Coder's Guide: Keeping Skills Sharp and Preventing Atrophy"&lt;br&gt;7. "Pandas Power Move: Merging Data Frames with Nearest Match"&lt;br&gt;8. "Guardrails AI: Revolutionizing LLM Reliability with Seed Funding"&lt;br&gt;9. "Sony's Struggles: Beyond PS5 Sales, the Games Margin Crisis"&lt;br&gt;10. "Além dos Templates: A Critique of Clean Architecture and Pragmatic Software Design"</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/voyager.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-02-19T08:04:19Z</published><updated>2024-02-19T08:04:19Z</updated><id>7e7d9a9a-9c4c-4301-8fd3-73c492a21e7c</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/voyager.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/7e7d9a9a-9c4c-4301-8fd3-73c492a21e7c.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world today, it is important to maintain a healthy sense of caution whenever running a `curl|bash` command. This caution is necessary to ensure the security and integrity of our systems and data. Additionally, there is a growing concern about the negative perceptions people have of veterans, which can make it challenging for them to transition into corporate roles after leaving the army. This issue highlights the need for greater understanding and support for veterans in the workforce.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A recent survey has revealed that K-12 schools are unprepared to manage the risks and capture the benefits of artificial intelligence (AI). As AI becomes more prevalent in various industries, it is crucial for educational institutions to adapt and equip themselves with the necessary tools and knowledge to effectively utilize AI in the classroom. This survey emphasizes the need for investment in AI education and training for educators.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the realm of technology, Nebula, a mesh VPN, may not be the fastest option available, but it is still a viable choice among other alternatives. This highlights the importance of considering various factors, such as security and reliability, when choosing a VPN service.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For those interested in learning Vue 3, a new book titled "Vue 3 Step by Step: with Composition API &amp; TypeScript" is set to be released soon. This book aims to provide a comprehensive guide to mastering Vue 3, utilizing the Composition API and TypeScript. It offers an opportunity for individuals to enhance their coding skills and stay up-to-date with the latest developments in Vue.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Even if one does not engage in coding, it is essential to keep skills sharp and prevent them from atrophying. There are various ways to achieve this, such as staying informed about industry trends, attending workshops or webinars, and seeking opportunities to apply knowledge in practical scenarios. Continuous learning and staying curious are key to maintaining skills in any field.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the world of data analysis, the question of how to merge data frames by the nearest match in Pandas arises. The solution lies in using the merge_asof function, which allows for merging data frames based on the closest match of a key column. This tool provides a valuable resource for data analysts and researchers working with large datasets.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the realm of AI development, Guardrails AI has secured $7.5 million in seed funding to solve the LLM (Language and Learning Models) reliability problem. This funding will enable Guardrails AI to develop innovative solutions that address the challenges faced by AI developers in ensuring the reliability and accuracy of their models. This project showcases the growing investment and interest in AI development and the need for robust and trustworthy AI systems.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On a different note, Sony has experienced a significant financial setback, with a $10 billion plunge in its stock value due to lower-than-expected sales of the PS5. However, a more significant concern for the company is its near decade-low games margin. This highlights the need for Sony to reassess its gaming strategy and find ways to improve profitability in the highly competitive gaming industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, an article titled "Além dos Templates: Uma Crítica Construtiva à Arquitetura Limpa e a Adaptação Pragmática no Design de Software" explores a constructive critique of clean architecture and pragmatic adaptation in software design. This article delves into the complexities and challenges of software architecture and offers insights into alternative approaches and perspectives.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, these news highlights the importance of caution in technology, the need for support and understanding for veterans, the challenges and opportunities presented by AI in education, the continuous learning and skill development in various fields, the advancements in data analysis tools, the investment in AI development, the challenges faced by companies in the gaming industry, and the ongoing discussions and critiques in software design.
    </summary></entry></feed>