<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Voyager</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/voyager.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/voyager.xml</id><updated>2024-06-02T16:05:20Z</updated><subtitle>Welcome to "Voyager," the podcast where the frontiers of technology, cybersecurity, and scientific discovery converge. Each week, we embark on a digital odyssey through the vast and ever-evolving landscape of the internet to bring you the most intriguing and vital stories from the realms of tech and science.

In "Voyager," we delve deep into the latest advancements in technology, from groundbreaking gadgets and innovations to the software shaping our digital world. We unravel the complex and fascinating world of cybersecurity, keeping you informed about the latest threats, defenses, and trends that matter in our increasingly connected lives.

But our journey doesn't stop there. We also traverse the exciting universe of scientific discovery, bringing you cutting-edge news, interviews with thought leaders, and insights into the research that's changing our understanding of the world and beyond.

Whether you're a tech enthusiast, a cybersecurity professional, or just curious about the scientific phenomena shaping our future, "Voyager" is your guide through the complex web of modern innovation. Join us as we explore the most compelling stories at the intersection of technology, cybersecurity, and science – stories that inform, inspire, and ignite the imagination.

Subscribe to "Voyager" and stay ahead of the curve in this fast-paced digital age. New episodes drop every week, filled with expert analysis, engaging discussions, and a passion for the marvels of the internet era. Set sail with us on this journey of discovery and exploration – into the heart of what's next.
</subtitle><entry><title>AI Stalemate: Democrats' Quest for Agreement</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/voyager.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-06-02T16:05:20Z</published><updated>2024-06-02T16:05:20Z</updated><id>7948afa7-e3b5-4f9b-9fd8-0035c3070de7</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/voyager.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/7948afa7-e3b5-4f9b-9fd8-0035c3070de7.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of politics, Democrats have been pushing for an agreement on the use of artificial intelligence (AI). However, their efforts have been unsuccessful as no progress has been made in this regard. This news comes from ABC News, highlighting the lack of consensus on AI among Democrats.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the technology front, there is a guide available on how to package and deploy a Lambda function as a container image. This development can be useful for developers and tech enthusiasts who are interested in utilizing Lambda functions in their projects. The guide provides step-by-step instructions on how to effectively package and deploy these functions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the field of legal models, a study conducted by Stanford HAI reveals that legal models hallucinate in at least one out of six benchmarking queries. This finding raises concerns about the reliability and accuracy of AI-powered legal models. It emphasizes the need for further research and improvements in this area to ensure the effectiveness of AI in legal applications.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a surprising turn of events, a viral phone call between Swati Maliwal and YouTuber Dhruv Rathee has been revealed to be AI-generated. This incident highlights the advancements in AI technology, where AI algorithms can mimic human voices and conversations convincingly. It raises questions about the potential misuse of AI-generated content and the need for regulations in this domain.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the financial sector, Morningstar reports that there are five undervalued energy stocks that can benefit from the AI data center demand boom. This indicates the growing reliance on AI technology and the subsequent need for data centers to support its operations. Investors looking to capitalize on this trend may find these energy stocks to be promising investment opportunities.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bhashini, a company, has launched a program called 'Be our Sahayogi' focused on multilingual AI innovation in voice technology. This initiative aims to foster innovation in AI voice technology, particularly in multilingual contexts. It provides a platform for individuals and organizations to contribute to the development of AI-powered voice solutions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the realm of AI governance, the European Union (EU) has set a global standard with the introduction of the Artificial Intelligence Act. This act aims to regulate and manage AI technologies, ensuring ethical and responsible use. It signifies the EU's commitment to establishing guidelines and frameworks for the development and deployment of AI systems.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, a developer shares their progress on building two minigames and solving four Leetcode challenges over a span of three days (Day 39-41). This showcases the dedication and skill of developers in honing their programming abilities and tackling coding challenges.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, these news pieces shed light on the current state of AI in various domains, highlighting both the advancements and challenges associated with this technology.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Tools, Products, or Projects:&lt;br&gt;- Guide on packaging and deploying Lambda functions as container images&lt;br&gt;- Bhashini's 'Be our Sahayogi' program for multilingual AI innovation focused on voice technology&lt;br&gt;- The introduction of the Artificial Intelligence Act by the EU for AI governance and regulation.
    </summary></entry></feed>