<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Voyager</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/voyager.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/voyager.xml</id><updated>2024-08-16T16:05:21Z</updated><subtitle>Welcome to "Voyager," the podcast where the frontiers of technology, cybersecurity, and scientific discovery converge. Each week, we embark on a digital odyssey through the vast and ever-evolving landscape of the internet to bring you the most intriguing and vital stories from the realms of tech and science.

In "Voyager," we delve deep into the latest advancements in technology, from groundbreaking gadgets and innovations to the software shaping our digital world. We unravel the complex and fascinating world of cybersecurity, keeping you informed about the latest threats, defenses, and trends that matter in our increasingly connected lives.

But our journey doesn't stop there. We also traverse the exciting universe of scientific discovery, bringing you cutting-edge news, interviews with thought leaders, and insights into the research that's changing our understanding of the world and beyond.

Whether you're a tech enthusiast, a cybersecurity professional, or just curious about the scientific phenomena shaping our future, "Voyager" is your guide through the complex web of modern innovation. Join us as we explore the most compelling stories at the intersection of technology, cybersecurity, and science – stories that inform, inspire, and ignite the imagination.

Subscribe to "Voyager" and stay ahead of the curve in this fast-paced digital age. New episodes drop every week, filled with expert analysis, engaging discussions, and a passion for the marvels of the internet era. Set sail with us on this journey of discovery and exploration – into the heart of what's next.
</subtitle><entry><title>The AI Invasion: San Francisco Fights Back Against Deepfake Pornography</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/voyager.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-08-16T16:05:21Z</published><updated>2024-08-16T16:05:21Z</updated><id>fa069763-f08b-4f5a-a31d-068e15f14979</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/voyager.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/fa069763-f08b-4f5a-a31d-068e15f14979.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent news, San Francisco has taken legal action against AI deepfake pornography sites, as they have seen a harmful trend of undressing women. The city attorney has filed a lawsuit against these sites, which have reportedly received a staggering 200 million visits. This move aims to address the negative impact of deepfake pornography and protect the rights and privacy of individuals. Meanwhile, Forbes explores the future of artificial intelligence and ponders where it will take us. The article delves into the potential advancements and implications of AI in various industries. On the other hand, director Ridley Scott, known for his work on "Gladiator II," has backtracked on his previous statement calling AI a "technical hydrogen bomb." He now seems to have a more nuanced perspective on the subject. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, one notable development is the I-SHEEP project. This project focuses on the self-alignment of LLM (Language Model) from scratch through an iterative self-enhancement paradigm. It aims to enhance the capabilities and performance of language models through a unique approach. Additionally, there has been a regulatory backlash against chatbots in the banking sector. Despite this, banks are finding value in their use and are exploring ways to leverage chatbots effectively. This highlights the ongoing debate surrounding the use of AI in customer service and the need for appropriate regulations. Furthermore, publishers have reported "negligible" traffic impact from Google AI Overviews. This suggests that the introduction of AI-driven overviews by Google has not significantly affected publishers' website traffic. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the world of finance, Micron Technology is identified as an important AI stock to watch. With the increasing integration of AI in various industries, Micron Technology stands out as a company that investors should pay attention to. Additionally, former Google CEO Eric Schmidt has identified Nvidia as a big winner in the field of AI. He advises investors to consider Nvidia when making decisions in the stock market. Finally, Cointelegraph reports that the San Francisco city attorney has sued sites that use AI to "undress" women. This legal action aims to combat the harmful effects of deepfake pornography and protect individuals from privacy violations.
    </summary></entry></feed>