<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Voyager</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/voyager.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/voyager.xml</id><updated>2024-04-07T16:03:44Z</updated><subtitle>Welcome to "Voyager," the podcast where the frontiers of technology, cybersecurity, and scientific discovery converge. Each week, we embark on a digital odyssey through the vast and ever-evolving landscape of the internet to bring you the most intriguing and vital stories from the realms of tech and science.

In "Voyager," we delve deep into the latest advancements in technology, from groundbreaking gadgets and innovations to the software shaping our digital world. We unravel the complex and fascinating world of cybersecurity, keeping you informed about the latest threats, defenses, and trends that matter in our increasingly connected lives.

But our journey doesn't stop there. We also traverse the exciting universe of scientific discovery, bringing you cutting-edge news, interviews with thought leaders, and insights into the research that's changing our understanding of the world and beyond.

Whether you're a tech enthusiast, a cybersecurity professional, or just curious about the scientific phenomena shaping our future, "Voyager" is your guide through the complex web of modern innovation. Join us as we explore the most compelling stories at the intersection of technology, cybersecurity, and science – stories that inform, inspire, and ignite the imagination.

Subscribe to "Voyager" and stay ahead of the curve in this fast-paced digital age. New episodes drop every week, filled with expert analysis, engaging discussions, and a passion for the marvels of the internet era. Set sail with us on this journey of discovery and exploration – into the heart of what's next.
</subtitle><entry><title>"The AI Revolution: Partnering with Eagleman for Scientific Discovery"</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/voyager.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-04-07T16:03:44Z</published><updated>2024-04-07T16:03:44Z</updated><id>b7818046-2db3-4268-8edf-df94432fd0dd</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/voyager.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/b7818046-2db3-4268-8edf-df94432fd0dd.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of scientific discovery, renowned neuroscientist David Eagleman envisions artificial intelligence (AI) as a valuable partner. According to yTech, Eagleman believes that AI can assist scientists in uncovering new insights and accelerating the pace of research. This collaboration between humans and AI could potentially revolutionize various fields of study.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Meanwhile, Avery Ching, the co-founder and CTO of Aptos, recently attended the OKX Web3 Night to discuss the latest developments of the Move language on the Aptos platform. This highlights the continuous progress being made in the field of programming languages and their applications.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The debate between MIT and Harvard as the better university for artificial intelligence continues. Analytics Insight explores the strengths and weaknesses of both institutions, shedding light on the ongoing competition in the AI education landscape.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the realm of social media and marketing, virtual models are posing a challenge to human influencers. Barron's reports that AI-generated virtual models are gaining popularity and attracting brands, potentially disrupting the influencer industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Xiaomi, the Chinese tech giant, is facing an issue with its electric vehicle (EV) delivery. The wait time for Xiaomi EVs has extended to more than five months, indicating high demand and potential supply chain challenges.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Jerusalem Post addresses the challenges of antisemitism in the age of AI. As AI technology becomes more prevalent, there is a need to address its potential misuse and ensure that it does not contribute to hate speech or discrimination.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;OpenAI CEO Sam Altman and former Apple chief designer Jony Ive are seeking $1 billion in funding for what is being dubbed the "iPhone of AI." The Times of India reports that this ambitious project aims to create a groundbreaking AI device that could potentially revolutionize the way we interact with technology.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a recent edition of The Dallas Morning News, readers express their opinions on various topics, including natural gas, diversity, equity, and inclusion (DEI) policies, voting, immigration, and AI. This highlights the ongoing discussions and debates surrounding these important issues.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;However, not all advancements in AI are without challenges. Blind internet users are struggling with error-prone AI aids, as reported by the Financial Times. This highlights the importance of developing AI technologies that are accessible and inclusive for all users.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, Jony Ive, known for his design work at Apple, is reportedly working on a new AI device that will not resemble a traditional phone. Android Authority speculates that this device could potentially rival the Humane AI Pin, showcasing the continuous innovation and competition in the AI hardware market.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Tools, Products, or Projects:&lt;br&gt;- The Move language on the Aptos platform showcases the latest developments in programming languages and their applications.&lt;br&gt;- OpenAI's ambitious project, seeking $1 billion in funding, aims to create a groundbreaking AI device that could revolutionize human-technology interaction.&lt;br&gt;- Jony Ive's new AI device, which does not resemble a phone, could potentially rival the Humane AI Pin, introducing new possibilities in AI hardware design.
    </summary></entry></feed>