<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Voyager</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/voyager.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/voyager.xml</id><updated>2024-02-15T08:05:29Z</updated><subtitle>Welcome to "Voyager," the podcast where the frontiers of technology, cybersecurity, and scientific discovery converge. Each week, we embark on a digital odyssey through the vast and ever-evolving landscape of the internet to bring you the most intriguing and vital stories from the realms of tech and science.

In "Voyager," we delve deep into the latest advancements in technology, from groundbreaking gadgets and innovations to the software shaping our digital world. We unravel the complex and fascinating world of cybersecurity, keeping you informed about the latest threats, defenses, and trends that matter in our increasingly connected lives.

But our journey doesn't stop there. We also traverse the exciting universe of scientific discovery, bringing you cutting-edge news, interviews with thought leaders, and insights into the research that's changing our understanding of the world and beyond.

Whether you're a tech enthusiast, a cybersecurity professional, or just curious about the scientific phenomena shaping our future, "Voyager" is your guide through the complex web of modern innovation. Join us as we explore the most compelling stories at the intersection of technology, cybersecurity, and science – stories that inform, inspire, and ignite the imagination.

Subscribe to "Voyager" and stay ahead of the curve in this fast-paced digital age. New episodes drop every week, filled with expert analysis, engaging discussions, and a passion for the marvels of the internet era. Set sail with us on this journey of discovery and exploration – into the heart of what's next.
</subtitle><entry><title>"The AI Showdown: Otter.ai Takes on Microsoft Copilot and Redefines Meeting Intelligence"</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/voyager.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-02-15T08:05:29Z</published><updated>2024-02-15T08:05:29Z</updated><id>f9e37f53-9788-4288-874c-c52ad8521ee3</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/voyager.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/f9e37f53-9788-4288-874c-c52ad8521ee3.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of AI, Otter.ai has taken on the challenge of redefining AI meeting intelligence with the launch of Meeting GenAI. This new tool aims to outpace Microsoft Copilot and provide advanced features for analyzing and understanding meetings. Meanwhile, Menlo Security has found that 55 percent of generative AI inputs contain sensitive information, highlighting the need for better data protection measures. Anvil is empowering product teams with AI webform translations, making software development more seamless and efficient. KaarTech has unveiled KTern.AI, an AI-first approach for S/4HANA transformations, aiming to drive global transformation in this field. In the tech world, there is a discussion on how to set up an EAS local build on GitHub Actions without having to pay for it. The Electronic Frontier Foundation (EFF) is urging the court to strike down age estimation in California while protecting consumer privacy. In space news, Varda Space Industries has received approval to bring its drug manufacturing spacecraft back to Earth, marking a significant milestone in the industry. On the social media front, Bluesky and Mastodon users are engaged in a fight that could shape the future of social media platforms. Lastly, Vali Cyber has announced early access to the first-ever runtime security platform for ESXi, providing enhanced security for virtualized environments. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, Cineverse has partnered with Google Cloud to launch a conversational AI-powered search and discovery tool. This innovative tool aims to enhance the search experience by leveraging AI technology to provide more accurate and relevant results. With its conversational capabilities, users can engage in natural language conversations to find the information they need quickly and efficiently. This project has the potential to revolutionize the way people search for and discover content online.
    </summary></entry></feed>