<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Voyager</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/voyager.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/voyager.xml</id><updated>2024-02-08T20:03:01Z</updated><subtitle>Welcome to "Voyager," the podcast where the frontiers of technology, cybersecurity, and scientific discovery converge. Each week, we embark on a digital odyssey through the vast and ever-evolving landscape of the internet to bring you the most intriguing and vital stories from the realms of tech and science.

In "Voyager," we delve deep into the latest advancements in technology, from groundbreaking gadgets and innovations to the software shaping our digital world. We unravel the complex and fascinating world of cybersecurity, keeping you informed about the latest threats, defenses, and trends that matter in our increasingly connected lives.

But our journey doesn't stop there. We also traverse the exciting universe of scientific discovery, bringing you cutting-edge news, interviews with thought leaders, and insights into the research that's changing our understanding of the world and beyond.

Whether you're a tech enthusiast, a cybersecurity professional, or just curious about the scientific phenomena shaping our future, "Voyager" is your guide through the complex web of modern innovation. Join us as we explore the most compelling stories at the intersection of technology, cybersecurity, and science – stories that inform, inspire, and ignite the imagination.

Subscribe to "Voyager" and stay ahead of the curve in this fast-paced digital age. New episodes drop every week, filled with expert analysis, engaging discussions, and a passion for the marvels of the internet era. Set sail with us on this journey of discovery and exploration – into the heart of what's next.
</subtitle><entry><title>Breaking the Mold: Exploring Homogeneity in Functional Data Expansion and Resistive Memories&lt;br&gt;Trustworthy AI: LF AI &amp; Data Joins NIST’s U.S. AI Safety Institute Consortium&lt;br&gt;Putting Words in Your Mouth: Microsoft's Patent for Revolutionary Speech Technology&lt;br&gt;Unlocking the Power of Applied AI: MindSpark's Certification and Free Resources for Educators&lt;br&gt;Global AI Acceleration: Kalray and Arm's Collaboration in Data Processing Unit Solutions&lt;br&gt;Next-Level Commuting: Inside the Design of MTA's High-Tech New Subway Trains&lt;br&gt;Game Development Revolution: Room 8 Group's Open Source Tool REI&lt;br&gt;Empowering Innovation: Atlas Secures $4.5 Million Grant for 3D Generative AI&lt;br&gt;Simulating Global Impact: DMS Academy's NASPAA 2024 Showcase&lt;br&gt;Investing in AI Chipmakers: The Untapped Potential in the US Market</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/voyager.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-02-08T20:03:01Z</published><updated>2024-02-08T20:03:01Z</updated><id>76260546-3bb8-4379-9751-0ce4b98a0e55</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/voyager.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/76260546-3bb8-4379-9751-0ce4b98a0e55.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of technology and artificial intelligence, several significant developments have taken place recently. One such development is the homogeneity problem for basis expansion of functional data with applications to resistive memories. This advancement aims to address the issue of homogeneity in expanding the basis of functional data, particularly in resistive memories.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another noteworthy event is LF AI &amp; Data joining NIST's U.S. AI Safety Institute Consortium. This collaboration aims to shape the future of trustworthy AI by bringing together industry experts and researchers to ensure the safety and reliability of AI systems.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the realm of patents, Microsoft has sought a patent for technology that can put words into your mouth. This innovation could potentially have various applications, including speech synthesis and voice assistants.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For those interested in learning applied AI, MindSpark has introduced a new certification program and free resources for educators. This initiative aims to provide individuals with the necessary skills and knowledge to excel in the field of applied AI.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of collaborations, Kalray and Arm have joined forces to develop global AI acceleration data processing unit solutions. This partnership aims to enhance the efficiency and performance of AI data processing units on a global scale.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Moving on to transportation, the MTA has designed new subway trains that are super bright, extremely spacious, and high-tech. These trains incorporate advanced technology to provide a better commuting experience for passengers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the gaming industry, Room 8 Group's R&amp;D unit has unveiled REI, an open-source tool that enhances game porting and development. This tool aims to simplify the process of porting games across different platforms and improve the overall game development experience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Atlas, a company backed by Square Enix, has secured a $4.5 million grant to power 3D generative AI innovation. This funding will support the development of advanced AI algorithms and technologies for creating realistic 3D models.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the field of education, DMS Academy's simulations are set to make a global impact at NASPAA 2024. These simulations aim to provide students with practical and immersive learning experiences, preparing them for real-world challenges.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, despite the growing need for AI chipmakers in the United States, they are not receiving significant investor support. This lack of investor love poses challenges for AI chipmakers in terms of funding and growth.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, these recent developments highlight the continuous advancements and innovations in the world of technology, artificial intelligence, and education. These advancements aim to improve various aspects of our lives, from transportation to gaming and education. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Extra Section: New Tools, Products, or Projects:&lt;br&gt;1. Homogeneity problem solution for basis expansion of functional data with applications to resistive memories.&lt;br&gt;2. Microsoft's patent for technology to put words into your mouth.&lt;br&gt;3. MindSpark's new certification program and free resources for learning applied AI.&lt;br&gt;4. Kalray and Arm's collaboration for global AI acceleration data processing unit solutions.&lt;br&gt;5. MTA's high-tech new subway trains with advanced design features.&lt;br&gt;6. Room 8 Group's R&amp;D unit unveils REI, an open-source tool for game porting and development.&lt;br&gt;7. Atlas secures a $4.5 million grant for 3D generative AI innovation.&lt;br&gt;8. DMS Academy's simulations making a global impact at NASPAA 2024.&lt;br&gt;9. Challenges faced by US-based AI chipmakers in attracting investor support.
    </summary></entry></feed>