<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Voyager</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/voyager.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/voyager.xml</id><updated>2024-09-07T16:06:36Z</updated><subtitle>Welcome to "Voyager," the podcast where the frontiers of technology, cybersecurity, and scientific discovery converge. Each week, we embark on a digital odyssey through the vast and ever-evolving landscape of the internet to bring you the most intriguing and vital stories from the realms of tech and science.

In "Voyager," we delve deep into the latest advancements in technology, from groundbreaking gadgets and innovations to the software shaping our digital world. We unravel the complex and fascinating world of cybersecurity, keeping you informed about the latest threats, defenses, and trends that matter in our increasingly connected lives.

But our journey doesn't stop there. We also traverse the exciting universe of scientific discovery, bringing you cutting-edge news, interviews with thought leaders, and insights into the research that's changing our understanding of the world and beyond.

Whether you're a tech enthusiast, a cybersecurity professional, or just curious about the scientific phenomena shaping our future, "Voyager" is your guide through the complex web of modern innovation. Join us as we explore the most compelling stories at the intersection of technology, cybersecurity, and science – stories that inform, inspire, and ignite the imagination.

Subscribe to "Voyager" and stay ahead of the curve in this fast-paced digital age. New episodes drop every week, filled with expert analysis, engaging discussions, and a passion for the marvels of the internet era. Set sail with us on this journey of discovery and exploration – into the heart of what's next.
</subtitle><entry><title>The AI Election: Unmasking Dizzying Deepfakes and Personalized Propaganda</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/voyager.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-09-07T16:06:36Z</published><updated>2024-09-07T16:06:36Z</updated><id>0778c0c5-df48-4a16-ac1a-9ee316967683</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/voyager.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/0778c0c5-df48-4a16-ac1a-9ee316967683.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of AI, deepfakes and personalized propaganda have become a concerning issue, as highlighted in Vanity Fair's article titled "Dizzying Deepfakes and Personalized Propaganda: Welcome to the AI Election." The piece discusses how AI technology has been used by Senator David Pocock to create deepfakes of politicians Anthony Albanese and Peter Dutton, calling for a ban ahead of the upcoming election. This development has raised concerns about the potential misuse of AI in political campaigns. Meanwhile, Apple's iPhone 16 AI features have been the talk of the town, with CNET providing an in-depth overview of Apple Intelligence. The Department of Defense is also keeping up with rapidly emerging technology through its AI Security Center, ensuring that they stay at the forefront of AI advancements. In the open-source community, a new AI model called DeepSeek-V2.5 has been released by DeepSeek-AI. This cutting-edge model boasts a staggering 238B parameter capacity, featuring a Mixture of Experts (MoE) with 160 experts, advanced chat, coding, and an impressive 128k context length capability. Additionally, Inc. reports on a breakthrough in AI technology, as a new open-source AI model has been developed that can check itself and avoid hallucinations, enhancing its reliability and accuracy. On a different note, Bill Gates has revealed his most frequent use of AI, which is covered by Yahoo! Voices. Lastly, TIME Magazine has recognized the contributions of Prof. Ben Zhao by naming him to their TIME100 AI list, highlighting his significant impact in the field of AI. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, the release of DeepSeek-V2.5 by DeepSeek-AI stands out. This advanced AI model offers a multitude of features, including a Mixture of Experts (MoE) with 160 experts, advanced chat capabilities, coding capabilities, and an impressive 128k context length capability. With its cutting-edge technology, DeepSeek-V2.5 is set to revolutionize the AI landscape. Additionally, the development of an open-source AI model that can check itself and avoid hallucinations, as reported by Inc., marks a significant breakthrough in AI reliability and accuracy. These advancements in AI technology showcase the continuous progress being made in the field and the potential for further innovation in the future.
    </summary></entry></feed>