<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Voyager</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/voyager.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/voyager.xml</id><updated>2024-05-23T16:04:54Z</updated><subtitle>Welcome to "Voyager," the podcast where the frontiers of technology, cybersecurity, and scientific discovery converge. Each week, we embark on a digital odyssey through the vast and ever-evolving landscape of the internet to bring you the most intriguing and vital stories from the realms of tech and science.

In "Voyager," we delve deep into the latest advancements in technology, from groundbreaking gadgets and innovations to the software shaping our digital world. We unravel the complex and fascinating world of cybersecurity, keeping you informed about the latest threats, defenses, and trends that matter in our increasingly connected lives.

But our journey doesn't stop there. We also traverse the exciting universe of scientific discovery, bringing you cutting-edge news, interviews with thought leaders, and insights into the research that's changing our understanding of the world and beyond.

Whether you're a tech enthusiast, a cybersecurity professional, or just curious about the scientific phenomena shaping our future, "Voyager" is your guide through the complex web of modern innovation. Join us as we explore the most compelling stories at the intersection of technology, cybersecurity, and science – stories that inform, inspire, and ignite the imagination.

Subscribe to "Voyager" and stay ahead of the curve in this fast-paced digital age. New episodes drop every week, filled with expert analysis, engaging discussions, and a passion for the marvels of the internet era. Set sail with us on this journey of discovery and exploration – into the heart of what's next.
</subtitle><entry><title>AI Unleashed: OpenAI's Media Strategy and the Sleeping Regulators</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/voyager.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-05-23T16:04:54Z</published><updated>2024-05-23T16:04:54Z</updated><id>9b3d7e3a-53d1-48b1-a9e0-f131c49d358a</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/voyager.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/9b3d7e3a-53d1-48b1-a9e0-f131c49d358a.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of technology and artificial intelligence, OpenAI has made a significant partnership with News Corp, a major media company. This collaboration raises questions about OpenAI's media strategy, as regulators seem to be slow in addressing the implications of such a partnership. Meanwhile, Core42's Arabic LLM, a language learning model, is now accessible on Microsoft Azure, providing users with a valuable tool for language acquisition. Nvidia, a leading AI company, has reported impressive earnings that surpass expectations, thanks to the soaring demand for AI technology. As AI continues to thrive, the first part of "The Ultimate Guide to Finding Outliers in Your Time-Series Data" has been released, offering valuable insights into analyzing data. On the governmental front, the "First federal CIO" has provided three reality checks on the implementation of AI in healthcare. Additionally, the Department of Defense's AI Chief is determined to further enhance capabilities for the warfighter. However, Baidu's CEO believes that achieving artificial general intelligence is still more than a decade away. In other news, concerns have been raised about Microsoft's UAE deal potentially transferring crucial U.S. chips and AI technology abroad. Finally, Nvidia's profits continue to soar, indicating that the AI boom shows no signs of slowing down.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, Core42's Arabic LLM on Microsoft Azure stands out as a valuable language learning model. This tool provides users with the opportunity to enhance their Arabic language skills efficiently. Additionally, the release of "The Ultimate Guide to Finding Outliers in Your Time-Series Data" offers a new resource for data analysts to identify and analyze anomalies in their datasets. These tools and projects contribute to the advancement of AI technology and its applications in various fields.
    </summary></entry></feed>