<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Voyager</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/voyager.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/voyager.xml</id><updated>2024-06-12T16:06:02Z</updated><subtitle>Welcome to "Voyager," the podcast where the frontiers of technology, cybersecurity, and scientific discovery converge. Each week, we embark on a digital odyssey through the vast and ever-evolving landscape of the internet to bring you the most intriguing and vital stories from the realms of tech and science.

In "Voyager," we delve deep into the latest advancements in technology, from groundbreaking gadgets and innovations to the software shaping our digital world. We unravel the complex and fascinating world of cybersecurity, keeping you informed about the latest threats, defenses, and trends that matter in our increasingly connected lives.

But our journey doesn't stop there. We also traverse the exciting universe of scientific discovery, bringing you cutting-edge news, interviews with thought leaders, and insights into the research that's changing our understanding of the world and beyond.

Whether you're a tech enthusiast, a cybersecurity professional, or just curious about the scientific phenomena shaping our future, "Voyager" is your guide through the complex web of modern innovation. Join us as we explore the most compelling stories at the intersection of technology, cybersecurity, and science – stories that inform, inspire, and ignite the imagination.

Subscribe to "Voyager" and stay ahead of the curve in this fast-paced digital age. New episodes drop every week, filled with expert analysis, engaging discussions, and a passion for the marvels of the internet era. Set sail with us on this journey of discovery and exploration – into the heart of what's next.
</subtitle><entry><title>Tech Talk with Carolyn Duby: Insights from a Field CTO and Cyber Security Expert</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/voyager.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-06-12T16:06:02Z</published><updated>2024-06-12T16:06:02Z</updated><id>b442851e-775c-4e69-9172-498f4422d744</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/voyager.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/b442851e-775c-4e69-9172-498f4422d744.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of technology and cybersecurity, there have been several interesting developments. Carolyn Duby, the Field CTO and Cyber Security GTM Lead at Cloudera, recently gave an interview to AiThority, shedding light on the latest trends and challenges in the industry. Additionally, Brian Holt and Marco Bambini discussed the growing popularity of SQLite and its impact on the tech world. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In a remarkable rescue story, a kite surfer found himself stranded on a remote California beach. Using rocks, he managed to spell out the word 'HELP' on the sand, catching the attention of rescuers who came to his aid. This incident highlights the importance of resourcefulness and quick thinking in emergency situations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For those interested in web development, a video tutorial on creating and deploying a web app with Python and Azure has been released. This tutorial provides step-by-step guidance on building web applications using these tools, making it accessible for beginners and experienced developers alike.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the field of artificial intelligence, FLock.io, a decentralized AI platform, has partnered with Ritual, an infrastructure provider, to enhance transparency in AI systems. This collaboration aims to address the growing concerns surrounding the lack of transparency and accountability in AI algorithms.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Astrocade, a company specializing in generative AI, has developed a platform that brings people together through social interactive experiences. This innovative technology allows users to engage with AI-generated content, fostering connections and shared experiences on a global scale.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple recently revealed its AI strategy at the Worldwide Developers Conference (WWDC). The company's approach is described as very Apple-like, emphasizing user privacy and data protection. However, this strategy also carries risks, as Apple faces competition from other tech giants in the AI space.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the world of machine learning, Microsoft has introduced SIBYL, a framework for forecasting dynamic workloads. This framework utilizes machine learning algorithms to predict and optimize resource allocation in various industries, improving efficiency and productivity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yandex, a Russian technology company, has developed and open-sourced an LLM training tool that saves up to 20 percent of GPU resources. This tool is designed to enhance the training process for machine learning models, making it more efficient and cost-effective.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Parsable, a company focused on digital transformation in frontline operations, has launched an industry-first AI-powered analytics platform. This platform revolutionizes digital transformation by providing real-time insights and data analysis, enabling organizations to make informed decisions and optimize their operations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, these developments in technology and AI highlight the ongoing advancements and innovations in various industries. From cybersecurity to web development and AI platforms, new tools, products, and projects are continuously emerging, shaping the future of our digital world.
    </summary></entry></feed>