<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Voyager</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/voyager.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/voyager.xml</id><updated>2024-02-06T20:03:02Z</updated><subtitle>Welcome to "Voyager," the podcast where the frontiers of technology, cybersecurity, and scientific discovery converge. Each week, we embark on a digital odyssey through the vast and ever-evolving landscape of the internet to bring you the most intriguing and vital stories from the realms of tech and science.

In "Voyager," we delve deep into the latest advancements in technology, from groundbreaking gadgets and innovations to the software shaping our digital world. We unravel the complex and fascinating world of cybersecurity, keeping you informed about the latest threats, defenses, and trends that matter in our increasingly connected lives.

But our journey doesn't stop there. We also traverse the exciting universe of scientific discovery, bringing you cutting-edge news, interviews with thought leaders, and insights into the research that's changing our understanding of the world and beyond.

Whether you're a tech enthusiast, a cybersecurity professional, or just curious about the scientific phenomena shaping our future, "Voyager" is your guide through the complex web of modern innovation. Join us as we explore the most compelling stories at the intersection of technology, cybersecurity, and science – stories that inform, inspire, and ignite the imagination.

Subscribe to "Voyager" and stay ahead of the curve in this fast-paced digital age. New episodes drop every week, filled with expert analysis, engaging discussions, and a passion for the marvels of the internet era. Set sail with us on this journey of discovery and exploration – into the heart of what's next.
</subtitle><entry><title>1. "Data Detectives: Uncovering the Power of Varonis MDDR"&lt;br&gt;2. "Unleashing the Future: India's Data Centre Expansion Plan"&lt;br&gt;3. "Resilience in Action: Navigating the Kahramanmaraş Earthquake Sequence"&lt;br&gt;4. "Analyzing the Past, Shaping the Future: Minimum Trace Factor Analysis"&lt;br&gt;5. "LinuxONE 4 Express: Empowering Businesses with Cyber-Resilient Hybrid Cloud and AI"&lt;br&gt;6. "Fighting for Fairness: Wage Theft Legislation in New York"&lt;br&gt;7. "Securing the Future: Cisco and NVIDIA's AI Infrastructure Solution"&lt;br&gt;8. "Loyalty in the Cloud: Flaunt's Enterprise Solution for Roblox and Shopify Plus"&lt;br&gt;9. "Behind the Scenes: FSTR CEO Reveals the Studio's Secrets"&lt;br&gt;10. "Building Bridges: Google's Investment in Rust C++ Interoperability"</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/voyager.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-02-06T20:03:02Z</published><updated>2024-02-06T20:03:02Z</updated><id>8a9a62d0-edb0-4682-9da0-e9113f4d33fd</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/voyager.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/8a9a62d0-edb0-4682-9da0-e9113f4d33fd.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent news, Varonis has introduced the industry's first Managed Data Detection and Response (MDDR) offering. This new tool aims to enhance data security by providing proactive monitoring and response to potential threats. Meanwhile, India's oldest data center operator has announced an expansion plan worth INR 1900 Cr, aiming to meet the growing demand for data storage and management services in the country. This expansion will contribute to the development of India's digital infrastructure. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another significant news is the research on the 2023 Kahramanmaraş Earthquake Sequence, which focuses on finding ways to build a more resilient, sustainable, and equitable society. This study aims to provide valuable insights into earthquake preparedness and response strategies. Additionally, a new analysis technique called Minimum Trace Factor Analysis has been introduced, offering a fresh perspective on data analysis and interpretation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;IBM has launched LinuxONE 4 Express, a cyber-resilient hybrid cloud and AI platform that aims to provide cost savings for businesses. This platform combines the power of Linux, cloud computing, and artificial intelligence to deliver efficient and secure solutions. In other technology news, Cisco and NVIDIA have partnered to help enterprises quickly deploy and manage secure AI infrastructure. This collaboration aims to provide businesses with the necessary tools and expertise to leverage AI technology effectively.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the business sector, Flaunt, a company specializing in enterprise loyalty cloud for platforms like Roblox and Shopify Plus, has raised $1.8M in funding. This investment will support the development and expansion of their loyalty programs, benefiting both businesses and customers. Additionally, the CEO of FSTR, a prominent studio, has discussed the company's history, services, and the reasons why developers hire outsourcers. This insight provides valuable information for those interested in the game development industry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, Google has made a significant contribution of $1M to the Rust Foundation to support the development of Rust C++ Interoperability. This investment aims to improve the compatibility and integration between the Rust and C++ programming languages, benefiting developers and enhancing software development practices.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, these recent developments highlight the continuous advancements in technology, data management, and business strategies, showcasing the ever-evolving nature of the world we live in.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;New Tools, Products, or Projects:&lt;br&gt;- Varonis introduces the industry's first Managed Data Detection and Response (MDDR) offering, enhancing data security.&lt;br&gt;- IBM launches LinuxONE 4 Express, a cyber-resilient hybrid cloud and AI platform for cost savings.&lt;br&gt;- Cisco and NVIDIA collaborate to help enterprises deploy and manage secure AI infrastructure.&lt;br&gt;- Flaunt raises $1.8M for their enterprise loyalty cloud for Roblox and Shopify Plus.&lt;br&gt;- Google contributes $1M to the Rust Foundation to improve Rust C++ Interoperability.
    </summary></entry></feed>