<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Voyager</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/voyager.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/voyager.xml</id><updated>2024-02-04T08:04:28Z</updated><subtitle>Welcome to "Voyager," the podcast where the frontiers of technology, cybersecurity, and scientific discovery converge. Each week, we embark on a digital odyssey through the vast and ever-evolving landscape of the internet to bring you the most intriguing and vital stories from the realms of tech and science.

In "Voyager," we delve deep into the latest advancements in technology, from groundbreaking gadgets and innovations to the software shaping our digital world. We unravel the complex and fascinating world of cybersecurity, keeping you informed about the latest threats, defenses, and trends that matter in our increasingly connected lives.

But our journey doesn't stop there. We also traverse the exciting universe of scientific discovery, bringing you cutting-edge news, interviews with thought leaders, and insights into the research that's changing our understanding of the world and beyond.

Whether you're a tech enthusiast, a cybersecurity professional, or just curious about the scientific phenomena shaping our future, "Voyager" is your guide through the complex web of modern innovation. Join us as we explore the most compelling stories at the intersection of technology, cybersecurity, and science – stories that inform, inspire, and ignite the imagination.

Subscribe to "Voyager" and stay ahead of the curve in this fast-paced digital age. New episodes drop every week, filled with expert analysis, engaging discussions, and a passion for the marvels of the internet era. Set sail with us on this journey of discovery and exploration – into the heart of what's next.
</subtitle><entry><title>"The Data Scientist's Edge: Unveiling the 40 Under 40 Winners of 2024"&lt;br&gt;"Crypto Tax Talk: Are the Crypto Bros Paying Up?"&lt;br&gt;"Microsoft vs. Activision Blizzard: Gaming Takes the Lead"&lt;br&gt;"Web-Based RISC-V Compiler: TCC's Breakthrough with Zig Compiler"&lt;br&gt;"AI on a Raspberry Pi: Exploring Speech Recognition and PTT"&lt;br&gt;"Atropos Health: Revolutionizing Healthcare with Google Cloud"&lt;br&gt;"Chipotle's Gen Z Revolution: New Benefits for a Growing Workforce"&lt;br&gt;"Inside the Vision Pro: iFixit's Deep Dive into the Tech"&lt;br&gt;"Clarifying the Numbers: Microsoft's Gaming vs. Windows Revenue"&lt;br&gt;"Tempus One: Empowering Lens Data Analytics with AI Assistant"</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/voyager.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-02-04T08:04:28Z</published><updated>2024-02-04T08:04:28Z</updated><id>f2b68909-25b6-4857-ba7f-3c799229b6b1</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/voyager.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/f2b68909-25b6-4857-ba7f-3c799229b6b1.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of data science, the 40 Under 40 Data Scientists Awards for 2024 have been announced, showcasing the brightest minds in the field. Meanwhile, there is a growing concern about crypto enthusiasts and their tax obligations on their gains. Microsoft's latest quarter results have been visualized, with the inclusion of Activision Blizzard for the first time, highlighting the increasing significance of gaming over Windows. In a fascinating development, the TCC RISC-V Compiler can now run in web browsers, thanks to the Zig Compiler. Additionally, a weekend AI project involving speech recognition, PTT, and a large action model on a Raspberry Pi has caught attention. Atropos Health is leveraging Google Cloud to generate actionable clinical evidence for healthcare institutions. Chipotle is introducing new benefits to attract and support its growing Gen Z workforce. iFixit has dissected the Vision Pro, revealing its internal components such as connectors, screens, and fans. Lastly, Tempus has launched an AI assistant called 'Tempus One' to enhance research in their lens data analytics platform.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, the TCC RISC-V Compiler running in web browsers is a significant advancement, allowing for greater accessibility and convenience in programming. The weekend AI project utilizing speech recognition and a large action model on a Raspberry Pi demonstrates the potential for AI applications in everyday devices. Atropos Health's use of Google Cloud to generate actionable clinical evidence showcases the power of cloud computing in the healthcare industry. Chipotle's introduction of new benefits for its Gen Z workforce highlights the importance of attracting and supporting the younger generation in the workplace. Lastly, Tempus' AI assistant 'Tempus One' promises to enhance research capabilities in their lens data analytics platform, potentially revolutionizing the field of data analysis.
    </summary></entry></feed>