<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Voyager</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/voyager.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/voyager.xml</id><updated>2024-04-23T16:03:36Z</updated><subtitle>Welcome to "Voyager," the podcast where the frontiers of technology, cybersecurity, and scientific discovery converge. Each week, we embark on a digital odyssey through the vast and ever-evolving landscape of the internet to bring you the most intriguing and vital stories from the realms of tech and science.

In "Voyager," we delve deep into the latest advancements in technology, from groundbreaking gadgets and innovations to the software shaping our digital world. We unravel the complex and fascinating world of cybersecurity, keeping you informed about the latest threats, defenses, and trends that matter in our increasingly connected lives.

But our journey doesn't stop there. We also traverse the exciting universe of scientific discovery, bringing you cutting-edge news, interviews with thought leaders, and insights into the research that's changing our understanding of the world and beyond.

Whether you're a tech enthusiast, a cybersecurity professional, or just curious about the scientific phenomena shaping our future, "Voyager" is your guide through the complex web of modern innovation. Join us as we explore the most compelling stories at the intersection of technology, cybersecurity, and science – stories that inform, inspire, and ignite the imagination.

Subscribe to "Voyager" and stay ahead of the curve in this fast-paced digital age. New episodes drop every week, filled with expert analysis, engaging discussions, and a passion for the marvels of the internet era. Set sail with us on this journey of discovery and exploration – into the heart of what's next.
</subtitle><entry><title>"AI Scam Calls Exposed: Safeguarding Yourself and Loved Ones"</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/voyager.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-04-23T16:03:36Z</published><updated>2024-04-23T16:03:36Z</updated><id>faf91a81-2be6-436b-83b4-9dc3ca5c1550</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/voyager.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/faf91a81-2be6-436b-83b4-9dc3ca5c1550.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent news, there have been several developments in the world of AI. One concerning issue is the rise of AI scam calls, which can pose a threat to individuals and their loved ones. It is important to take precautions to protect ourselves from such scams. On a different note, China has acquired US-restricted Nvidia AI chips, as revealed in tenders. This acquisition showcases China's growing interest in AI technology. Similarly, Vietnam's FPT has announced its plans to invest $200 million in an AI factory that will utilize Nvidia chips. This investment highlights the increasing global interest in AI and its potential applications. In the software industry, Pico has launched machine learning and AI capabilities in its Corvil Analytics 10.0 software release. This advancement will enhance data analysis and insights for users. However, with the rise of AI, there has also been an increase in AI-driven phishing attacks, as discovered by Zscaler Research. This highlights the need for improved cybersecurity measures to combat such threats. Moving on to technology projects, Microsoft has made a new push into smaller AI systems, as reported by The New York Times. This indicates a shift towards more accessible and user-friendly AI solutions. Additionally, Google has ventured into AI applications for military disaster response, aiming to leverage AI technology to aid in emergency situations. Lastly, a recent study has connected gut bacteria metabolites to the progression of Alzheimer's disease, thanks to AI. This breakthrough could potentially lead to new insights and treatments for the disease. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In terms of new tools, products, or projects, there are a few notable mentions. Pico's Corvil Analytics 10.0 software release introduces machine learning and AI capabilities, enhancing data analysis and insights for users. Microsoft's push into smaller AI systems signifies the development of more accessible and user-friendly AI solutions. Google's AI venture to assist the military in disaster response showcases the potential applications of AI in emergency situations. Lastly, the study connecting gut bacteria metabolites to Alzheimer's disease progression demonstrates the power of AI in uncovering new insights and potential treatments for complex diseases. These advancements highlight the continuous progress being made in the field of AI and its wide-ranging impact on various industries.
    </summary></entry></feed>