<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Voyager</title><link href="https://novasparkxx.github.io/vite.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://novasparkxx.github.io/vite.xml</id><updated>2024-02-02T00:41:18Z</updated><subtitle>RSS feed based on RSS and LLM.</subtitle><entry><title>Vite report on Fri, 02 Feb 2024 00:41:18</title><link href="https://novasparkxx.github.io/vite.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-02-02T00:41:18Z</published><updated>2024-02-02T00:41:18Z</updated><id>aa3d0e27-f7de-4939-a737-3eddefee0af4</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://imgproxy.nanxiongnandi.com/P_O89MPBYlhmFIfXN1-KWHdQIOZ40lkQcMHMZlMdWf8/w:1280/aHR0cHM6Ly9pbWcu/bmFueGlvbmduYW5k/aS5jb20vMjAyNDAx/L0J1a2hhbnNhblNl/b3VsLmpwZw.jpg" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/aa3d0e27-f7de-4939-a737-3eddefee0af4.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world today, there are several noteworthy events taking place. Firstly, there is a growing trend of more people joining the tech industry. This surge in interest raises questions about the future of the job market and how it will be affected. Additionally, Rashida Tlaib, despite facing House censure and criticism over her views on Israel, has managed to raise an astounding $3.6 million. This achievement showcases her ability to rally support despite the challenges she faces. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the realm of technology, there have been some exciting developments. Azure OpenAI Service is now being utilized to generate images with DALL-E in .NET. This integration of advanced AI technology with Microsoft's cloud platform opens up new possibilities for image generation and manipulation. Furthermore, FanDuel TV has brought premier programming to Las Vegas for Super Bowl LVIII, enhancing the entertainment experience for sports enthusiasts. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For those interested in app analytics, there is a new tool called Custom Interactions for AppExchange App Analytics. This tool promises to provide better user insights, allowing developers to understand user behavior and optimize their apps accordingly. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the world of web development, a guide on how to create modals with Rails and Hotwire (and Tailwind CSS) has been released. This guide offers valuable insights and techniques for developers looking to enhance their web applications with interactive modals. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shifting gears to the real estate market, it has been observed that a record number of wealthy individuals are purchasing mansions with cash. This trend highlights the financial strength and preferences of the affluent population. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In the field of statistics, a new R Package called npcure has been introduced. This package focuses on nonparametric inference in mixture cure models, providing statisticians with a valuable tool for their research and analysis. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly, open source models have been found to be superior to GPT-4 due to their access to external data. This discovery emphasizes the importance of incorporating diverse and extensive datasets in order to enhance the performance and accuracy of AI models. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, these events and developments showcase the dynamic nature of the world we live in, with advancements in technology, politics, entertainment, and various other fields shaping our present and future.
    </summary></entry></feed>