<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Voyager</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.fun/podcast/voyager.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.fun/podcast/voyager.xml</id><updated>2024-10-18T16:08:27Z</updated><subtitle>Welcome to "Voyager," the podcast where the frontiers of technology, cybersecurity, and scientific discovery converge. Each week, we embark on a digital odyssey through the vast and ever-evolving landscape of the internet to bring you the most intriguing and vital stories from the realms of tech and science.

In "Voyager," we delve deep into the latest advancements in technology, from groundbreaking gadgets and innovations to the software shaping our digital world. We unravel the complex and fascinating world of cybersecurity, keeping you informed about the latest threats, defenses, and trends that matter in our increasingly connected lives.

But our journey doesn't stop there. We also traverse the exciting universe of scientific discovery, bringing you cutting-edge news, interviews with thought leaders, and insights into the research that's changing our understanding of the world and beyond.

Whether you're a tech enthusiast, a cybersecurity professional, or just curious about the scientific phenomena shaping our future, "Voyager" is your guide through the complex web of modern innovation. Join us as we explore the most compelling stories at the intersection of technology, cybersecurity, and science – stories that inform, inspire, and ignite the imagination.

Subscribe to "Voyager" and stay ahead of the curve in this fast-paced digital age. New episodes drop every week, filled with expert analysis, engaging discussions, and a passion for the marvels of the internet era. Set sail with us on this journey of discovery and exploration – into the heart of what's next.
</subtitle><entry><title>AI Unplugged: Navigating the Future of Multimodal Models, Security, and Scams</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.fun/podcast/voyager.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-10-18T16:08:27Z</published><updated>2024-10-18T16:08:27Z</updated><id>dff71322-cf94-4729-98e1-1a679e0048be</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.fun/cover/voyager.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/dff71322-cf94-4729-98e1-1a679e0048be.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In recent global developments, the tech landscape is witnessing significant advancements in artificial intelligence and its applications. DeepSeek AI has unveiled Janus, a groundbreaking multimodal model boasting 1.3 billion parameters, which includes capabilities for image generation. Meanwhile, H2O.ai has launched new multimodal foundation models specifically designed to tackle document AI use cases, enhancing efficiency in data processing. In a collaborative effort, MetConnections has partnered with HTEC to create an innovative AI-assisted connections application, aiming to improve user interactions. On the cybersecurity front, a new zero-touch cloud security initiative is automating threat detection and remediation through a collaboration involving Wiz, AWS Security Hub, and GitHub Actions. Additionally, researchers have made strides in understanding how language models develop semantic attention by learning from data, providing new insights into AI's cognitive processes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;However, the rise of AI technology also brings challenges. A troubling incident in California highlighted the potential dangers of AI voice technology, where scammers exploited this capability to deceive an elderly man into transferring $25,000 under the false pretense that his son was in a serious accident. In a cautionary note, prosecutors in Washington State have warned police against using generative AI for writing reports, emphasizing the need for human oversight in critical documentation. In the business sector, Chinese self-driving startup Pony AI has filed for an IPO in the U.S., signaling a growing interest in autonomous vehicle technologies. Lastly, Google has enhanced its AI podcast generator, making it more customizable for users, reflecting the ongoing trend of personalizing AI-driven tools.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;### New Tools, Products, and Projects:&lt;br&gt;1. **Janus by DeepSeek AI**: A multimodal model with image generation capabilities, featuring 1.3 billion parameters.&lt;br&gt;2. **H2O.ai Multimodal Foundation Models**: New models aimed at improving document AI use cases.&lt;br&gt;3. **AI-assisted Connections Application**: A collaborative project between MetConnections and HTEC to enhance user interactions.&lt;br&gt;4. **Zero-Touch Cloud Security Initiative**: A security framework automating threat detection and remediation involving Wiz, AWS Security Hub, and GitHub Actions.&lt;br&gt;5. **Google's Customizable AI Podcast Generator**: An upgraded tool allowing users to personalize their podcast generation experience.
    </summary></entry></feed>