<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Voyager</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/voyager.xml" rel="alternate"></link><id>https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/voyager.xml</id><updated>2024-03-20T16:04:11Z</updated><subtitle>Welcome to "Voyager," the podcast where the frontiers of technology, cybersecurity, and scientific discovery converge. Each week, we embark on a digital odyssey through the vast and ever-evolving landscape of the internet to bring you the most intriguing and vital stories from the realms of tech and science.

In "Voyager," we delve deep into the latest advancements in technology, from groundbreaking gadgets and innovations to the software shaping our digital world. We unravel the complex and fascinating world of cybersecurity, keeping you informed about the latest threats, defenses, and trends that matter in our increasingly connected lives.

But our journey doesn't stop there. We also traverse the exciting universe of scientific discovery, bringing you cutting-edge news, interviews with thought leaders, and insights into the research that's changing our understanding of the world and beyond.

Whether you're a tech enthusiast, a cybersecurity professional, or just curious about the scientific phenomena shaping our future, "Voyager" is your guide through the complex web of modern innovation. Join us as we explore the most compelling stories at the intersection of technology, cybersecurity, and science – stories that inform, inspire, and ignite the imagination.

Subscribe to "Voyager" and stay ahead of the curve in this fast-paced digital age. New episodes drop every week, filled with expert analysis, engaging discussions, and a passion for the marvels of the internet era. Set sail with us on this journey of discovery and exploration – into the heart of what's next.
</subtitle><entry><title>"AI Showdown: Nvidia vs. AMD - Which Stock Should You Buy?"</title><link href="https://podcast.novaspark.io/podcast/voyager.xml" rel="alternate"></link><published>2024-03-20T16:04:11Z</published><updated>2024-03-20T16:04:11Z</updated><id>fd77f034-1948-4caa-96bb-32d6c544eb16</id><summary type="html">
        &lt;img src="https://podcast.novaspark.io/cover/voyager.png" alt="Article Image"&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        &lt;audio controls&gt;
            &lt;source src="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/novasparkxx/novasparkxx.github.io/main/voice/fd77f034-1948-4caa-96bb-32d6c544eb16.mp3" type="audio/mpeg"&gt;
            Your browser does not support the audio element.
        &lt;/audio&gt;
        &lt;br&gt;
        In the world of technology, the battle of the super AI chips has caught the attention of investors. The question arises whether it is the right time to buy stocks of Nvidia or AMD. Both companies are known for their advanced AI chips and have been competing fiercely in the market. Meanwhile, a Spring Boot App has been implemented that utilizes AWS Secrets Manager to securely store MongoDB credentials. This ensures the protection of sensitive data in the app. Artificial intelligence is making a significant impact on the manufacturing industry, as highlighted in a comprehensive overview with Beckhoff. The article explores how AI is transforming various aspects of manufacturing processes. In other news, Saudi Arabia has announced plans to establish a $40 billion fund dedicated to investing in artificial intelligence. This initiative demonstrates the country's commitment to embracing AI technology and its potential benefits. Despite a slight decline in revenue, Xiaomi has reported strong net profit growth in 2023. The company's success showcases the growing demand for its products and services. Renowned AI expert Geoffrey Hinton believes that AI is rapidly approaching the level of human intelligence. His statement reflects the remarkable progress made in the field of artificial intelligence. Microsoft has made a strategic move by hiring the chief of Inflection, a company specializing in consumer AI. This move indicates Microsoft's ambition to dominate the consumer AI market. While artificial intelligence is gaining prominence in various fields, sports analytics may be lagging behind. The Associated Press suggests that AI applications in sports analytics are not as prevalent as in other industries. Lastly, for those seeking a live translation app that runs constantly across their screen, there are various options available. These apps provide real-time translation, making communication across different languages more convenient and efficient.
    </summary></entry></feed>